(lyrics)
Hi guys.
Hold up.
Let me turn the music down a little bit.
Everybody. What's up.
Good evening. Good morning.
Hope a lot of people.
didn't have to wake up too early
for this as well, but.
Hey. Hi, everybody.
Hope you're having a good day so far.
It's been a little bit,
but I've been working hard.
I've been working
really, really hard for the stream.
Because, you know,
I've wanted to really make sure
I knew how to do some of these songs.
So that's why, you know, I spent.
Pretty much all.
Day today and all day yesterday doing
what's it called?
Just practising a bunch of songs
Umm,for the stream.
I am going to have sound
alerts and notifications off in order to,
you know, just make sure there's
no interruptions during the stream.
But I will probably be doing
a reading for all of the
for all the donations and
any other messages
you guys send after we do our karaoke, OK?
So we'll have a bit of an.
After party and then just chill and chat
once the karaoke is over.
If that sounds good to you guys.
All right.
Yeah, we are.
And I'm so nervous.
I don't know why. I've done karaokes before,
but I think it's.
Just because, like,
I don't know, there's just so much more
so many more of you guys around now.
That makes it.
All the more like my heart
is going really fast.
Right now.
Like, if I had the microphone the yes on
my microphone, I could let you guys hear.
Actually, I do, but. I don't think
I want to do that. Right now.
It's gone.
Ba dum ba dum ba dum, ba dum, ba dum.
And and my hands are,
you know, I'm doing the thing
where when I get nervous,
I, like, rub my legs.
Oh, my God.
I don't know why.
It's like the nerves are getting to me
right now, but I think, like, once
you get into the songs, it'll be OK.
Yeah, we've done
karaoke before, but it's just,
you know, I'm.
I'm. I'm shy of it from time to time,
I guess.
I don't know.
I'm just the.
Ignore me in my, you know, nerves
getting all over the place.
But, yeah. I
I think I have.
Quite a few songs that I just want to sing
that are kind of new.
And there's some there's going to be
some old ones returning,
but I'm OK with taking song requests
in, in between songs, but,
you know, just don't request it
during the songs.
When I'm done with a song.
In between, we can talk.
And then if you have a request,
that's something I know I can't promise
I can do like a song that, ah,
what's that?
I can't promise that I can do a song
that you
want me to do because I may not know it.
Right? I can, I can
attempt to,
if I know the song though, but like.
Yeah.
But, oh dude, I,
I'm so excited because this is a big.
Celebration for a really big milestone
that we hit on the channel.
300 K on Twitch is no joke, guys.
That's a lot of people and it's a
make even like, you know, more crazy.
It's over that over
before I drink on Twitter
and on YouTube,
we're almost at 400 as well like that.
There's a lot happening.
There's a lot, a lot happening
and I got a lot of plans
and there's like new there's
so much coming down the line and I hope
everyone's excited for it
cause I am super stoked for everything
that's going to be happening
Congratulations on all the followers.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Congrats. Congrats.
Thank you, guys.
I don't know.
Why I was so nervous today, ah but
just got to shake off the nervous.
Shoto, shake off the nervous.
It's. It'll be okay.
Is my throat OK?
Yeah, my throat is OK. Yesterday, I.
Kind of overdid it
because I realised, like,
it got really raspy,
but I slept with my humidifier on and
gave it some proper rest in the morning
before I practise again.
So I think I'm pretty. Yeah, pretty good.
I feel I am pretty good.
I don't think there's going
to be any problems, but I know my limits,
so don't worry.
I will be able to.
I'll stop when I feel like it's too much.
But usually I can handle what my throat is
a, you know, a sturdy boy.
He's got it.
But hopefully.
Everyone's been having a wonderful week
so far.
It's already Friday.
It's Saturday for some of you.
Saturday morning, I think an hour
or about to head into another week.
It's it's almost may believe that
April is already almost over and then.
We're heading into another month of spring
and then summer's coming down the line.
And man, it's crazy, guys.
Like we're
almost to the halfway point for the year
it's it's a really fucking crazy dude,
but I'm excited for everything
that's coming.
And like I said before, hopefully
your week's been good
and everyone's doing well
for your exams
because I know it's a busy exam period.
So. So, like I said, Livestream,
you got this.
All right?
Don't don't stress out too much over it.
Just take it easy and, like, don't,
you know, cram everything.
You'll be fine.
Lots of people are still doing exams,
but if you.
Finish your exams,
hey, pog, you're done, GG, guys.
You made it
to the yards at the end of the year
and gets enjoy your summer vacation break.
Right. I'll I think a lot of.
People get to enjoy their breaks now
since they're done with school.
OK, but I think.
We can probably head into the first song
just to, like,
you know, get things, you know, break,
break the ice for tonight.
Guessing are an old favourite of mine
I've done on the channel
quite a few times,
but I'm not like all the time,
but I like the song a lot
and if you guys want to guess,
you guys want to guess what song it is.
It's something we've seen before, so
probably not too much of a surprise mm.
Lemon.
No, not lemon.
Oh, give me a second.
Wait a second. What's happening?
Oh, no. Oh,
oh, God.
Internet
oh, no way.
Internet.
What are you doing?
Oh, no. Oh.
Oh, god. OK.
All Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, dude.
Really?
Ah, I think. I'm.
Ah. It seems that there is some lag. Hmm.
Hold on.
I think it might get better.
Hopefully that was temporary
yeah.
Hopefully it's back now. Oh, my God.
I don't know what that was.
Mm. Is it butter?
I think it's better now. Oh, jeez.
Oh, jeez.
It's like. Uh.
Can you guys hear me?
Is everything back
where we were chillin or die?
Jobs.
Are things ok?
OK, yeah.
Just be sure to.
Refresh the stream. Hold on. Let me check
to make sure that everything's good.
I hope. I hope.
And and
that's not being dumb again tonight,
because if it is then I would be very sad.
I could. Yeah.
Just refresh on if everything's OK.
If it's a bit laggy.
I think it's good now.
I think it was just a temporary hiccup.
We cool now?
OK, yeah.
We'll wait a little bit
until everyone, like,
you know, everyone stabilises again
because.
I think that was just a.
Little you know, we're a little
kind of.
Just just a small. Blip.
Don't know why that happened, though.
I think we're good now. Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I don't know why that happened.
Hmm. That's odd.
Well, hopefully that doesn't happen
for the rest of the night,
because if it and look.
Well, I'm gonna.
I'm going to eat Comcast's.
Arse. OK?
But a lot of you are saying quite it's.
Did I really think that that much?
I do. To be honest. You're right.
But no. We're not singing that one today.
Um, yeah.
Hold on. Give me a second. I'm gonna
find the lyrics for it right now.
Because I didn't pull up the lyrics
like a smart move.
Why don't I do that beforehand?
Hold on. OK.
All right.
There it is.
All right, here we go.
For some of the night
now was my. Heart, dude.
My heart needs to get it
under control. Ah,
all right.
私は私
貴方は貴方と
昨夜言ってた そんな気もする
わ~~
グレイのジャケットに
見覚えがある
コーヒーのしみ
相変らずなのね
ショーウィンドウに
二人映れば
stay with me
真夜中のドアをたたき
帰らないでと泣いた
あの季節が 今 目の前
Stay with me 口ぐせを言いながら
二人の瞬間を
抱いて
まだ忘れず 大事に
していた
恋と愛とは
違うものだよと
昨夜言われた
そんな気もするわ
二度目の冬が来て
離れていった貴方の心
ふり返ればいつも
そこに 貴方を
感じていたの
Stay with me
真夜中のドアを
たたき 心に穴が
あいた
あの季節が
今 目の前 stay with me
口ぐせを言いながら
二人の瞬間を抱いて
まだ忘れず
暖めてた
まだ忘れず 大事にしていた
oh! Uh.
shake off nervous, Shoto.
Come on, it's not that bad.
Oh, my God I feel I feel like I of.
Bruh ruh ruh ruh.
I got.
I got real nervous during that one, bros.
Damn, I think I fumbled a lyric or two,
but that's OK.
That's OK.
So yeah,
that was the first song of the night.
Stay with. Me. It's uhm.
I only.
Got in so like,
you know, city pop not too long ago,
but it quickly became one of my favourites
because of the city pop.
or Japanese pop genre and God it is,
it's such a beautiful song.
I always go back to it
whenever I want it, you know, just
like the original song.
I like the guitar version
or anything like the O.G version.
It's so fucking good and I recommend
people listen to the full thing
if they haven't before.
I'm glad you guys liked it.
Thank you so much.
Like I said before, I.
Will read through the donas.
All of the gift, subs, and bits after
the karaoke session is over. OK.
I promise I will
I love you guys.
I'm glad everyone was able to,
you know, come by today
and make time for this because.
I really.
Wanted to do something special.
As a, you know, as a celebration stream
for a
for this milestone.
And I thought, you know,
I think another like
alcohol, whatever, one shot, one screams,
everything would just be like, yeah.
But I think the best way I can do it
is by sharing something
that is really precious to me
and something that I feel like
is probably my most prised.
Oh, I don't know.
In most
the thing
I'm like most shy about my singing.
Like, I fully believe that anybody
who shares their singing voice
with the world or like any other person
or just like another of friends or an
individual, it's something very special.
Singing and hearing somebody like
their own
singing is something magical to me.
And that's. Why. I.
I feel like
hearing being like, graced
with somebody else's voice when they sing
a song is like one of the highest honours,
I guess, to me.
So that's why when people had their
first time karaoke is
like, you know, my other friends did.
It was just.
It made me smile.
It made me smile so much.
And I really hope I get to hear
more people who haven't sing, sung
Yeah.
We're
going to be drinking some alcohol later,
but I don't have
I have some in the fridge nearby
so. Yeah, that was.
Stay with me
I hope you guys enjoyed that
So this next Song
I wanted.
To talk a bit before we sing the song.
It's been.
It's been wonderful.
And I have.
Loved every moment we've
gone to share together on our adventure.
And the reason why I started this guild
and the reason why I'm here with you all
now is because of a promise
to a friend and
a friend.
It's a friend who was lost long ago.
Many, along with many others from my home,
we promised each other to see the world
to go on many adventures to soar,
the blue skies of elves on ships
into coastal waters of the east.
But and we wanted to do it all together.
Hand in hand. And that was our dream. But
he's not with me anymore.
And since that day, our
since I'd say I was
lost, confused, and.
And I didn't know what to have my.
Myself.
I had no one,
and I lost everything I cared for.
But being in this guild with all of you
and continuing to
grow and rebuild
this family, I once lost
has been the most surreal journey.
And I promised Aether
that I would see the world with him.
But now I carry on that promise
to you guys and to myself.
And I vow to journey forever and ever.
As long as my soul continues to burn.
As long as my legs can stand.
And as long as you all
will stay by my side.
I mean, I just want to adventure
and carry on his wish
for not only the both of us,
but for me and my guilds.
Like,
I'm your guild leader and it's been
it's been the greatest honour
in the world to be someone that
to be someone that you can look up to,
to be someone to inspire
and to laugh with and
I promise
I promise to take you
my guildies,
that as long as you're with me
and as long as you're with the Guild,
no, I will continue to do my best
and make this an unforgettable journey.
An unforgettable journey to remember
for the rest of your lives.
And I. I
I want to hold.
On to this feeling you've given me.
And I never wants these journeys to end.
And I'm prepared
to take on the strongest of bosses,
the most difficult of rides.
And I sound like it and the most
intimidating of our worlds.
Unknowns in order to keep doing
what I'm doing with you all
now for as long as I can and I just.
I really want to try.
I really just wanna try
So thank you all
for making me
the happiest boy in the world.
Really?
I can't.
I can't thank you enough for that.
And for helping me fulfil my promise
The next song
I wanted to sing captures that
this feeling that I've been holding on
since the very beginning
and since we've gone on this journey
together.
And it's called The Promise of the World.
It's from Howl's Moving Castle.
I think a few of you might know it
I've never sung this before.
I've tried to practise, and I hope it goes
well.
I'm OK.
I gotta look up the lyrics.
There it is.
You're so dumb shoto.
涙の奥に
~
ゆらぐほほえみは
時の始めからの
世界の
約束
~
いまは一人
でも二人の昨日
から 今日
は生まれきらめく
初めて会った日のように
~
思い出のう
ちに
あなたはいない
~
そよかぜとなって
頬に触れてくる
~
（るるるら~）
木漏れ日の午後の
別れのあとも
決して
終わらない
世界
の約束.
いまは一人
でも
明日は限りない
あなたが
教えてくれた
夜にひそむ
やさしさ
思い出のうちに
あなたはい
ない
せせらぎの
歌に
この空の色に
花の香りに
いつまでも生きて
~huh
oh, god.
Oh, oh, oh.
I yeah.
That's a apologise there.
I think I. Almost ah, I think I was, I was.
Holding back a little bit
because I told myself I wouldn't.
Cry.
oh, I'm sorry.
God.
I really don't appreciate you guys a lot,
so thank you for being here
and for
for holding
that promise I made long ago to my friend.
It means a lot.
So yeah, that was
that was a promise of the world.
It's a song
composed by, you know,  Hisaishi Jō.
It's from, from
it's a Ghibli song from Howl's
Moving Castle, and it's
something
I think fondly about long ago. And
it has a
sense of nostalgia to me
til when I when I listen to it
and I finally got to learn it
and share it with you guys.
And I'm happy that I did
I hope you enjoyed it.
I didn't butcher anything.
I think I did. But
muah,
thank you guys.
Ah.
So let me add that to the list that was
promise of the world. OK?
OK. It was
I was just a little
a little shaky there, but
then I just.
The song is a lot.
More like beautiful.
I thought when I actually got to sing it
and like, you know, go through the lyrics
and learn my flow with it.
I've.
I've known the song for a long time
because I was moving.
Castle used to be part of my,
you know, childhood.
I love that movie.
And I love the
you know, I love Ghibli films a lot.
So I guess it's there's a difference
between just listening to it
and learning the songs
and learning the lyrics and like learning
the flow of it with the in like,
you know, tandem with the instrumental.
It's really beautiful.
And and I think I really don't want to.
It feel, It makes me feel
like I want to learn more songs, I guess
for lack of a good explanation there.
I think this one
of all the ones that I practise
was the
was that really pushed me
to get more motivation
to sing some more new songs
and share with you guys
oh, OK.
Yeah, that was Promise of the World.
I love you so much.
I love you guys too.
Thank you.
It's like it's very warm.
And comforting to have them.
You know, the company of my guildies here.
It's like, you know, cheer me on when.
I like I was.
Really nervous even yesterday.
Two days ago, I think that's.
When the nerves started hitting.
And I don't know why.
I guess, like,
like I said before, it's just the thought
of there being so many new guild members.
And, you know, the fact that I'm just
there's a lot of new songs still,
and it's like, out of my comfort zone.
Which is really making me
but it means a lot that you all are here.
Like, I don't know what I would do
if I don't have my guildies
there to support me. And
you guys're always still, as always still.
And I give back. OK?
But for my next song,
I think I'm going to do another good
do another one
that's familiar to a lot of you guys.
It's uh. it's another city pop song.
You guys want to take a guess?
you wanna take a guess or what it is?
It's I guess.
I've done it before multiple times as well
as solitary.
Just that.
Dude, I. Wish I could do right on time.
Oh, my God. Right on time
is such an amazing song.
Ah, I tried practising it, but.
I didn't have enough time.
I felt like and it's like.
If I want to do it right.
I got to do it right, you know? So
maybe, maybe another,
another time for another day
in the near future.
I can learn right on time.
Right on time.
Not bad up, but da da da da.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
So your next.
One is.
If you put it on before we sing it
Plus the glove.
Yeah.
On my favourites.
I I think my top to say
pop songs are plastic glove ends on
and stay with me
oh, my God.
Thank you so much for all the donations,
guys, and for the gifts subs.
I promise I'll get to it after we're done.
Thank you so much.
Yeah. OK.
Yes, a second.
Plastic love
Here we go.
hum hum hum
bala bala bababa
OK.
Still nervous, but
we got the this.
We got this.
bara
barabab do bam~
突然の
キスや
~
熱いまなざしで
恋のプロ
グラムを
~
狂わせないでね
出逢いと別れ上
手に
打ち込んで
時間がくれば終わる Don't hurry!
愛に傷ついた
あの日からずっと
昼と夜が逆の
暮らしを続けて
はやりのDiscoで
踊り明かすうちに
おぼえた魔術
なのよ I'm sorry!
私のことを
決して本気で愛さ
ないで 恋なんてただの
ゲー ム 楽しめば
それでいいの
閉ざした心を飾る
派手なドレスも靴も
孤独な友だち
私を誘う
人は皮肉なものね いつも
彼に似てるわなぜか
思い出と
重なり合う
グラスを落として急に
涙ぐんでも わけは
尋ねないでね
夜更けの高速で
眠りにつくころ
ハロゲンライトだけ
妖しく輝く
氷のように
冷たい女だと
ささやく声がしても
Don't worry
I'm just playing games
I know that's plastic love
dance to the plastic beat
another morning come
on just playing games
I know that's plastic love
Dance to the plastic beat
Another morning comes
I'm just
playing games I know that's plastic love
Dance to the plastic beat
another morning comes
I'm just playing games
I know that's plastic love
dance to plastic beat another morning
Comes oh,
oh pog.
Pog. OK
I love that song so much.
I love it so much yeah
I'm just.
~dude
Oh, my God.
Plastic love will forever
be like top tier,
top tier song
all ever listen to your answer sing, man.
And they stay with me.
They're just so fucking good.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot to ah to ask.
Because I'm a
Dumb arse. ah the volume sounds
OK, cause I forgot to ask that.
After the first song.
Does it need any adjusting?
I too quiet am I too loud?
Do I sound OK? Sounds sounds fine.
I think. Sounds fine.
It's perfect.
OK, nice. Thank you.
I don't really change it too much, but,
you know,
I just want to make sure
it wasn't like too loud or too quiet.
I don't want to, like, overpower the
the music
I don't want to like
Sounds too quiet, either.
So, yeah, that one was plastic love.
I do the, I do the.
Song a lot on the stream just because
it's, you know, it's a comfort song.
It's something that I'm.
It's like
when you go to McDonald's. Right?
And you get like the ten piece chicken
nuggets or like maybe you get the fries.
It's like the equivalent for me.
It's like my, my nuggets and fries,
essentially
so that's all I like.
That's all I get
doing it a lot for everybody.
Yeah, I do.
Payphone? Payphone.
I think that might be
a little too high for me.
I've I'm not a pay phone.
Yeah, no, no.
I don't think I can do it today.
It's, like, really, really high.
A lot of songs that I have prepared
don't go to too much.
And also, Maroon Five
just has insane range, bro.
My God.
One of these days I'll.
Be able
to, you know, increase my range that far.
Something that I really.
Wish I could do
is like.
I really wish I could share.
Recordings of when I used to sing back,
like, in back then,
because I used to practise a lot in the,
you know,
just record my shitty ...,
you know, practise sessions
when I was a lot younger.
So I wish I could, like,
do a comparison before
and like with now
just to see how much I've grown
because there's like so many songs
that I wasn't able to like reach the,
the right range and stuff, but I'm just
oh no.
I'm proud that we are able to
light switch Japanese version.
Oh my God, wait,
I've been addicted to that.
to that song recently, but I don't think I
how does it how does it go again?
Those are
mm hmm.
How did it go again?
真夜中の「もしもし」どいう意味？わかんない
それでも電話を取った　yeah
いつも
恋人ふりをして
恋遊び
が好きだけ
That's a.
It's a really nice song.
Oh, maybe next time. Fuck.
That's a really good one.
Good suggestion, but I don't think I can
you know, do today,
because it's, you know, Japanese lyrics
take some time to learn
君に
魅力
された 今回が最後
だって　何度も 言ったのに
I think that's how it goes, right?
And then that's all I.
Know because that's like,
you know, the parts I hear the most
on like tik-tok and shit
OK. Oh, for the for the next song. Mm.
I don't know which I do or which I do.
I'm like looking at my list right now. Uh,
you know,
I might try.
This out.
Because. Ah.
Yeah, I'll try this out.
It's, um.
It's an English song.
Yeah, this one is an English song.
and.
I. I thought about it a lot.
Because I have a lot of,
you know, people in China that call me.
Like, they call me Baobei and people say
that Baobei means treasure, right?
Or something precious. I don't know.
So that got me thinking.
I feel like I want to sing
something related to that.
And what do you know?
There's a song called Treasure.
By Bruno Mars that I coincidentally.
Also forgot. I knew how to sing. So
I'm going to do that
let's do treasure.
Yeah.
Yeah, baby.
That is what you want honey.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
honey here. Let me treasure you.
OK, here it is.
Uh, huh.
OK. I think this is the right one.
Gimme, gimme, gimme attention, baby.
I got to tell you a little
something about yourself.
You're wonderful. Flawless. Who?
You sexy lady, too.
But you walk around here
like you wanna be someone else.
I know.
Oh, I know that you don't know it,
but you're fine.
So fine, fine, so fine.
Oh, oh, oh, girl.
I'm gonna show you one.
You're all mine, mine, mine. treasure.
That is what you are.
honey.
You're my golden star.
You know you can make my wish come true
if you let me treasure you.
If you let me treasure you
oh, oh, oh yeah.
Pretty girl, pretty girl.
You should be smiling
A girl like you should never look so blue.
You're.
everything I see in my dreams.
I wouldn't say that to you if it wasnt true
Oh, I know that you don't know it,
but you're fine,
so fine.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, girl.
I'm gonna show you when you're mine,
oh mine
treasure
that is what you are,
honey, you're my golden star.
You know, you can make my wish come true
if you let me  treasure you.
Yeah, you
if you let me treasure
oh, oh, oh.
You are my treasure You are my treasure.
You are my treasure yeah.
You, you, you, you you are
You are my treasure You are my treasure
you you, you treasure.
That is what you are,
honey.You're my golden star.
You know you can make my wish come true.
If you let me treasure you.
If you let me treasure
oh, oh, yeah.
Ha ha, la.
So, yeah,
I thought I was thinking of you guys when.
I figured out, like, oh, treasure,
baby, that that's a
this would be a fun one.
to do.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
You're my treasure.
Let me get some more water.
Hold on.
Clean your throat
like that is never a good idea.
I have such a bad habit of doing that
every time.
Don't do what I'm doing. Like, don't do.
Like that.
It's not healthy.
It's just, like. It's.
Habitual.
Like, once you start a habit of it,
it's really hard.
So it's really hard
to break the habit. You know,
you guys enjoy that one.
Really? It's. Ah. I. I remember the song.
Like, brings me back years ago
because, um.
You know, I has a lot of.
A lot of good nostalgia
from, like, early on.
Tons of things, like 20, 12.
It's only 13 years it's ah.
It's a very.
You know, feel good but also just,
you know, Bruno Mars songs in general.
It just has that fun vibe.
Unless it's like a sad love song.
He does
yeah.
I haven't,
I don't think I've sang it ever
and except for like years ago.
So like doing this again,
it's just, man,
I don't know, it
just brought back that inner
child, I guess.
Like,
I'm just listening to the radio.
I'm singing in the backseat of the car
on a summer day.
This is going to game driven to my
cousin's house or something like that.
I don't know.
That's what that's what gives me are
memories of mostly OK.
So I wanted to switch over
to a different place for this next song.
So give me a second.
I'm going to change the
our location. Yeah.
Good. Ginger location.
So be right back, really quickly.
All right. Mm hmm.
Now just give me a second
I hope that wasn't sore.
You know, it's about
everything looks good.
Yeah.
I want to come back here because I.
I think this would fit the vibes
better for the them
or the other songs
that I wanted to sing for you guys.
I, I do really love my fair
share of K-pop or Korean songs.
And some.
Recently, I attempted to sing spring day.
I know you guys probably saw on Twitter,
and I did upload a
small version on YouTube, but
I wanted to learn the whole song,
and that's exactly what I did.
I learnt more except for the raw portions
because I'm not that good at rap yet.
I've learnt that I did
that the entirety of it or like
as much as I could of spring day
and so I thought be a good idea
to share that with you
since it became one of my favourite songs.
While it is.
Currently one of my favourite songs
because I learnt about it not too long ago
and it's just been, it's been a vibe,
it's been a real good vibe and to,
you know, have it on my, have it on my playlist
so that is our next song, Spring Day.
It's really fitting too.
because you know why
it's currently Spring
and the gang in the warmer weather.
I'm getting my allergies.
Oh my God.
I went out yesterday to go to the gym
and as soon as I stepped outside
I was sneezing and like wet. But.
It just felt so gross
because like, yeah, there's more.
The flowers are really blooming
now and are, you know, is warm.
And then I have appalonology though.
Yeah.
So I get a little I get the a stuffy nose,
which is not the best when,
you know, you're trying to sing.
So thank God it wasn't yesterday.
OK? Oh, spring day
lyrics.
Romanised
because I cannot read on Google
OK, there you go.
I really hope I don't butcher.
I know one of my.
Mods or like two of my mods are Korean
and I like to like had cannon in my head
that there are bullies
and every time I mispronounce a Korean
word they like,
they go Asian mom on me and they're like.
Oh, how could you fuck this up?
You are terrible.
You got an f you
how could you do this to our family?
Disowned that or something. I don't know.
That's like I
if I to if I like misspeak .
Like mis enunciate one
ah one honk or something it just them
I'm going to hear the never hear
the end of it from a from a couple months.
OK all right.
Ah. So hope you guys enjoy
this next one, spring day
and. Hopefully you pick.
Some flowers sometime soon.
I really want to.
Just go out and I don't know, I remember
going to Singapore like a few years ago
in Gainesville.
I could go through the gardens
by the bay and start seeing the flowers.
There was really something
beautiful in God and I go back again.
There are so many flowers there.
It smelled so nice ha.
But OK,
I'm ready.
Dum dum dum bum bum.
Bum bum bum bum.
Bum bum bum bum bum bum bum.
허공을 떠도는 작은
먼지처럼 작은
먼지처럼
날리는 눈이 나라면
조금 더 빨리
네게 닿을 수 있을 텐데 눈꽃이 떨어져요
또 조금씩 멀어져요
보고 싶다 보고 싶다
얼마나
기다려야 또 몇 밤을 더 새워야
널 보게 될까 널 보게 될까
만나게 될까
추운 겨울 끝을 지나
다시 봄날이 올 때까지
꽃 피울 때까지 그곳에 좀 더
머물러줘
Da da da da da da da
Da da da.
Da da da da
시린 널
불어내 본다 연기처럼
하얀 연기처럼
말로는 지운다 해도 사실
난 아직 널 보내지 못하는데
눈꽃이 떨어져요 또 조금씩
멀어져요
보고 싶다 보고 싶다
조금만
기다리면
며칠 밤만 더
새우면
만나러 갈게
데리러 갈게
추운 겨울 끝을 지나
다시 봄날이
올 때까지
꽃 피울 때까지
그곳에 좀 더 머물러줘
머물러줘
oh well.
And that was spring day.
OK, I'm. Ready.
I'm ready for the I'm ready for the rubber
flip flop to get, like,
smacked against my arse.
Because I know I fucked up.
I'm ready.
OK, who's going to who's going to do it.
Who's gonna
I don't know.
Who's the who's the.
Answer that's going to like.
You know, assault me cause I fucked up.
I don't know.
I'm just kidding.
Muh uh. Uh.
Yeah.
Thought I really enjoy the, um,
the melody for this song.
Is so beautiful.
The chorus, the pre-chorus.
Is so it's just so good.
Like, God damn, man
was it?
I think it was I it's I'm cooking.
Was it Jin?
I hope they're they're
parts are really good.
I think I'm.
I'm just a big fan of ballads,
I think. Yeah.
And a song that's just like a ballad
really, really hits for me.
Mm hmm.
Uh, thank you, guys.
It makes me feel better.
I'm gonna do.
Another one from most likely.
I have a couple in mind.
I want to try a
again.
From last time.
I've sang one of these before.
But I feel like
I could do a little better.
Yeah, I feel like I could do it
a little better than last time.
I know.
If you guys remember, you want wanna sing?
Yes. You want to go? Yes.
I was
it's another odds in her career and one
song so deep comma.
No, it is not deep. Come
no villon.
Eh? You got it.
Yeah.
Next one is gonna be Villon.
And filling is such a is such a bop.
I feel like I've listened to it
so many times.
But I never somehow get tired of it.
It's just really fucking good.
Yeah.
One of these days,
I do want to learn a six on sunset deja vu
all like like like
like you guys are like
the one that's like.
That says a who does love. You?
I forgot the people that sing that down
I'm still trying to learn that
one from you guys, but soon
is not is an easy song.
This is definitely not an easy song. So.
OK, well, all right.
Here we go, villain.
Let's see if I still got it.
Oh, I'm doing drink some.
More water before we get into it.
So I don't like overdo.
Anything.
Bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum, bum.
Like I want to do more.
Yeah.
Slowly integrating more Korean songs
into my, like, repertoire
or like, I was I know how to sing
Korean. OK,
we are
pretend to be the heroes on the good side.
Oh, oh,
oh, yeah.
Autumn Tonga's
song going on sec autumn goes on I on sick
sick on your coffee
pick up on me on all the gay
nunchuck inside of me go yeah not one
side of me
Go Sammy on me Sad song Gun her back
So many shades of grey
Oh get a not a song he saw
Oh Could easily
say it's a way I'm good on the roads
Oh, it's him Not because I'm a villain
When I got to sing again
It's not where my guns are going
Oh, my guts and mine got it
Well yeah I fell learn
and I got to sing again
Midsummer lights on omega on the on
and some shake on me
So I'm killing someone
Maybe killing someone
Maybe I'm killing you
who maybe are killing me Maybe we are.
Pretend to be the heroes on the good side
But what if we're the villains on the.
Other
am I good?
I'm a bad a are you good or bad?
A man gets a
no honeymoon and gun and no return
and then a gunman again say, are we good?
Are we bad?
Eh, what is good or is bad?
A they get
there were a honeymoon, a gun and said,
I'm burning than a girl just sick.
Say so many shades of grey.
Took out the mortar saw a saw Oh good.
Easily fades away I'm bored
and the roots are too much because I love.
And when they're cursing like a tomato
and more guns
I'll come on
maggots and lying Go love you love
And I never got to sing God Good Matsumoto
da dum I'm a gun The un and some shit
Chicago is soft
All villains When I go to sing
I do not
wear more guns I'll come
ohmygod roaring Go to LA
We're all villains And then I go to sing
God Give me some love Oh my God.
And oh dudes and blah.
I'm killing someone
maybe or killing someone
and maybe I'm killing you
who maybe are killing me.
Maybe we are priests
and we're the heroes on the good side
but what if we're the villains
on the other?
We all pretend to be the heroes
on the good side.
But what if we're the villains
on the other.
We are pretend to be the heroes on
the good side.
Are I try to go
for like a cool zooms are in the loft
I think I I've.
Fucked up on the back. Down.
Got is a hard as.
Far as hard how does it
oh the good easily fades away part. Ooh.
Yeah it's like trying to do a zone change
there is rough
but or like a pitch change
there is rough edges
I feel like a
I feel like we did a good job
I feel like I see a job
I love the raw
I think if there's a favourite
part of that song for me it's
definitely the
it's definitely the middle rap.
I love it so much.
It just like it goes, it
just you're such a.
Good that you could flow so it so it's
not too long, it's not too noisy or short.
It just works.
They get to day on a. Hunt
and the guns that have been in.
The gods are sick, sad,
it's really a
it's addictive.
I think that's the word I'm looking for.
Addictive. It's a deal.
Also. Thank you for the hype train, guys.
Thank you so much.
I really appreciate all the
the support we're getting tonight.
And like I said before,
I promise I'll read through everything
at the end of the karaoke session. OK.
I'll do my best.
Congrats on three energy. Kay.
Thank you, guys.
You're part of that.
300 k is like, yo, we were here.
You know, we were. Here.
As me bang my chest.
It's not a good idea.
That kind of hurt. Oof!
I just it was all
it was a monkey.
Woo monkey
been influenced by too many other beats.
Ubers.
I am like slowly adapting their language
and behavioural rhythms into my own
it's, it's.
It's not like it's not bad thing,
that thing.
Yeah.
So it's kind of like endearing,
you know. OK.
So, all right, this saw this next song
I wanted to sing
this next song
is one that I learnt recently
and it was at the request
of another guilty.
Maybe they're in the chat right now.
I'm, I'm not sure but I, I learnt the song
because I remember
promising I could try and I did and.
It's like
I'm. I'm baffled
guys that we've come this far.
I know I've said it many times
and it feels like I'm being a dead horse.
At this point, but I really just cannot
fathom everything you all have given me.
And many times I've touted my decisions
I've doubted my self-worth,
I doubt in my efforts.
But every time I have those thoughts
that seem to cloud my judgement
it's.
It's always you.
All that helped pull me from it
and make me realise
that you're all very much here.
You're, you're all
some of the kindest
and most supportive souls I've had
the honour to call my guild members,
and it really hasn't been easy since.
Sometimes I do feel like
I'm on my own
as an independent streamer, but.
It's like an art.
It's an obstacle
I'm learning to surmount every day.
And I. Have.
Good friends, I have like really good
friends that convince me otherwise.
And it's because of you guys
and it's because of my dear friends
that I'm reminded of that
I'm reminded of that fervent love.
And I owe you the world's
I owe you guys the world for making me
live what feels like a dream.
And for
the longest I could remember,
I've always wanted to
make people happy while enjoying things.
Something I, I love to do.
And this felt perfect.
And it felt more than right. And
it's all because of you
and your support
that I could be here right now.
Streaming every day as often as I do
in the mornings.
And. In the nights
to give everyone a chance to see me live.
And it understand
how much I think about you guys like
and how much I love you all for helping me
be who I am.
Like despite all the milestones.
And we just keep continuing
to grow bigger and bigger by the day.
And I just.
I see how much love you all
put into the community,
all the fan arts,
all the all the support of comments.
Every time you show up, every time you're
here, every time you come in, it's simply
it's just
it's amazing.
And I really I really.
Couldn't smile harder at the thought
of being blessed to see this every day.
And I never want to let that go.
I really I
I don't want to let it go, ever.
And one day I hope that
I can learn to see myself
as you all see me maybe,
and know why you continue to support
this dumb boy who screams a lot so much.
And is what, Suzie?
24, seven.
One day I'll know, but I'm getting there.
I promise.
This next song is called Dry Flower,
and I hope you guys enjoy it.
Double with us.
Sit on the cooter in the yo yo knife with.
Re that the sea geyser looking back
and go back to see this
gold man there Sudan.
I saw the the DA he thought the start
zero and nine there without accuracy gain
I hate the song and not the buck hurry
and thus they die on their mercy he took
oh gaga there I had to kill no cop.
Oh, well, what are their guru
gonna do you?
Not some.
Oh, I'll listen, you cat it's
never gone.
Them up on the cool Nova.
Yeah, come on.
Come on, Bucky.
You not talk of Sandbu.
Send the camera.
He's on the line.
All good eye food.
I've meet the key needle
in my living room.
Keep going.
Keep the key.
Thaw can't eat us
starving.
He needs another good day.
OK, Arthur Monoxide.
It had gotten. Warm.
I see what that's about.
Guarding their GitHub memo.
Knock not
Anthony gonna see you got it.
And the gun got out the bubble suit
at the gun
authority he thought I'm not became you a.
Sound like accurate that you look a lot.
More calm oh no the can he got us
I need I need
sea pick on me that whole sea
so good guy
he no Kiawah then been done there
then you see the kids in the
in the tar scar
see hanzi
call him a couple more boogie on that
all come off Tyburn emo
kid he turned nine off
goodbye food I wanna eat
duck to your gun got that there bar.
Keep the keep the.
Key to keep the euro us around
Zaki I got
he need my mom guy
you ready to keep the lot
the same model casita a two corral
you mean you see Kaci
gaga boom
a cocky
eyed Hogan who named the orca
sit on the gun
no, ma'am, I will your boo Sookie
your game or team attack
oh, come on,
come on, Bucky Not the law Come on sand.
Sand.
He Kira he die of murder a in my eye
now came in this on this.
Sit, sit, sit.
Does the car got your.
How ok
oh. I.
A fun fact.
Sorry. Let me take a drink.
When.
I. I learnt this song
literally today.
I learnt it today and I, I know it's some.
No it's really beautiful.
I remember I lost.
Again, like I said before,
actually getting to sing the song
and see the, you know, I
let go of the flow and learn the flow
and like realise how.
It's just it's such.
A different experience and
I'm really happy
that you guys recommended this to me.
It's a really amazing song
and I like it a lot.
It's probably going to be
something I sing again in in the future.
For Iraqi refugees to come.
They must feel like I like.
The kid, the.
Kid, the kid, the kid to eat asks. For.
It feels nice and all.
All my friends really like the song Sil.
Oh God.
So thank you to the guilty
I don't know who you were, but
I remember your recommendation
and saw it is
is by all means very well
appreciated that you know,
you got me to write it down
and try for this session.
Thank you so much.
I feel like I want to.
Do it again, though.
Mm. Would you guys.
You guys be.
OK with me trying it one more time?
Encore! Yeah.
Encore! Encore!
Oh, yeah.
I forgot to put it in the list. Ah.
All I see.
Dry flower
Now let's do it one more time.
Hmm. OK.
I, ah.
You know, I feel like I could.
I could do better.
I can do better.
This one.
This one, for sure.
Hmm. Thank you.
My guy.
The balloon
with us Zeitoun the good
the any you all you.
Life with daddy dog
Percy keys who came back in.
The back to see the sun go man
he said Donna sought the Lord
the DA Keith though the statue
when lying there with three kids
he came yeah.
The saw on that the bakery and asked
if they on their.
Most seats gonna go Google their there
I out y'all know a cop
oh what out there could Eric Garner
are you what son of Amazon
he carried along on the bird gone then
told me now oh yeah come on
come on the kill not saw
come on Santa sand
Kira he turned I know Dora
he thought of me die
Kaemi the law he be more
keep the key to keep the key
to it all I said
the balloon
Kimmy to knock they your God
the whole narcos said it
it got blown
I see what does see but God isn't
there could all be more knock
not Anthony can now see you about got it
the more the gun got out there
above us suited
the gun authority thought on that boogie
You are.
The lucky Jared.
That you do look and Mark
Oh no beat Acuna He got a
some high need any luck
see taconite a ha see so go green
coloured then I mean the
the down must see that glutamine
mean that scar see he call him on
come on the will you not.
Oh come on kaboom e
mom all Chiara he done I all
but I food of a meat duck
you gun
go about there bar keep the keep the
kids are key to he Ramos at
uh psyche
a guard he need my mom Olga
you read to get thought
the same old dog Garciaparra Good
I mean this easily
go kaboom
a cocky I you don't go moon they now
all cool suit Don that the my mommy
well your boo zuccato e your game
or team locker oh come on
come on brother Keon that's all
come on send send
he kid I need
I Your mother got in my eye now
well came in he's
all at this sit, sit, sit,
sit the cock at your.
House
how are.
And that was a dry flour
strive la mm
I hope you guys enjoyed that
I think I thank you for the anchor.
No problem.
I think, you know,
I feel like if I didn't do it justice,
usually I want to like, redo write
this onto every deal.
If I feel like,
you know, I could have done better at it.
Oh, thank you so much, guys. Oh.
You're also nice, all of you.
Are you too nice to me?
I wasn't that.
Great.
I'm still I'm.
Still trying to get used to the song.
Eventually, I'll get better.
I mean, do you like it better? Right
thank you so much listening.
And thank you for being nice
about
about every every song I've done so far.
I really like all of you guys heard the
the first take version
of this song before it's.
But it is really fucking good, man.
Yuri is his voice is amazing.
So, I mean,
I could not hold a candle to his voice
compared to mine, like, in terms of like,
is a I like his ability to sing the song.
I mean, he wrote the song.
So but then one of these days,
I'm gonna get better at the song.
Your first take is amazing.
All over a lot of the people they bring on
and the songs that they tell
the one of my favourites of all time
was the.
It's got none, none of her dah dah done.
I'm on the.
Whatever that song was God of.
I known them on my.
Yeah, I think
like the first day for
that was really cute and fun.
Mm. OK.
Oh, I mean, it's a stretch.
It's, I need to stretch my back
and my neck
so it doesn't get stuff like I feel.
Like I tense. Up my entire upper body.
When I sing,
so I need to stretch like everything. Out
so it doesn't get, like, all knotted up.
All right, that's bad for me.
Mm hmm.
I sing.
Nicole. Nicole, I dash.
You mean Nicole by this?
All My God, that's
that's another hard one.
You know, I'll add that to the list.
Maybe we can try and learn it someday.
And what's a really good song?
I look it up
because I remember listening to that.
A lot's
oh, here it is.
Oh, no, that's not it.
Oh, there it is.
No, I can't find it.
Ah, Vine.
Oh, it's. Song you're talking about.
His voice is magical till
and the song is just really good
in my circulation.
Mm hmm. Mm hmm.
That's on Monza ora
OK. Are
I want to try something.
Mm hmm.
I want to try.
Something a little different.
I, I was considering not doing this. One
and, like, not including it, but I feel.
Like.
It shouldn't be too bad.
I. Hmm.
Bear with me.
I kind of want to give it a shot.
All right. Yeah, I'll give it a shot.
I'll write it down on the plus, I think.
I don't know if you guys know this one,
but I know it's known by a different name,
but this is, like,
the one that most people know it by
it's a very short song
until OK.
I see.
Hold on.
Oh, my.
Oh, no.
Lyrics.
I'm not.
I did that.
The mother died, and then.
OK, and now you're not gonna
hear it.
Is OK.
So meet diagnostic.
Don't die then, huh?
All right,
so my the commode,
they're don't don't the die.
Go, Mom.
You mean the look,
not the to go knock may.
Well, I could die and only but the Galina.
Yeah.
Get them on that gas on me see.
On their game then my also go
move the lot you all the God it's so.
I that come out that don't want to die.
I don't know I mean I'm not going to go
look in the mirror Black Dynamite
Mama bear.
Go find them. Yeah.
Get them on the
gas on me see like I'm. The
sick and want the not the Yoba.
Garza died in my midline.
Look the burn on the head they are
there I see no harm done.
Look him let's see it doc madame
a doc or dom or that they used this song
or God
that long karate thing on again
on their salt, the salt, the all.
See them with that.
I see Sagi now khaki
well I see bands and that go ducks in it
He wanted that sword the awesome like this
that. Was
I might.
Know.
A Miri do that
encore encore
Mike one more time our time.
But I'm. Done
yeah one more time
it once more once. More.
This is such a stupid
I don't know why this.
Came into my head.
The Jonesy on fire.
I just really wanted to give it a shot.
I said, fuck it.
Right?
Fucking
behind the.
It's my command.
They're gone.
Don died.
The low can mean they're not going to go.
I'm not gonna be well.
I could die in the near not go find you.
Yeah, get them on the Carson.
You see, I'm their guy.
I'm not the
most sick month, the Martha all but God.
It's only like a small deck. Don't.
Don't die, though, Mama.
Do you mean they're not gonna to go?
I'm not gonna live or die, Mommy.
Not going die.
Yeah. Get in the gas on me.
See, on that guy.
My dad mos again.
Not the Lord, the father.
But that and Medina.
But the burn dead
and that they all died there.
I seen the home, the marquee Nazi doc
and Madama that God damn that.
They used this song God Dead or La.
Guardia dying on the.
Get on this song.
The sort the all see, the.
My God, I see the guy in the khaki.
No, I see the that cynic
what he met the guy
and then that saw
the Austin light this that.
It's not it's not a very.
Long song so.
I've them them Donald but out the down
but out I'm.
Yeah.
This one's a Vega is a bill mean
by love it a. Lot.
Because it's a little silly
can on my one
more on my one what's in there
that's the that's the.
Song I mean I think
it's like I forgot the. Original song.
It is not.
Actually called that it's like there's a
it's from something else
I just forgot the name.
It's like an OSD from a game I believe.
Yeah.
I'm sure.
Again,
you guys are silly.
You guys are so silly.
And why do coffee
coffee?
I sure
muffle your song. All my alanine.
My throat was ready for mafia song today.
I'll do one request.
Sure.
Because I not
why not?
Right.
Everybody loves a little coffee
I love coffee.
You love coffee?
Again.
Don't stay awake for too long.
It's on. Go to bed.
I'll make a cup of.
Coffee for your. Head.
I'll get you up and go and out of bed.
And I promise that one day
I'll feel fine
and then I promise that one day I'll feel
all right
and I'll make a cup of coffee
with the right amount of sugar.
I lie.
Yeah,
and I'll make a cup of coffee
with the right amount of sugar.
How you like it?
I know I can
so now how long
I'll stay for Itzhak?
Knock on your door.
Won't you come down and get me.
I like when you call me I
you make me feel nice
The cream in your eyes makes me feel warm.
Inside I
And I'll.
Make a cup.
Of coffee with the right.
Amount The sugar I get
and I'll make a cup.
Of coffee with the.
Right amount of sugar How will I get
oh, you're like.
OK, there's your coffee.
There is your coffee.
I love the I love this song
so I like it comes from the analogue.
People know it better from like the rap
that this was sampled from.
Right?
Like this the.
Rap assembled this VI arm.
And it's I just.
Like chill chill vibes.
It is I sense so much
but I'll never get tired of it.
And hey, it's kind of ironic, though.
I don't really drink coffee
like coffee for it's
not like I don't drink coffee
and e I like the song though.
I feel like I could go for a Oh yeah.
Was it that awful gato thingy.
I'll have to try one day.
That sounds really good.
I do that tomorrow.
You guys reminded me.
I think I want to try. Hold on.
I know what?
I wanted to offer
some point coffee in there, but.
This is a song that I think.
Everybody. Knows.
If you don't know this song, then
I feel like of what are you doing?
It's so it's a very.
It's very simple,
but I don't know. I
I wanted to try it here.
Here, now.
As it comes from a good movie,
a really good movie
of one of my favourite ones are not like,
be fair on that score.
Jamal
bon as much type cock.
What am I doing
Eric? Go
you got.
A friend in me.
You've got a friend in me.
When the road looks
rough ahead and miles and miles from nice.
When did you just remember what your.
Old pal said?
Boy, you've got a friend in me.
Yeah, you've got a friend in me.
But da da da da da da
da da da da
you've got a friend in me
You've got a friend in me.
You've got troubles.
I got him too.
There isn't anything I.
Wouldn't do for you.
We stick together and see. It through
because you've got a friend in me
Yeah you've got a friend in me
Some other folks
might be a little bit smarter than I am.
Bigger and stronger, too.
But none of them will ever love you
the way that I do.
It's me and you, boy.
And as the years gone by.
Our friendship will never die.
You can see.
It's our destiny Nay,
you've got a friend in me.
Yeah, you've.
Got a friend in me.
You've got a friend in me
The da da da.
Da da da da da da.
Oh. I love it so much.
I love that song so much.
It makes me want to rewatch Toy.
Story.
Shot All Love Toy Story, huh?
It's. Oh, it's a really grown man.
I don't think anyone can complain.
It's just a feel. It's.
Oh, it makes me.
Happy.
It's always something makes me happy, man.
As one of my first thoughts as Disney
movie still.
All right.
Like, I don't think anybody hasn't.
Seen Toy Story. Before. I.
I don't know anyone who hasn't seen it
before.
Or, like, knows of it
or doesn't not know of it.
Am I freezing that
right? English? I don't know.
You got a friend in me.
You got a cock in me.
OK, that's enough.
Curse the content. Huh?
So for these
it's all for this next song.
So on
oh, boy.
Well, now, knowing that no one heard that.
No one heard that.
Clip it out.
Clip it out to the other side.
Thank you.
You rhythm lads.
You fool in the harnesses, don't you?
Oh, God.
I don't think I. Can do it today.
Not to kick you.
That's mean knock on who the he car game
or your key meet in the.
And think I'm no match today.
I would really like to do it next time.
I've done it before.
We've done it
before. On the last karaoke session.
When we had our white day or that. Yeah,
but I think I'll
you know, we got like
two more songs that I want to do.
Yeah.
My God has already been almost two.
What the heck, guys?
It's three, almost 2 hours.
What's how
got that.
Down that flew by man.
Yeah, that really flew by so fast.
OK, then I'm going to switch over
to our last location night.
We're going to go somewhere else.
Let's get out this saw this little flower
field, the sakura blossom area.
I'm to take you somewhere else.
OK, baby.
Mm hmm. Hmm.
OK, been here before.
You guys remember?
Right
and you hear that?
It's the,
ah, the crickets and all that stuff.
The moon, right?
Yeah. You see that moon?
You see that moon?
If you can guess what I'm guessing
next, huh?
Yes. I'm guessing next.
I'm going to give you a little bit
of a different flair this time, though.
Usually I do it like for.
Me to them
me play amongst the stars.
But I want to try a little.
I want to try something different
this time.
OK, bear with me.
Now, bear with me for a second.
I'm going to do something
non-conventional
all right.
Well, I don't butcher this
I wish me luck.
The sexier version.
What do you mean, the sexier version?
Fly me to the moon
and let me play amongst the stars.
Lemme see what spring is like.
Jupiter serving Mars another.
But hold my hand. Hmm.
Another way it's a baby.
Kiss me and
fill my heart with song
and let miss sing for evermore
You will love our love Long for
all love worship and the saw
and not the words
Please be true
Enough though Why
I love you
Fill my heart with song
And let me say for evermore
are love long for a love worship
and that song And though I
please be true
another way it's
in other words In other words
I love you
Oh ha ha.
Oh you did it
all so far.
And that was the violence in L.A.
more often.
I don't I don't really do.
All that all that extra flair to it
because I just like to keep it simple.
But I want to try a different,
you know, style of singing it.
Let me play amongst the stars.
That was amazing.
Thank you.
You like jazz?
Don't really said gunshot. OK,
it's a lot of fun, right?
I think that's the point of our guys.
That's the point of karaoke. You know,
is got to have fun with it.
You have to have fun with it.
Oh, yeah.
I'm not having fun with it.
Then what's the point right?
Yeah.
I also hope that you guys
can feel my joy from over there.
I like I mean, like you're right
next to me.
We're holding hands.
I mean, what are.
So this next song
is going to be.
Our last song for the night
it's.
Yeah, this is going to be our last one.
And I think we're going to wrap it up
there and just have a small chill
before we end it off.
2 hours went by so fast, guys.
You really did. Wow.
But everything I've said before,
I really does hope.
I hope that rings true and that you guys
hold it near and dear to your dear hearts.
Because, I mean, what I said
this next song holds
the weight of my feelings to each and
every one of you and to the
future guild members that join our home
in some sample for a bite.
I want to sing it again
since it has a special meaning to me.
And there's a lyric in the song
that translates roughly to
I'll pluck the stars from the sky
and give them to you,
my galaxy and
I never
like to think much about the future
because. I'm.
I'm a person that loves to live
in the moments
and enjoy today rather than worry
about some all all the time.
But I know that there will be battles,
struggles and obstacles for not only me,
but for all of us.
And I mean, that's normal in the quest,
right?
In any journey or adventure, it's
never a straight line.
There's always some type of
network like this.
There's always some type of monster
or side quest or mini boss or chops
we fall into.
But that's why
we called an adventure. Right?
And that's all you guys are part of.
My no part of our.
Adventure scaled, and I'm
growing and I'm learning.
I'm expanding my skill tree
all the time, every day.
And I really want to be a better person
every single day.
And I know I won't be.
Able to please everybody, but.
I've never.
Had such a
I've never had such a strong desire
to make myself
a better version of myself
than I was yesterday before.
And so I met all of you guys
and all my precious friends. And,
I mean, I'm still young as hell,
and I'm still trying to learn the world.
And, I mean, we all are in some way,
whether we're ten, 20, 50, or even like
206 year old elves.
If you guys are out there by
I. I.
I want to try and
be an inspiration
to as many people as I can,
and it feels like
that's my duty
as your guild leader as well.
And I want to help you all realise
how far you can go as well and
to be at your happiest.
And I hope I can help you guys get there
and realise it
This next song is called Galaxy
Song and before and that song.
It's a good one.
I love it so much.
Galaxy.
Yes, remember that, right?
Cause they're on the money must.
So now they are soon.
Sony Mac the can dig.
Someone's are.
A saga off sire tons and their their bits
and not anyone
none the second son gets
Oh it's you know I can say
bearer
good does some young does in the back yard
some to gets song nigh upon
Matt than Lamar to sons
saga dun
gas man got they are my good apple
but be to Sunday night I
go yeah see them until
all right all America like how I
co-sign the pilot anywhere
cause I'm a pilot
anywhere lighting star shooting site
can they galaxy
because I'm a pilot anywhere Kazaam
your pilot make out that's about avatar
they get him on track and my galaxy.
La la da da
da da
la la da.
Da da di.
La di da.
Took in the galaxy
I lost in the mega
urban It's on so I saw it in the gun
Hey saw gun the gun
good they had I'm sad gone I saw one suns
where though beating not enough
gonna be heard he got better get big
I oh then I gun said
oh god that's some young the scene
they got their dumb did gets on
the other are it's the none much
not in God's and got man got the
my god at my pulpit
and saw the night I got
I can see it on Monday
October not a Gaga thank you
Carson a
pilot anywhere Carson a pilot
and he led lighting
star shootings that again
they galaxy Carson a pilot anywhere
Carson your pilot
they get there to pull it out
they get him on circuit in my galaxy
because I'm a pilot head anywhere
because I'm a pilot
anywhere lighting star shooting
star to game they galaxy
because I'm a pilot
I'm your pilot
lighting star shooting starts in the game
they galaxy
La la la la la la.
La, la. La
But I didn't
I, I the I'm not going to lie the
the high note was kind of a for flavour.
I, I didn't know how
all that was going to go. I.
I just felt like doing it.
And um, it kind of. Works I mean I.
I really
um, I like that song like girl me so much
and I'm glad I gets to feel
that comfortable with song so fast.
They can like, you know, free.
Myself.
Oh man.
I really
I feel so lucky to have
all of you here and
be grace
by for quite possibly the best community
I could ever ask for.
Yeah.
I love my guilty so much
thank you so much for listening.
So all my songs.
Yeah, that was my last one.
I don't want to overdo it.
I can feel like again I can feel my throat
getting a little bit raspy.
And at that point,
I think it's better to just, like,
hold it there and not, you know,
overdo anything
so I feel like
if I overdo it, it's not all that good.
I don't wanna.
Have we have to.
Stream tomorrow, too, so I don't know.
I like
wrecking myself.
Yeah.
It's never
it's never a good idea to overdo it, guys.
Never a good idea.
For all, though.
I thank you so much for listening to all
my songs and every word and everything.
I said meet me. I mean it.
I really do want to try my best
and I hope that
I can
continue to be an inspiration
for so many of you
and to show you, like, how
wonderful
you guys are as well. You've sing.
I like, I'm this,
like, lovely or like amazing person, but
look at you guys, all right?
That you guys mm.
Yeah.
That concludes our karaoke session
for the night.
I'm gonna switch on over
switch on over to
the bedroom
and just, like, have a small chill.
So give me a quick
moment, all right? I'm gonna
be back in, like, a minute or so.
I'm going to grab myself a quick drink.
Uh, I think I'll get myself.
Yeah, soju.
My soju. OK, baby,
give me a second.
Now let's use the bathroom because.
Oh, my God, I drink so much water today.
I drink so much. Voila.
I'll I'll read through all of the.
Donations and all the sobs
and all the bits during the during
the after party.
OK, so baby, give me one second
yeah.
Well, I copy
it's like a Polaroid, love.
It's not there.
Just sit on. Good guy.
I'm just kind and guy Sinatra.
But now now
listen.
I am man and got you.
A tap on gum.
Johnny's in the mood.
Tell me that.
I could go back to them.
Tonguing up
when you
kiss good,
it's like a shot and
then like a big
yeah.
Know you
on it, Gina.
Boy, I
sure to
imagine
numb. Now.
The lower down the music a bit.
I guys, I'm back.
Yeah, you missed me.
Of course you did.
Didn't, did, did, didn't.
I don't know what I said there to you.
I'll come back.
Thank you.
Thank y'all. Love I.
I got myself a little,
a small little beverage.
Not a big cluster.
Yeah.
To soar to some peaches
you I've had left over from us.
The voice is so charming.
We are proud of you.
Thank you.
All of you guys
enjoyed all the songs tonight.
Do you.
Have a favourite out of all of them.
Like we've done so many.
Good morning show love from HK all
300 K on Twitch
I will have an exam within five.
Good morning.
What's your major in college?
Oh. I don't think I'm a
I don't think I cannot say that,
but I'll keep that, you know, to myself.
But have a good morning. Ziadeh,
thank you for coming by.
Well, ok.
I promised that I
would read through all of the what's it.
Through all. Of the
donations and such right.
Now, give me a second.
Because wow, there's a lot of.
There's a lot of them ends are
I feel bad that I think lets us
say anything during the stream.
I just want to keep it's
focussed on the music and the singing.
Thanks so much for sharing your story
and time with us.
You really have to tug
at our heartstrings.
Very much appreciated
and loved by your community.
Also, congrats on the milestones.
Keep plugging on.
Keep logging on. I like that.
Thank you so much, bro.
Ah, suki, thank you for the five time
gif subs a little more.
Thank you for the donation.
So happy to see you progressing, babe.
The reason you dropped off
your son is because of your voice.
But reasons I say is you, sweetie.
I really.
Everybody says, like.
The reason why people stay or, like,
enjoy.
Like, it doesn't matter.
The game, it like the game or the
what we're doing oh.
Let's keep growing our boys.
I think people enjoy, like,
you know, just the the person.
But I don't know.
I guess I struggle to, like, accept
that sometimes because it's like.
Sometimes, like.
Sometimes I think, like, I. Really
I don't know if.
I'm doing enough for you guys and I.
I keep wanting to do more, but
it's, it's like, you know,
I think everyone in my friends can relate,
so there's like,
that internal, like, struggle, like,
am I doing enough and what's going enough?
So I always want to try and do
as much as I can for everybody.
We are lazy.
Thank you for the I don't know.
Thank you for everything, pumpkin.
You always bring a smile to my face
one eye and make me laugh when it's own.
Oh, I'm glad I can bring
a smile on their face and.
Knowing that.
Somebody laughs from my dreams still is.
You know it means the world to me.
Galaxy.
Yeah, I really like
Galaxy was a really fun time.
Then I. Got I want to sing more dry.
Flower. Dry flowers.
Such a good song, man.
Uh, I'm really, like, happy.
I learnt about it.
Thank you for the wonderful karaoke
tonight. Hmm.
I love you.
I love you guys still. Yeah,
I go.
Cause I'm
not. Yeah, I thought
not about blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
I was really vibing off far dry flower
along. Give me a. Second.
CC Oh, cc, thank you for that's all.
Now it thank you for the tell
no and zacky.
Thank you for this.
I know this is your first.
I know
you were really having a bad day today,
but hearing you sing gives me strength.
And comfort
or for all
that.
I will continue to always support
you and I look for.
It's history. Me too.
I love you, shuttle. Congrats on three.
Thank you so much.
Thank you guys so much.
I was looking complimented.
For my singing. It's just like,
man, you're making.
You're making a young boy very happy.
And inside me, there's a young boy
who has always wanted, like,
you know, someone to recognise, like,
their efforts to, like, sing better
and, like, try better at singing.
And he's like very much elated right now
and, like, having the time of his life.
Thanks to you guys. Congratulations.
I love your singing so much.
Keep going. We'll always stay with you.
Love you.
Move, move, move.
Move, move.
Thank you
any for the big dance now as well.
Thank you for this honour, too.
You're thinking someday for this this.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay, ay.
Somewhere I think there's this talk about
an s summer club.
I'll try and read that later.
Sorry. Thank you for. That's l know.
Glad to have such
an unforgettable experience.
If you.
Oh, you got me velvety.
Shut out now.
You and that's cheesy.
Hi, Sholto.
Congratulations.
On the 300
K on twitch and 400 K on twitter.
Thank you for appearing in my life.
Thank you for the karaoke stream.
I really enjoyed it.
I love you so much.
And I'm always on your side.
Guys, I'm going to I'm going to write.
I like I want to.
Grab your guys is like by the scruff.
Give you a little kiss on the cheek
and toss you in.
So, like, I don't know
until like a field of flowers.
I'm not think of it.
It's ancient. Sorry. Your voice
so comfy that I actually fell asleep.
Yeah, I have important interview.
And today, please lend me a little
good luck.
Good luck to you.
You got this? I believe in you.
All right.
Guys, what?
You got this, bro?
Asuka, thank you for the doll.
Now, a sort of subtle softball.
I love you.
Thank you for your sweet singing
from him, bro.
I hope I can do more karaoke.
In the future for everybody.
This one was supposed to be
a very special occasion, and I hope
we can do another one probably next month
or in the couple of months after.
You know, I practise some more songs
oh. I'm going to go back and read through
some of the earlier ads on Asian
Steel and stuff like the most recent ones.
Coffee. Thank you for the resolver.
Welcome back.
And I hope you've been doing well, bro.
Where is it?
I am. I'm stupid.
I'm stupid. Where is it?
I know
my dumb boy.
I'm a fucking dumb boy.
Oh, my God.
Here it is.
All right,
euphoria.
Thank you for the.
Odds on our gum,
but the thank you so much.
And that's it.
Ah! Oh, my God.
Machida, what's
all this shit?
Thank you for the 1000
1000.
Oh, Mike.
Dude, what the fuck?
I don't.
I don't know. With the holy shit, dude.
I'm like, oh, that's.
That's a lot of.
Yeah, that's a lot of money.
Are you. Sure?
Are you sure?
I, I, I.
I oh.
Oh, wow.
That's a very big deal.
No, dude, I
thank you so much.
I hope you are.
I hope you're able to,
you know, feed yourself.
And, you know, enjoy your.
Treat yourself as well.
I don't give too much to me. OK?
I really do appreciate it, though.
Thank you so much.
But I really hope that, you know,
you're well off, too, and that, you know,
you're taking care of yourself.
Bro, it means a lot. Thank you.
You, too.
You're been such a big supporter
of the Charlottesville.
It means like the world to me
that you continue to do so
and so support not only me, but
the guilds as well.
Thank you so much.
I'd love
to see you. And you are.
Thank you for.
The 1000 berries.
Can graduation.
Can graduation. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Overall,
and another year for the five johns.
Thank you for the $3.
Golly, Gail, thank you for that.
Sincerely and yourselves.
Your supporters.
Thank you for that.
Well, now, congrats on for an education.
We plan to set up a pa pa pa pa
You want a name for your group?
Mm. Shuttles, wolf squad.
Oh, that sounds funny.
Oh, my God.
Shuttle's Wolf Squad.
I don't know something.
Hmm. You guys got.
I don't.
I don't know. What I would say. Huh.
Sounds like a funny name.
Wolf.
I'm not dog, though.
It sounds. You know, just
because, like I say this every time,
just because I bark, because I know.
Because I.
You know, it doesn't mean I'm a dog.
Do you see ears anywhere?
I don't think so.
And you guys can't put any ears.
On me tonight
because I turn it off. So get. Direct.
Yogi.
Thank you for the honour.
So are we listening to your stream
and class?
Is your first time
catching up your karaoke?
Oh, OK. Lack of class, dude.
Pay attention in class. Don't.
Guys, guys.
Pay attention, class. OK,
I thank you for the ads.
Oh, no.
And see what else.
And Zorn, thank you for the 1000 bits.
Take these big.
Skipping, amazing shot, bull.
Thank you so much, man.
I hope you enjoyed the songs
in the karaoke, Wolf.
Sure.
Right.
Oh, boy.
I'm just drinking casually at the moment,
so that's not so much.
Reverend, thank you for the honour, Sean.
Thank you for it. That's all now.
Yeah, I was really nervous.
They'll be so nervous.
You say you actually live.
I said you're very careful.
Your mom said I was cute.
Your mom approves of me. Wow.
Ha, ha. Wow.
Do your guys's moms approve of me?
Do your parents approve of me?
I don't know.
Maybe I'm not.
So I'm not like a doctor.
I'm lawyer enough for some people.
I know.
My my my parents are like that. I'm
pretty sure my parents are like, that.
So it's called. It's called. Asian.
Asian life breath.
OK. It's always.
It's always like oh, like what?
How how much money does he have?
How how is he handsome?
Is he tall?
How can he support this family?
Right.
It's always
I feel like it's always that kind of.
Like mentality
when it comes to appearance. It's like.
Oh, what can he give you?
Or like, what can he give us, too?
Right.
It's so.
Dumb.
I'll miss the thank.
That's for that.
Ali, thank you for the talent, though.
And Kyra,
and thank you for the gifts, jobs.
And I am thank you for the 50 50.
It's your one gifts, jobs.
I think you give like a hundred
yum or I am.
Thank you so much for the 100 gifts
I was Rowan's I really hope
that the karaoke you know was
that's your it's your pleasure and taste.
And another I'm sorry I.
Got seriously
but thank you so much for the raid Yana.
Well, if you're still here
and if you are, then the
operation was good.
And I hope you're having a great night
so far.
Pinky, thank you for the doll.
No, starting each with its own now
and something for that's all.
Know a star like that guy from Black
Clover, a star or ask the he stuff.
It's like it's all a so it's like,
you know how.
Aaron has a double A and you say like
Aaron or some people say Aaron, I guess.
It's I call you. A star or.
You're a star.
A star. I don't know
any. Thank you for the attendance
you're on yourselves.
And Hepner is.
Good morning. Well,
thank you for that solitaire on gift subs.
And Cindy thank you for that's on the on
thank you for the.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God. My thing refreshed.
I lost track of where it was
a cat. Thank you for.
That's Elmo and Lauren.
Thank you for the tickets.
You're on guest subs.
Just thank you for the throwing
gifts of still why are you so cute?
This explain explain.
What do you mean?
Why am I so cute? What? How, huh?
What am I doing right now?
That is so cute, huh?
I'm just reading
just thank you for the 30.
01 I. Subs. By the way, I saw ads.
On a message that says like,
sorry I can't donate much as of lately.
Don't ever never.
Apologise for that.
OK, that's the last thing I want
you guys to do.
You guys watching.
And just being here.
Is doing so much more than than
like you can imagine.
Donating is just is.
Always an option. OK.
Please, like, don't give me.
Anything if you're having a hard time
or don't like feel like you.
Have to
please just think about yourselves.
Treat yourself so like some ice cream,
you know I'm gonna do tomorrow
I'm going to go give myself
some strawberry and cheesecake ice cream.
I think you guys should do. The same,
all right?
Instead of, like,
you know, given something to me,
you know, make me happier if you just.
Think about.
Yourselves once in a while as well.
All right, thank you.
Like, of course, I'm.
Not going to say don't do it,
but just like.
You know.
Always consider yourselves
and always prioritise yourselves.
That will make me
the I'll make me very happy
to know, like, you're you're OK.
Deli, thank you for the sensor
on our subs as well.
I pinch. Thank you for. That's all no NCR.
Thank you for that's on now are thank you
for being so much warm and fun for us.
I hope everybody.
Enjoyed the karaoke whether it was just
by listening or the small little advancers
or whatever
or I just hang out and chat it's
it was a very fun session like.
This was probably one of the most funds
I've had.
For a karaoke session in a long time.
You know, like,
I fumbled a few lyrics here and there.
I still enjoyed myself despite that
ringer.
And thank
you for an another for another Johnno
and so we thank you for that's on
law and Moomaw.
Thank you for the honour and the link.
Thank you for that download.
Congrats on 300 k.
Thank you so much. Link apply.
Thank you for the big deal.
Now if you're so thankful and lucky
that I can be you want to kill this,
we will always stay with you
and see the world together.
No matter what happens.
You're worth all the love and support
and you're the best guild leader.
I try to.
Be a good leader for you guys
any time I can.
And I mean
it's just the beginning, right?
There is. This is just like.
What the first chapter
or the first few chapters.
We have so much more to do.
We have so many quests.
The gone.
It's like an endless journey, right?
You're going to have that endless journey
together and we'll see where it takes us.
And I'm excited to see what comes down the
line where it's take it on
you. Watch Hal's moving castle.
Two days ago, and it's such a blessing
to hear you sing this.
Thank you so much, Rubble.
And I love
and hope that you have a nice life.
You're amazing.
OK, the promise of the world was, oh.
I don't know when I why I thought
about singing it, but I was thinking about
you know, talking about my promise
to my, my, my best friend.
My he's no longer with us,
like I said, but I really do
want to sing something
that captured that feeling I wanted.
So, you know, I give to you guys.
And I think that was like
the perfect song.
It really was.
To get the message through.
So I'm glad you guys enjoyed Joy that are
part of the karaoke
are amazing that God, thank you for the.
All the bits. That's a lot of bits, bro.
He's so much a six.
Thank you for the multiple donors.
Oh, my goodness.
That's that's a lot of donors are.
Ron, thank you for this honour
you undertake.
Congratulations. That is also.
The 30th. Day since you watch your show
and you are my treasure til baby.
Well, I mean,
well, I mean
ends are for other was your oine right.
Getting better and better at.
Saying that one that's it's difficult
I stutter you know
puff thank you for the AIDS. Oh, no.
Congratulations.
You're glad to be part of the guild.
Every day of your life is full of joy
and hope and you really hope
to enjoy the time with me
and learning English from my stream.
I don't think.
Learning English
or my friend is the best idea,
but if it helps, then, hey, I'm glad it.
It's been helping
I do want to
say, like, if you do want to learn more,
you know, English,
I hope all your schools are teaching.
You are like you take classes.
Have like the best.
Ways to take classes and like,
you hit the textbook still.
That's why I want to. Try and learn.
I try and learn Japanese very soon.
I got to get.
Go get those textbooks. Man.
That's the first language I'm tackling.
And then now I know I want to try Mandarin
as well.
Mandarin Chinese and so
and so what else I think
brush up on Spanish again.
I really do want to do more Spanish.
Spanish is a fucking awesome
language, man.
It makes sense.
English doesn't make sense.
The Spanish when I learnt it in
high school or like part of it, I forgot.
It just makes. Sense, man. Like it was
God bless
Moyer.
Vonnie, thank you for the big deal.
No cuts.
Thank you for the honour of Mommy.
Mommy.
Thank you for the ads on his wall. Sissy.
Thank you for the five.
Oh, it's your own give subs
ends. Are zero.
Thank you for the $50.
Congrats on 300 k.
Thank you to all the thank you so much.
I hope you're still around.
And if you are I hope you're
having the awesome fucking night bro.
Thank you for another.
Hope and everybody thank you so much
lady Jemmy. Trask. Now.
Oh yeah. That reminds me.
I don't know if to.
Shit, we got to finish that, Tony.
Maybe I'll put that on schedule
for next week
if I remember
but she's. She's dead now.
We killed her, right?
Yes. See ya.
See, congratulations on the day
I'll always be there with you.
Your songs are beautiful.
Yes, you are wealth. They are treasure.
Treasure.
That is what you are. Her.
Honey, you're my golden star.
Yeah.
I know.
It's a great song, man. Our Bruno Mars.
I feel like I should sing more
Bruno Mars song.
Still all. Right.
I'm all right.
Yeah. Yeah, I like you.
Guys idea of, like, dedicating a stream
to, like, a specific genre
of songs and music,
so I might try and do that.
For future karaoke, like,
you know, like rap,
rap, rap, karaoke. Or.
Or K-pop karaoke or, you know, um,
just sad love songs or something
like that.
Stick to a theme or something.
Right?
Oh, girl.
Thank you for another two and give subs
tight end.
Thank you for the 300 bits.
I am. Thank you for that, Donald.
So sorry. Sorry I stay here,
but you have to go to work.
I'll be over.
Great. Simon, I really enjoyed
seeing listening to you sing.
You're great.
You know more.
You thank you for listening and zahava.
Wow. Have a good day at work.
I can't talk.
Wow. I'm like, my work
also.
Yeah, I think a lot of people didn't know,
but I do like rapping.
I do like rap music a lot.
I listen to it a lot
when I. Go to the gym.
It's like my motivation, music it's like,
get shit done.
Rap music is awesome, and I don't.
I'm just. I suck at it.
There's like one rap from a native, sir,
that I wanted to learn.
Those are from like a collaboration
or something like that.
You're more Sagar Kimmy.
Only you're more Su Sakura.
Keep me on my feet.
Yeah, and he did it often.
That's, you know, and
it sounds like all on life.
Find it
just stay the same.
It sounds really good.
I wish I had seen it in the past.
You know I hate you.
Yeah, it's,
ah, it's a really intense rap, but.
I feel like that is my goal, bro.
That's like the top of.
My list
priority of trying to cover this song
with a friend in the future.
If I once I learn, like, you know,
get more comfortable with, like, actually
doing rap in both, like,
English and Japanese,
not suit darker.
I thank you for this honour to educate.
Congrats all day.
We love you and thank you for bringing.
Out a good. Song
bringing so much,
because I hope I read that right.
No problem.
I, I think it was right
talking about treasure.
I'm glad you guys love treasure, man.
That's
that's really good to know. Like this.
That was kind of like a.
You know, a curveball in the karaoke
along with Fall on my limo.
But, yeah, i, i really.
I'm really glad that treasure
was a favourite of many people.
You guys are my treasure.
You, Michael.
Hui, thank you for the big tell.
No. Oh, my God.
Thank you for the karaoke stream.
Not today. Only I mean every stream.
I'm very.
You're you love listening to me sing.
And your voice makes me relax and heal.
Don't be shy.
Your voice is very nice.
You can't even, like,
I will always. Like, be shy.
You know. It's hard sor
it's hard to get over those nerves,
I guess.
Like,
I to I don't think I'll.
I'll ever get over those nerves.
Like it's a good thing.
Like people have that,
you know, positive stress
before they go into like, something big.
It's normal.
But yeah, I was just really shy
because I was worried I would
the songs went, like, fuck up real
hard on a song or something like that.
But I'm glad to know, like.
You know, I didn't, I didn't blunder
anything and it went really well.
Fiona Hannah see.
I did it all. A couple of karaoke ago.
Oh, nurse, thank you for the $300.
Ah, congratulations on 300 k.
I promise I will stay here
as long as I can.
And you shine so bright today.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh.
Well, that's a sweet message.
Well, it's
a shine bright that I really
shine bright
I'm glad you're here.
Thank you so much for the know, and
I appreciate you listening to my songs.
I had fun with fire.
I think the one that I enjoyed
the most was probably dry flower.
Like I said,
I got to go do more dry flower.
Enzo, thank you for putting the stream
in the community.
Hypnosis like it means a lot easier.
Thank you so much.
Bunny.
Thank you for another day now. Love you.
Love you, too.
Noona.
Thank you for the doll.
No, Ahmad.
Thank you for the doll. No.
And, Mira,
thank you for that song, though.
And the fat. Fox.
Thank you. For the doll.
Now, Rich, thank you for the 15 months.
Welcome back, Rich.
Hey, I got how to do on how to do.
And how's it going?
I wanted to. I don't know how it's ok.
With the bubble,
but do but do. You'll be do be
gonna thank you for that.
Oh, no and make a
thank you for the it's on though
as well
Chyna thank you for the doll now
and keeping faith
it's on our thanks for the karaoke baby
that's all we all love you.
Well I need I'll be.
Cute call me that and.
So I'm going to
grab your face and
only thank you for the song as well.
Hey, on the album,
congrats on hitting so many milestones.
You're doing so great.
And I was a love to listen to you sing it.
Is there of all the love.
Oh, right. I forgot.
I will make I will publish the vide.
I should publish the bottle right now.
But for. Some reason, switch.
Doesn't want me like,
you know, publish the VOD
until after the stream is over
for some odd reason.
So I'm going to
I think that's just how it's set up now.
So ill girl.
So you guys can listen to the
to the songs again
once I end stream later
a lot of people do I have to head out?
Yeah. You guys are busy days today.
It is the morning for some of you. Right.
So have a good day.
Don't don't feel pressure to stay.
All right.
Be sure to us your responsibilities
and there will always be the bad.
Take care.
All right,
Amber, thank you for that sonar and saw
it's in the air.
Think of it. It's online.
Vampire Popper, the funny name
oh, see?
That's it, shopper.
You've killed me.
I'm on the way to the grave now.
What did I do?
What did I do? What I do?
Something bad.
It was it. The songs? I don't know.
Don't die.
Please don't die. I'll be sad if you die.
No, no dying.
OK, I'll fucking kill.
You if you die.
Amamou Thank you for the I'll again. Ah,
I see he Tommy.
Thank you for the baked on.
No, congratulations on the 300
can switch and £400 order.
Thank you for appearing in my life
and thank you for the karaoke scream.
There's something that.
Just hit me in the heart.
And. On you when people type to thank you
for appearing in my life.
That's a very sweet line. I don't know.
It's like the equivalent of saying
thank you for existing,
I guess, and analogies
means a lot to be appreciated that way.
Thank you.
My stomach just rumbled.
I got to get food after the stream.
There's a there's some food.
Downstairs, so I got to eat that.
I did not.
Eat before the stream like a dummy
because I wanted to
just have a short one today.
So I will eat afterwards.
No worries.
My mom has food downstairs.
Mama, thank you for this. I know, pumpkin.
I love you.
Maybe you can hear some Chinese songs
in the future.
I was considering doing some, but it's
just like I don't know which ones to do.
I remember my friends did one.
I was called, like, warrior or.
Something like that and saw
I might give that a try,
so I forgot to turn.
Alert Box is back on. Sorry about that.
I don't know what it was, but I.
I want to try and,
you know, expand the different languages
as well.
Like other different languages
besides our Japanese and Tsar
and Korean, which are my comforts
job. I sing a black pink song.
I love black pink, bro. My God,
watching cookies.
K-pop inspired me to,
like, wanted to do more K-pop song style,
acoustic style.
Most likely.
Then. Thank you for that's on our show.
He's amazing tonight. We love you a lot.
And your son scenes also come in
so you have a good night.
You have a good night.
The odds you would hope
it's not too late for you Guru.
Thank you for the deal. No,
and I thank you for this. I know.
I sure thought thank you for being a huge.
Inspiration to me and becoming a YouTuber.
Because of you. I'm honestly.
Trying to do the best in everything all.
You dude I it's
i, i really I'm really glad you.
Brought that up because like
you all say, like, self
helping YouTubers or not viewers
or whatever, but really, I believe in you.
You got this.
I Twitter on 400 k oh it's an amazing
you I'll always be there for you and big
who you love our leader.
Oh cut off what I weird.
Right back to my other.
Point though I was saying.
I started off.
As a P&G I never had you know this
I was just you know a pick
just a picture on the screen and
going from that to
this has been quite the journey so
if it means anything, hey
I know exactly where you're coming from.
I used to be,
you know, really, really small and
now I have so many wonderful
friends and guild members with me
to join me on this wonderful journey.
So I hope that.
You can reach
reach that same happiness that I have.
OK, you got this. Don't don't stop.
Don't give up.
Trust me, it gets better.
It will get better.
I was in.
Your shoes like a year ago, a couple of
years ago, and I know what it's like, bro.
So just keep it to keep at it.
All right?
Are on.
You sing very well,
and I can feel the emotions in your song.
Ah, I listen to your songs to sleep
every day and I have more songs.
All you guys listen to me sings.
I got a better lot
of what you guys listen to me
when you get to bed.
Oh, my. God. That's sweet.
I might post.
A couple of the songs
that we did tonight on my channel.
Maybe we'll see, because I was a
I was proud of them.
Wasn't one of them.
I will see y'all.
I'll see
Keith Staples.
Hasn't been long.
By really love coming to your streams.
Your voice is always so comforting. Oh.
My stomach is rumbling a lot.
Sorry, and always brings
a smile to my face.
Congrats on 300 K and thank you
for letting us hear you sing.
I'm glad that you were around to hear me
sing.
Dude, your company here, it's
listened to my songs into
my voice is very
it's very sweet and
I hope to be able to continue
to, you know.
Have more. People
come by
and enjoy themselves as much as you do.
Every day.
There's like always new guilties.
I see new guilties in the all the time
the new people are coming into this court.
So I really hope you enjoy your time here.
And I'm glad to know that saw you have
been having fun for as long as you have.
And it's been fun, right?
Because I've been having fun still.
And so it's nice to know
that you're also having fun, bro.
Key. Thank you for that honour.
Thank you so much, guy.
Ah, thank you for this karaoke show
and super congrats on hitting 300 k.
It makes me happy to see you grow so much
and wish you the best for the future. So
thank you for agreeing to be part
of the mod scene and for being such,
you know, a supportive member
while still doing an amazing job bro.
I don't know what to say. Thank you
Azita.
Thank you for the words.
Oh no, I can't expect that
I cried a lot today.
Oh no. Please don't cry.
Please don't cry.
Don't cry. Ah,
no, no crying.
You want.
You want to wipe your series on my jacket.
I got you on my sleeve.
I don't know why I use my sleeve, bro.
You can feel my sweet just don't cry
of raqqa.
Thank you for the hotel now as well.
He got here. Thank you for that.
I know
and so goal shock.
OK, Sagar,
I love you so much.
Lucky that you're my first voice.
You were your first voice.
You were, bruh.
Your that's that's fucking sweet.
Knowing like you're somebody for something
is always always means the world's
a person. So don't take that lightly.
I never take that lightly.
Nino Mia, thank you for the.
5000 bets on, you know. Mia,
thank you so much.
Dude, have you been enjoying yourself
and had a great time in the stream
I'll do thank you for that's all.
No ends are a come to think of it.
It's not Andre. Mikey, think of it
that's on the agenda for this.
I know you love.
Promise of the world
the most. And yes, that you're wonderful.
You know, because of that, I will try to.
Do promise of the world again
next time, ok?
I promise.
I will do promise of the world's
yeah. It's a promise, guys.
All right.
Thank you.
Promise you can't break a pinky promise.
So expect that in the next karaoke stream.
Kate Couscous.
Thank you for the doll.
No, my bird kitty
cuddled up and fell asleep
as we listen to her beautiful singing all.
Are you giving kitty enough seeds?
Are you feeding him well or her well?
He's also a big fan.
Of you. I'm glad.
I really like it.
One of those birds,
like cockatoos, cockatiels or on parrots.
Like, I like it when they sing.
Like, with you or like you know, mimic
your mimic your sounds.
I love birds. That's you.
That's just super cute.
I don't know if he's one of those,
but they're really adorable.
I hope he's he's well fed and happy.
Karen, thank you for the ads. Oh, no.
You have a friend
who can't watch this stream in class,
but she also said congratulations.
Thank you.
How was your friend?
A great day.
Did and focus on class?
I think they've with it's on now and yeah.
Thank you for this honour.
Congrats on three K.
It's your first ever.
Donation and it was a very big one.
I love you so much.
You really had a bad day,
but your voice cured my day.
Thank you for the positivity.
You can call me. Yeah.
Of course I can judge you.
Up less than.
Three, Lucia.
I think for. That's all.
No, Enzo, Lexie.
Thank you for the bits. And you.
Thank you for the words.
I know it was something Kate.
Love you all.
Thank you so much.
You do for a
thank you for this honour and support.
Thank you for that.
So now a puppy.
Thank you for. That's all. No,
he got any thank you for that's on are.
You always be. Yourself.
You should be proud of yourself.
You will pinch your cheeks
you won't pinch my cheeks OK.
Come here. Do it there. Right now.
There are now
going to do it.
Are going to do it or what?
Fine.
Serenity. Thank you for the oh, no.
And our puppy. Thank you for this.
I know.
You're a badminton.
Player, so you're going to be parts
this being your first national.
Tournaments.
Whoa, that's big, dude. Congrats.
And I hope you succeed in the tournament.
Get first or if you don't, then that's ok.
That's ok to just have fun
and do your best.
We're all cheering you on, bro.
All the other guilty still vivi
thank you for
these are no ends all star
thank you for the doll no
thank you for healing my whole morning.
We also appreciate you
and thank you for existing in this world.
I love you all. Amy. Are
a sea.
I love watching your streams.
They're always so fun and comforting.
My life has definitely brightened
since I discovered you.
That's all I do.
That's like you guys saying this.
Thing is is like the equivalent
of a marriage proposal.
That's all I'm. Feeling on you.
See this? Oh, my. God.
It's really. Sweet.
Well, thank you for for the kind message,
and I really do appreciate
it, man.
I get me all soft already.
Or maybe that's the alcohol. I don't know.
Is it the alcohol or is it you guys?
Maybe it's both.
Just switch my music real quick.
Something a little bit more chill.
Awesome.
Thank you for the online show.
And thank you for that's.
I know my mother likes you very much.
She said she would
love to have a son like you.
She would love to have a son like me all.
Is that is that bad?
I what does that mean, Ellie?
Is she trying to say like like,
you know, those moms are like.
Oh, you should be like him or like, huh?
I wish I had a son like him,
and then they give you a side eye, right?
I don't know. I don't know.
I hope she. Doesn't do that.
I hope that's not
what she's implying, bro.
But yeah.
Like me.
Some. Thank you for the honour and Zulu.
Thank you for.
That's all. Now you're seeing as amazing.
It's been a wonderful, wonderful
time. Keep on partying.
I will
I will continue to blog as I see you guys.
Continue to blog. Jill, Vanessa,
I thank you for the talent.
All of you know how happy you make us
feel.
It's such a blessing.
And I hope you guys know
how happy you make me fuckers.
Zelda
Thank you for the big donor, but $200.
Thank you for being in my life.
I really love your voice,
your scream and your smile.
The screams.
Thank you for liking the screams.
That's part of the package.
I mean, you can't.
You can't sort of
have me without the scream.
Still, you know,
don't know how long your love will last.
Bye for now.
I really, really love you
more than anything else in the world of
Zelda.
Princess Zelda them is all that.
Thank you.
Thank you for the donation and I again. I
it means a lot.
Like the not like
the screams are endearing.
I always look at it as, like,
just something that's just.
Ha ha ha.
You know, or like, oh, my God,
why do I sound like that?
But the fact that you said, like,
you love it, it's just really. Huh?
It sounds like it sounds like a screeching
tire or a seagull sometimes, but, hey.
If you like that. Then I'm glad. I'm glad
recrimination.
Thank you for that, Donna.
I'll love you, honey.
I love you, too, bro.
Gnocchi.
Thank you for the donor.
And, Kenny, thank you for the. All
I realised your donor.
Was missing an extra zero. Here you go.
I think you added an extra zero
by accident.
Thank you for the big donation.
And Kenny, really
well, my God, guys,
a lot of there's a lot of donors tonight.
God is OK
to put on the mind brake tag already.
I think it's I think it's like Warren
said, right Allin.
Thank you for this.
Oh, no. And I do for you.
Thank you for this honour.
And you thank you for the honour as well.
And so thank you for this honour.
Karmically that you've ever done.
All five to our softball.
Congrats on 400 k.
What was the number?
I remember it was like 520.
1314. Right.
I get it right. I hope I did
kiss.
Thank you for the honour and sons and
thank you for the honour and the paper.
Thank you for another honour and Sally
thank you for the honour.
Your personal favourite was Villain
Your singing voice is just the medication
you secure your frustration and congrats
on all the milestones you'll hit more.
Celine, thank you so
glad you guys like the villain and.
I try to do like the whole.
What's it?
I remembered trying to do the laugh
in the middle and not being sure.
Like if that was a good idea, like be
as like a little adlib.
I'll pick him off.
OK, it's
so I thank you for another example and
just thank you for the big honour as well.
Congrats again.
Our Guild leader ends us so proud of you.
Always be by your side
I'm glad to have you guys by my side, man.
Thank you,
Roth. Thank you for this honour.
Time spent with
you has not only been a blessing to me,
but also to many girls out there.
You're able to find what you're seeking
deep within your hearts
and have fun on my journey.
I hope you guys will.
Also be able to find
what you wants on this journey because,
hey, we're all going on this together,
all right?
So, hey,
this is not just about me,
but it's about you guys still in the game.
It's not just sore.
It's not just mine, OK?
We're all in this together.
It's not a, quote,
high school musical or anything.
Mystery. Thank you for the opportunity.
Oh, thank you for the five
arts, your ones.
And Mimi, thank you for the big deal.
No. And
don't forget, Mama.
Thank you for this.
I know
you have a Chinese nickname,
which is Soul Bao.
So thou shall go cheval.
I heard two.
There's like, different ones.
She'll go on Soul Vow.
I shall Gonzales Puppy
you call me baby.
All right. I see.
Uh huh.
Oh, it's in me.
Yeah, I did see little intentions.
I read it earlier.
ARU, thank you for the elmo.
And it seems
thank you for the till now as well.
And I guess I'll thank you
for the five liberties
and Zerkalo.
Thank you for the XL.
No, we love you so much.
Your existence means only. There and.
Means so much to us.
Thank you so much for everything
and take good care of yourself.
By the way, you can.
Can you please say.
Mahalo. The cocktail hour.
I'm mobu oh, hey.
What is this?
Mahalo.
Cocktail mother.
Hey, swag. A peanut.
Ma. Ma, Marvel.
Has swag of.
You know what.
All right, pugi
the leave. What?
Thank you for.
The Are you ever the 100 cities?
Well, thank you so much for the bits
I really you guys.
Got me say something really
embarrassing ends up and in Pigalle.
Yeah a little diva that's on our end Zarco
Thank you for the zone,
though, as well. OK,
thank you for being here.
I heard you were nervous
about today's karaoke stream.
I'm also nervous.
Excited and it's on a perfectly.
It's amazing.
Everything you said touched me.
I love you, Bilbao.
Oh, call me baby.
I'm not a baby.
What's not a baby?
Unless you mean a like.
Oh, babe, it's a baby then. Yeah, OK.
That's that's cool, too.
All right.
I think that is
it because my stomach is telling me shop.
I'll go eat food right.
Now, or I'll sa I am going to die.
I got some food in my tummy
I have a pacifier asset.
Yeah, I do.
I don't use it though.
Now we should end it now because yeah.
I want to get some food in my belly
before I go to bed tonight.
We have another stream in the morning.
I don't know. Shit. Cancel it.
Oh I think we should be.
Able to play still. Yeah.
I don't think it's going to be a problem.
We'll be able to continue.
So in the morning we're going to play.
Alien isolation at
9 a.m.
EDT or it's 1 p.m.
GSD, so I'll be sure to come by for that.
All right.
Also off here, join the discord.
If you haven't joined the discord already.
It's discord at the bar.
Dogs.
I shop all. Right.
Up in there. And the eight of us
I post on when we go live and then other
announcements for upcoming streams.
So be sure. To check it out
also be sure.
To subscribe on YouTube
if you haven't already.
Since I do have a YouTube account,
I might.
I think I'll.
Plan the YouTube stream
for this coming week.
Yeah, and I.
Don't know what we'll do.
On YouTube though. Yeah,
and what else?
Papa. Papa.
Oh, yeah.
Follow me on Twitter
if you haven't already.
OK, thank you.
I'm going to go
and look for somebody to rate tonight,
but I'm to leave off
with one final message.
I hope everyone here has a good night
and I hope that everyone enjoyed my songs
and what I was able to do
with all of you tonight.
I mean, I see
that this has been an amazing experience
and I hope to continue having this feeling
I have.
It never ends and grasp
it firmly until the ends of the earth
because I wants to keep this journey
going and
hope that all of you will continue
to be by my side
for as long as you can on this journey.
All right.
Thank you for everything God is.
And I'll see you at
405 hundred K
and much more in the future.
OK, I'm going to play a quick outbreak
while we look for someone straight.
So give me a seconds, Barbie.
Who is live?
Yeah, Barbie, hold on.
Oh, yeah.
Overwatch two came out with Overwatch two.
I know some people are playing that show.
I try out Overwatch two.
I don't know.
I don't care.
Who is live, who's around. It's
not a gun
so. We can go and
read the data.
Oh. Oh.
Lend us.
Live witness, live our scars, live.
Scars playing.
All of this is the savage.
Raid that they do in the south, huh?
OK, fox boxes us alive.
You know, I haven't I've never gone
to opportunity to.
Read case on and.
She is an.
Inspiration to me and a lot of other vets
is I want to go and saw your farm.
You know,
you're my health Corey case on let's see
them so like oh my gosh.
So OK hope you guys have a good night.
All right.
Take care. And I'll see you next time.
You are you are.
Bye bye.
I hope the right one through
I hope it did.
Did it go through
the fuck?
Oh, yeah, I did.
Cool.
Oh, I got it.
My my back is so stiff from today.
I really think I like overly.
Tense my, my, like,
shoulders and neck and, like, everything,
it just feels all like.
Ooh, la la la la la la la.
You know, because of what's it
from all the singing
I love you guys.
Have a good night. OK, take care.
And I'll see you tomorrow for our alien
isolation.
Yeah.
Mama, mama.
Molly guitar a little bit about that.
You are a good, simple camera on
my equally ready zip down.
Well, I know I stole.
The Elmo bye.
Bye bye.
Now. Good night.
Oh, my God.
I need some more tea.
No, my tea.
It's. He's called.
Him. My fucking tea.
Cold tea is always a sad day.
All right. Bye bye, guys.
Take care.