But, um.
Hello. Hello.
Wait. Why am I here?
Hold on.
Give me a second.
What the heck?
Oh. Oops.
OK. Ah.
Hello.
Hi, guys.
Good morning.
Good evening, everybody.
They're waiting for me.
Let's get right into the game.
I think I just want to say hi there.
I love you guys a lot.
Mm hmm.
Some of the notifications will be off
for the stream,
so we can just focus on the collab with Vox.
Ike and Reimu.
So I just want to say, like,
those will be off, but
I'll be reading through the donations,
and all the subs
are after the mushrooms over
or after the collab's over.
Okay. Yeah, I'll be there.
I will be there.
All right.
I think they're waiting for me, though.
I don't wanna keep them waiting
any longer, ok?
Reimu just called me a bitch, so hold on
OK, let me see.
Where is he now? That's a reality?
No. Mm hmm.
Yeah.
Oh, Hello.
Here you go.
Hello. Here you go now.
Welcome back.
Hello. Hello. Hi.
Hello. Are you guys live too?
Yeah. OK, punk.
Nice. Hi.
I mean, a bitch.
We're, um. Yeah.
Well.
Well, sorry.
That was rude of me.
Bish Bish. There you go. Thanks lot.
That's the one I know.
Yeah. There.
Yeah, there's. A big difference.
She's you
know.
It's a lot more.
It's like,
how do I put it?
One, one?
You got to know if you know, you know.
I think. If you know, You know.
You know.
You know, you know.
But I don't. Really friends.
Hold on.
Is everyone ready.
I don't know how to like when
we see I have to start right?
Well, I, I yeah there is a big button that
starts the game.
Is big button that's a start game. Really.
Oh, there is a big one.
That's a start game. Yeah.
You fucking.
Hold on. I says I collect. I can.
Hold on, I can select the map
size, the difficulty and the lives.
If you go to the photos. Yeah.
So all there's only
one story and different cases.
What does that mean? Yeah.
Yeah, that this story, it's not just,
like, farcical, like just random pieces.
I mean, you can do both
Oh. I'm not doing.
Do what do we do?
Want to seen some stuff? Story? cases?
Which one? Let's just do a story.
I'll see the story.
Configuring your own character.
Wait.How do you do that?
You go to the tent.
Yeah,
but how do you change your character?
Like, completely? Boxes like. This.
No options for me.
Yeah. Like you go to the tent.
That's different.
I'm in the. Tents.
Go to the tent.
You can. Oh, I'm in the all.
Oh, wait. I'm in. The tent.
But I don't have any o.
Press the arrows.
There's only, like, three character.
Pieces I'll be this baby girl.
I think I'm just a bearded man.
I'm just going to be the stoner.
That's.
Yeah.
OK. Do not make fun of this guy.
He's pecing. Done in the.
All right.
Reimu, you and vox are matching shirts.
Aoh, adorable. I said, so we get to go
let go of this stoner guy.
You know, we can all be stoner together.
All right,
you guys ready? We get into the game.
Yeah. Let's go. Oh, I'll just disappear.
I got cut off.
Hello? Open the door.
You don't even want to play.
All right, here we are.
Oh, my God.
I think I can barely hear you,
so I think I'm everything is.
Yeah, the game is very loud.
Oh, my goodness.
Yeah. Music.
I can barely even hear myself.
Yeah, me too.
I'm know everything except for the voice.
The sound is.
so loud. It's fucking hilarious.
Kind of sounds scuffs. Yeah.
Hello, gamers.
Hello. Hello. Hello.
Guys.
How's the sound?
How's the sound? Nice. Yeah.
How does that sound? Do they sound better?
I increase the volumes.
Oh, my. God. It's still so loud.
So sorry.
I I'll try not to be loud.
I'd be happy to face my melody.
Yeah.
You're like whispering in my ear
well, I do the same to you.
I do the same to you,yeah yeah yeah.Do you like that?
I should be able to hear
you guys better now.
I'll go ask you your favourite sandwich, you bitch.
My favourite sandwich?
What is my favourite sandwich?
You like cheese?
Oh, there's more there's lower.
There's more? Yeah,
I found some more, too.
All right. So what do we got?
Our captain's warning. Here you are.
Have read out loud.
Hey, Jason.
I'm looking for that box of tape recorders
while you're setting
those stupid ghosts up.
What? What?
You'll find them in and lineal
oh, you owe you big time shooting range.
can't afford to lose many prises. Johnny.
Johnny. I‘m John Jones. Yeah.
I thought it said Johnny.
I like Jenny.
Jenny, Jenny.
You got the legs, right? That's right.
Survival says lt's in.
I wish this doctor would be quiet.
And you got new legs.
You said you want the dog to be quiet.
There's a dog got the duck. It's another.
This is nothing.
Nothing, nothing.
What?
Yeah, it keeps talking.
Make it stop.
Okay, OK, let me just.
I'm going in. There's another.
Oh, there's another note.
It says narrator shouldn't
be running this hard either.
Johnny's got something more hard in this
or the wiring's worse
than the damn hedge par
for the course with Johnny Bills.
Just charge him an arm and leg and look.
What the. Fuck?
Who the fuck is Johnny? OK, whatever.
I have no idea. OK, why are you so ugly,Vox?
You don't need to.
Complain about the bell.
I'm going inside
oh, once it's my throat, there
for staff to hear my current objective.
Wait. How do you run?
You hold. Hold. Don't shoot.
I'm going to throw rocks
through your window, you bitch.
It's time to see your current
available money.
Wait.
You can. Go into the. Trees. Oh, my God.
Look, I'm a tree.
Oh, wait. No, I'm not.
I got. You.
That's so creepy.
I'm a bush.
If I'm not a bush, I'm no one.
No one in the works. I'm a bush.
I'm a bush.
I'm a bush. If I'm not a bush, I'm no one.
How do you
how do you know every reference I made?
OK, that's  so culture
that one is exceptionally British.
That's a very British video.
Have you seen the one
where the guy is just like,
how many cigarettes have you got?
Yeah.
So many cigarettes.
Yeah. Mom.
And he just smashes his head into another.
So is so.
Your. Opinion it's OK. I already kind of.
Have you seen the one that works?
Like where it's like.
Can't believe I drunk you all.
I thought you're going to say,
I can't believe he's on this.
Yes, you all.
Can you tell the time? Yes.
He turns toward the clock and he tells it,
I am not fucking drunk.
I'm going to slap you
with my flashlight and keep this up.
I'll try it.
You're going to you're going to
you're going to smack your flashlight on
my tongue.
On your tongue.
I'm gonna suck your beard
and suck your silly little beard.
Oh, my boy is waiting for my beer
to be passed down.
notice.
Oh, hey. Look, it's not for generations,
this beard.
It's nice delivery, OK?
The the Joe, pick up the the flashlight.
I picked up a flashlight.
I have a flashlight.
How do I. How do I look?
Laura? Laura, Laura? Laura.
Laura? Yeah, or not? Not really. Laura.
But it's a collectable.
It's like. Hello, internet.
Welcome to Game. Theory.
Oh, this is like the third one.
I saw this.
I can see my legs.
Welcome to the maze survival guide.
A complete guide of getting out of a maze
and survival tips of surviving enemies.
I met my by Matthew Patrick.
You ever watch where you're lost
in a maze?
You're watching this classified
don't panic.
Have you guys ever seen Hitchhiker's
Guide on the front?
Don't panic. Number two,
I'm. Just a runaway.
Number three, I don't want to.
Oh, my God. This is
this is fucking amazing.
That number. Three,
we just left vox.
We just locked it.
Well, it's a flashlight out.
Something funny
I was reading something funny.
Press one
where you can cycle stuff.
Press one to. One.
Wait, hold on. I don't know.
What's the flashlight button.
On the back of the book?
The English is a little broken.
It said that there are no number three.
You arescrewed.
I Yeah.
So I hear they scream already.
Yes. It's my.
One. Now.
I don't know.
I mean, this is, like
spooky house of jump scares.
I love that game.
I have.
I cleared it, by the way.
You did good for.
This is a small beat.
How do you like how do I.
Pull out my flashlight
and tell me I to pull out the. Flashlight?
Whine why?
Nobody read.
It. Is a dead
end. Reading's annoying. Yeah.
Pick it up.
Pick what up?
you. Bitch you get.
No, I didn't. That was no, I didn't.
You don't knowshit. You didn't heer that.
You did't hear anything.
I guess I'm going down this way.
Oh, we should stick together, guys?
I guess I was that way. Guys.
I saw that too.
Yo, I stop. I can stop going.
Guys, guys, guys.
We got to stick together, otherwise.
Ike can you hear me? Stop running.
ike vox， get back here.
What do you mean, go?
Yeah, we saw it.
We saw, like, a demon or something
running through the maze.
The juice about that by the saw.
Just. Oh, like. No, no, no, no, no.
You were behind me when it happened.
Yeah,
I like how you're. I like how your butt.
Wiggles now I feel emasculated.
Ooh, yellow.
Like you see it.
Do you see a bite
wiggles? Collectable？
Look back.
You go the wrong way.
I'm I'm. I'm looking at how.
I. Shot the lesson.
I put out a reference sheet like the.
Oh, yeah, your flat is five and.
Zero k motherfuckers.
Zero K when you have no no was like
I do not appreciate everybody
like just staring.
It was just like last longer.
This. Way.
I made it look, dude, if I put a
if I put a balance on the.
It would be like a whole 180 degrees.
Oh, did you guys see that?
Yeah, I sold out.
Oh, yeah.
Shut the fuck up.
Take a break.
Whoever is running around with.
Everybody going.
Creepy, you how about we don't do that?
Thanks. Who wrote. That?
You should take a break. Let's squat.
Oh, you want a squat.
To whoever is running around in the dark?
It's creepy. How about we just don't?
I just don't.
Yeah, it is kind of weird.
You're so it's a mushroom.
So the demon thing,
that's the shade of a shadow
or whatever it is that's running around.
It's not a clue because I saw it
just run straight into a deep end
and straight to a dead
end. And then it disappeared.
He likes you bagging the mushroom.
Yeah, OK. Anyway, well.
I'll teabag your mushroom in a minute.
Oh, boy. You guys catch me.
Fucking catch me first. Me, get in here.
You know
all I know.
And I'm
why is there so many ducks?
Like the duck is, like, everywhere.
Is this a theme, man?
When I. Went back.
Went way, I
might not like you do that with.
You. Well, you know that.
Oh, not that you guys.
Guys, I think we left Ike
Barton's guys. I think we left.
I, i, i i i i'm sorry, ok?
I just I had to sneeze
well.
Oh, nice. Ron.
Fox. Like what?
I had to sneeze.
I'm not. Allowed to us these.
Women. That's right.
I'm doing it on this court again.
This motherfucker. Give me a second.
Where are we? We wait.
Are we actually
are we not using ingame voice?
We we're using. End game voice.
We're using game voice.
No, never mind, guys.
He is not muted. Stop.
Yeah, it's double.
It's doubled up.
If I mean, this goes something you gave.
Update it.
Glowsticks made it out.
We already
put your volume to zero, though,
because we want the Fuji thing
to light up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Oh.
Oh, I get it.
I'll tell you, you're. A smart boy.
Thank you.
I was down here
this is like a little fight
about a fighter,
but it is this like a we can crawl inside.
I'll know. What the fuck.
I'll call inside. You crawl inside.
All over.
That's that's a lot to fit inside. OK?
Yeah. Yeah, I know, I know.
I get that a lot amount.
What is this, like a underground mine?
Are we going to the mines?
No, I believe it's just.
All right. We have officially entered the.
This is our last two.
This feels like Alice.
All right,
so it's not scary, then. Gotcha.
Yeah. What, you weren't that scared by it?
Nah. Last two is mostly
just kind of gross.
It was.
It's very gory and dark.
It's very gory, very gross.
But it wasn't really that scary.
My favourite part was at the beginning,
there was one dude who ran away
from the crowd like he was after me.
And then suddenly he turned around
and he ran away,
and he just kind of, like, crouched over
and ran away, like, smuggle it.
Maybe it made me laugh quite a bit.
In the first part, they were there.
The word was on the statues, deeper
in the maze.
It's L, so begins with E.
Are ha got it?
Had to shift some stones. With E.
And there is. What the hell's
the password?
Giant maze open for me.
Maybe there's a clue somewhere
like open sesame.
Also, I believe we've lost our friends.
Well, yeah.
I thought there.
Oh I hear them remove. Remove.
Hello them behind for you.
Yeah. I've just progressed.
Where hazing you. This is how you get used
to this experience.
OK, also congratulations for beating 52.
That's a difficult game.
Oh, you bet.
Yeah, I was there one and a half
and I was, I was like cheering.
It was great. It was. Amazing.
You did so well.
Honestly, I was so proud.
That game night
while that game took me a while to be.
The sixth night, though.
Oh, my God. Oh, my. God.
I had to shift some stone plates
around to get this thing working.
Now, what the hell's the password?
Giant maze open for me.
Maybe there's a clue. Some it somewhere.
We had to look for clues. I am the best.
I know.
We can't move it right now,
but the code begins with E and ends an s.
Eggs.
You're a funny fucking guy.
No, no. We got a real fucking comedian
way home.
Oh, it's one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Yes, a q. It's nine letters long.
Has a Q after that.
What was the first and last letter again?
Equality is the first letter and then the
second letter, but we can't read.
So a share.
No, it's just. Uh.
What? Oh. Oh, I.
Oh, no.
What? Oh, my God.
What will happen alone?
Hey, guys, I'm scared.
What happened over here?
Well, by.
Itself, it was through my screen and went.
Boom,
no one boom vine boom.
Like a vine. Boom.
Yeah, like a vine boom.
Oh, my. Oh, I didn't save it.
I don't know.
I got to I put the phone app to JavaScript
sound of my dogs la
the other day, and I forgot to save it.
I think I got jump scared by tech soccer.
I'm not going to allow. What
hey, guys.
I see.
Oh, wait. You guys hear that?
I just heard someone breathing.
Something is breathing around me.
I don't. Know.
Why are we heading towards the ghost?
Why are we wanting to. Face.
I heard of creepy.
There's a fucking tricycle there.
They're laughing out for a ride,
guys. I'll be it.
Is the shining.
Yo, I don't think we should head
towards. The ghost.
Noise. Oh, my God.
Somebody. Somebody ran to the side.
They went ooga booga.
Somebody went down that way.
Somebody will
it's like, well, that's.
Close to an adult male.
Adult male male.
Seven has removed all the teeth.
Everything's just. OK.
They had a man that's information.
Mark Oh, this way,
this way, this way. This.
This is where they went, though.
This is where the ghost ran to.
Yeah, exactly. So we're chasing the.
Ghost thing, which.
Is how all the sights
I mean, the the how do.
I don't think this is, like, fisma phobia.
Hello?
Is there, like, a. Limit in the.
I think we're supposed to use the ghost.
They will find our way.
Yeah. Yeah,
I think. My God, we all thank you.
Thank you. Yeah,
I forgot about the guys. Guys, it's guys.
I found the. Oh,
my team were full of idiots.
Well, it's a big bone, really.
This thing. This thing does. It's a bone.
And it also it does that kind of stuff.
It looks.
Like.
Oh, hi, h this is Officer Frank Mills.
My boy Robert's been missing
for nearly two days now.
We're not moving fast enough.
I'm taking it on myself
to get through this damn gate.
Find where is hiding in this fucking maze?
This should help me keep evidence.
Anyways.
That's a
boner.
It's ominous.
Did you guys heard the audio tape right.
Yeah, I heard. It.
I didn't hear any of that.
Oh, you didn't really?
Oh, no.
Yeah, no,
I heard something, but it was super quiet.
Oh, wow.
So a boy got lost.
You know, and got lost.
Then he's in these fields. Shit.
So fields of.
Green opening up here.
At least
oh, there's a shadow.
This is the safe house.
Oh, like this.
Oh, I hear music come from it.
Creepy arse. Music. There's music.
And like, a lot of religious things,
then it's a safe house.
Nice. It sounds like little nightmares.
Kind of.
Somebody's having a bad day down here.
Reminder to self.
Give them some space.
This is a creepy arse folk music. Yeah.
It reminds me of the little nightmares
theme.
You know, I'm
on some sort of.
Method of mechanism.
So dark hair
and you get the whole thing glowing.
What if controls anything
OK? Oh, checkpoint.
Checkpoint. Hey, we got a checkpoint.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Mechanism is
just sort of mechanism mechanisms
to get the whole thing going.
One of the controls, anything?
Nothing else. You
gain here is tweaking, working.
Thought he was looking now.
Tweaking, but he was looking right at me.
But I just froze up and he wandered away.
Note to calls called someone to come
get this guy when I saw this,
and I just froze up and he wandered away.
So that's highlighted.
So if you guys see anybody.
Don't move.
All OK? Why?
Oh, that's all. Well, that's a hint.
OK, so if we see a.
Ghost I don't. Know.
I didn't get the hint.
If we see a ghost,
do not move and don't see anything.
Am I the only one
that's using the glow sticks?
Yes. Oh, yes. Walls and.
Oh, it says a. Bunch of statues.
About this find the.
Labels are ruined, but a few of them
still have letters remaining.
Hello?
Oh, pow, pow. Wow.
Well, what.
Am I, dead
by man?
I'm dead. I'm dead, too.
I am on the ground. Ike,
you got to pick me. Oh, someone.
Oh, don't don't pick me up
like I picked me out.
You'll get it.
Get the fuck out of here first.
OK, pick me up.
Hello? I'm about to die.
I'm bleeding out. I'm bleeding out.
I'm bleeding out. I'm bleeding.
Oh, my God. I'm dead.
He always got me I'm revived now I'm dead.
All thank you.
Sorry. I thought I could.
I couldn't speak.
I did speak either.
This bitch is still screaming like hell.
All I think boxes
that we can go back
and get them in there on the safe house.
Oh, so I guess so
I just so I just wait. You die.
You just kind. Of come back.
Yeah, we turned off her body.
Just a bit after that.
After I was.
I was right back.
That, like,
the fact that both walks and shot
are just the hand on the paper
just went completely out the window.
So I just stood there and watched
you two get mangled.
No, I just. Yeah, you know what happened?
I wish she was, like,
helping us like this motherfucker.
No, look.
I heard whispering,
like, right deep into my left
ear canal, and I panicked the fuck out.
I thought something was on my arse
and I was dead anyways,
but that was right in front of us.
And Vasari like a bomb.
Oh. I did, I did.
I saw the I saw, like,
the dude, like, kissing your soul
oh. Well, OK.
So now we know what to do, at least.
Yeah, let's not let's not scream.
Not whatever you guys did.
I'm sorry.
I think there's a.
Bunch of statues back this way.
Labels are ruined, but a few of them
still have some letters remaining.
OK, so this one says e u e,
but imagine this is the first clue.
This is the first three letters
of the three guys.
Yeah. Oh,
go. Help, help, help! Oh!
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
The way guys.
My bleed Alzheimer I bleed out timer.
Oh, no.
Oh, he was.
I'm very pretty.
Probably guys going to I oh.
I could be OK.
I think it's because of his socks.
Oh, no, I'm that.
I'm that.
The end endgame voice.
I was like in between Ike's legs there.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, OK.
All over were liver
I'm alone now, I think.
No, you're not.
Oh, hey, what's up, demons?
It's me.
Yeah, boy.
It got.
OK, which one's the lights? Sticks.
I got to use the light sixes.
Well, number two is to be
lost. You're going to get us killed.
So you just got killed.
Oh, wow.
We're back.
Speaking.
Audio.
Audio jungle time.
You turn your rules away.
Shut the fuck up, British.
Shut up, British.
Because of what Virginia all spoke.
Where? The spoons in here.
Shut up, British.
I like that one with ghosts.
I know how to deal with ghosts.
I found out. I found a little.
I found a puzzle area.
Why was this puzzle. Huh?
Oh, no.
There's just me and you guys now.
What is this?
This mechanism looks old.
I thought Johnny set this up with a fair
can afford this kind of budget.
A Jason. One.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Oh, it's like it's one of.
These puzzles
ok. OK, ok.
All right.
Well, I think I need my friends
for this one, so I'm going to go back
and get my friends,
or I could just solve it on my own. Why?
I don't want to do that.
I will look for them.
Hey, it's my first time.
Who's ever said that to me?
I found a. Puzzle.
You a puzzle? Yeah. And bass.
If you ever play heroes of or watch,
it's like it's similar.
It's like you press one symbol,
and then the surrounding symbols light up.
So you got to like, oh.
Like you to use my glow stick.
Oh, I get it. I get. It. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't.
You have to, like, look, glow them all out
glow them a lot, I think.
I think you got some either Jago them
all out is what I'm thinking right now.
OK, so give me a second.
I happen to be standing here
which set off enough stuff.
Or maybe you all glow.
I don't. Johnny set this up.
No way.
And the fair
can afford this kind of budget.
We can change
the colours of our Glowsticks.
See a Jason.
OK, I get how it works.
Now, when you step on a tile,
it highlights everything
that is adjacent
on, like the X and y axis.
Mm hmm.
So not diagonal.
Yeah, only z, our x and y.
So we have to, like,
make it all glow. I think
seems right.
Yeah, we can go. Yeah.
Hold on, everybody step off them.
And, like, let's think about this.
I want to. It's OK. So wait.
And if I fill them off,
put them that are mine.
So OK.
So now most of them are off.
Yeah, most of them are off now.
OK, let's pick this one.
That turns that one off.
Know you play a bunch of puzzle
games earlier.
I think you have the, you know, the
the brain folds for this one, right?
I that's why. Perhaps.
I heard something
was I.
Know that's me stepping on the.
Fucking box doing weird sounds.
Right?
I thought it was a.
Somebody
walking around on the puzzle pieces.
Sorry. I yeah.
That's what's.
Happening.
Is blowing vox meteor.
T y you
mean main stream, the way you named it.
You are terrifying
when you walk up in from my face.
You know that.
Oh, my God.
If I go too close to you
like your eyeballs,
I can see I can just cut through your head
and see your eyeballs.
I can smell your hair.
If I do that. It should turn up.
It smells like. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is it about these inexpensive steam
ghost.
Left.
Have such funny characterised.
Some form of phobia to use as a glitch.
Ghost?
I think.
I think Ghost Hunter Core is my favourite
one with the way that they just kind of
have their arms hanging by their sides.
And they walk slowly.
They just look really funny.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
I see the equation.
No, I don't. Oh, you're so close.
Are we?
Are we ok? OK. OK.
This is. All. Worn.
This one out.
I think we have to be such here
and here.
Here and here and then.
Oh, you're close.
You're close.
Middle one middle, one middle, one metre,
one middle.
You got a middle one.
But no, no.
I'm different weight. I'm stupid.
Ignore me. Ignore me.
I'm a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
And and then
after that. We have to.
Turn them all on.
If we can highlight
only the corners we win
wait.
I think I have an idea. I have an idea.
Oh, OK.
Shit.
No, wait, wait, wait.
Do you see it? You see it?
No, not quite.
If I do
that, then we get to those corners.
And if I do this,
we get those corners
it's just that thing in the middle.
Where's Box?
Oh, my God. He's here. Three.
Yeah, he said.
I. I'm chilling in the corner because
this puzzle is genuinely beyond me.
I'm really bad at these.
We got to get the ones
to light up in the corners first.
Yeah. Prioritise that. Yeah.
1000, oh.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. I think I know, I know.
Yeah, yeah.
Can somebody step in the middle.
Of the middle? Hold on, hold on, hold on.
No, no, never mind.
It was a good idea.
Oh, OK.
Not now. We're all stepping on them.
Hold on, hold on.
Well, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, yeah. Hold on for a second. OK.
Uh, I just want to see if I can.
How do I.
I want to get this.
OK. OK, and then
only and so on. Stepped on the middle.
Hold on. Fuck.
I'll step on you.
I think I saw it for a second.
Because I want these to light up.
And then no.
It was close.
Fuck. OK, I have an idea. Hold on.
If everybody could, like,
step away from the tiles,
I want to see if I can try something.
OK. Well.
Ok. So
I figured out that these
the corners work that way.
Oh, oh, oh, that's it.
Oh, yeah. That was all.
I was nice hey, smart car.
Smart.
Smart cookie.
Oh, my god.
I was pretty good.
Know I was about of girl
that when the teacher says
find a duet partner
for this work a bit like I.
Don't.
And then we
just have to pick out with someone stupid.
I guess I'll just go with shuttle.
I'm stupid. Yeah.
Yeah, you are.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where the fuck we do?
They leave.
What?
Well, OK.
OK, then.
I guess we are, huh?
Guys, what the fuck?
Why'd you leave us? Come on, keep up.
Keep on trying and trying.
Trying. Right?
That's a really dark like.
And this one. Also.
It's a long and dark.
I really. Like.
So why? Why?
I heard something.
Or something,
but it was not in front of my face.
Low facts that, like,
when you when you go into the trees,
you can still move like
a completely unencumbered movement speed.
So it's like you just like. Yeah, yeah.
When you're talking.
And then you walk into the, oh.
Yeah.
I'm going to be the first time
you walk into a bush wooded box.
Oh, we're back now. Now, listen, Michael.
What do you mean? Easy. Wait.
So important lesson put the glowsticks.
Over back here, OK?
Oh, no, thank you.
He q you is a IQ. Yeah.
I'm his. Equations.
Is that it? Equations?
Oh, I thought it was equations,
but it's one little short. Oh.
Equestrian.
A hunger.
Equal equal.
Equal y.
Equals equal.
You're the one that ask
what's the who's a lie?
Oh, he was misled.
Never mind that young demon slayer.
He grew on me like he was E.coli.
And I was British beef at room
temperature.
Equinox guy.
You know, stupidity, though.
Alba Knox.
Albert Knox.
I assure you can do this
at trying to find a cure for like.
What was the letters on the statue again?
I don't remember.
Listen, listen.
I'm slightly I'm slightly tipsy
and my eyes are full of tears.
I'm doing my best.
So I'm going to give you a clip.
I missed it again. Yeah.
And you want to wipe your shirt
on top of your chair?
So my shirt.
What? You.
L. L.
L. What the fuck is.
Wrong with you? I'm offering.
What's what's that?
Why is it always at all
kind of, like, patchy in some places.
I've had dried semen.
But you. You are.
You are.
You know, that's a lot of myself.
I'm not sure that.
You are such a. Bastard. Man.
You know what you're facing at this point?
We have me and I. Got the exact same shit.
What the hell are you talking about?
Well, fine.
You want me to.
Oh, it's with.
Oh, OK. Give me a second.
I think I messed up with this one. Yes.
I was doing that.
Why did you why did you eat this?
So equal sign equally.
E and you. Okay.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, we should go back inside.
I don't like the little wiggle
that you deal when you're like.
Yeah, why is. It like, I'm slow?
Why is it why is it working?
Like my camera
when I was doing my cooking,
which is slowly bouncing over my kitchen
counter, hmm.
OK, ok. OK. We're done with this.
No, don't move anything.
I just want to see.
OK, I'll be right back.
I'm going I'm going to head back into
the maze real quick and just take a look.
Are you trying to put in?
So I'll be there.
I just want to. See the way.
You maybe spelled it now. OK,
no chat it's just me and you guys missing.
Yeah,
I'm just kidding.
I actually.
Do you want to go back into the maze
and look for any other clues?
Because it seems like
we're missing something
it feels like it might not be a word.
Like if it feels like
it might not be a word
and it might just be like
a jumble of letters,
and it's just trying to give us
the illusion.
It's an actual word.
So that's why we're going to head back
over here and take a look
this is a solo mission.
I think I can still hear
the voices of the gamers,
and that will optimise with the
what's it called with the audio it's
it seems
this thing's looking at me.
Why are you looking at me?
Hello, Oh,
oh, OK.
Well.
Ah, well,
it might be about time
while we get the fuck out.
I think OK.
OK, we're fine.
We're fine. Right.
Don't move.
No, it's ok.
It's OK.
No, there's nothing.
I got nothing out of this.
What the fuck?
Actually got.
Nothing.
Sounds outside that as well.
Oh, my God. Wait. I think I'm lost.
Oh, no, wait. How do I.
Is it blocked off?
Wait, is it blocked off?
Oh, my God.
It's blocked off.
Guys, I'm actually way.
Oh, fuck.
That's bad.
Help!
Help! Someone!
Someone send help!
Guys, guys. Somebody's going to. That.
I need help.
I don't know.
Is he is he going to
Oh, no.
I said not to move, so I didn't move. Oh,
no, no, no.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God. That's bad.
Hang it.
Fuck! No.
Oh, I died.
Too. There was no good clues.
I'm so confused.
I got wrecked by the monster.
I Sierra.
I don't like the way he looks.
Creatures terrifying.
You are
maybe I go down this way instead, right?
Oh, my God. I'm lost. I'm so lost.
I'm so lost.
And I get the fuck away from him
where I'm at.
I actually
flew.
I found another clue. Oh, my God.
It was worth it.
Holy shit. It was worth it.
X, x x.
Yes, ok. OK.
Oh, my God.
I got to help him, dude.
I got to go back and tell them
that I
please.
Please don't die. Please don't
I please don't. I need. I have.
To. This is a vital it's a vital clue.
What the hell, man?
You know,
oh, my God.
I hate it. I hate it so much.
I hate it so much.
Maybe there's another clue back here.
E q you and axes
if both.
Oh! Ow!
Oh, it hurt me.
Oh, my God.
The ghost the fucking ghost heard me talk.
I'm so damn oh.
Oh, my fault uses them.
They use. I forgot it uses my microphone.
A jar.
Godzilla, Ant-Man.
Oh, all right.
All right. OK, ok, ok. OK.
All this.
If I can make it back,
I need to make it back.
Hello.
There he is. I found the clue.
I found another clue.
Where is it? I've.
Ah, it's the last part of the.
It's X.
Yes, it's the last three letters are x s.
Yeah.
It has to be for the latter. Or something.
I think so. Yeah.
So the first 23 letters are
I. Yeah,
why me?
All right.
I lied.
I didn't do anything.
Well, I can crawl.
I can crawl
all right.
I think I got
oh, Robert, fuck me.
Fuck me. My
I can't believe I just said all right.
I think we're good in that.
I got it.
Listen, sometimes
in life,
we can feel like there's no way out, OK?
You're a sheep trapped in a maze.
You're back. Oh.
Designed by wolves.
OK, I got you on
oh. Fuck me.
But in a maze like that,
there's always two doors to choose from.
And behold, one of those doors is all the
sweets and confectionary you can imagine.
Fantastic.
How come you bring this oh, no.
Oh. L.A.
fan to McDonald's.
Burger King
but there's also another burger block.
A Burger King Doyle.
Not a fan, not a friend.
The door is another door.
Another door is harder to get through. Oh,
if you want
to hazard a guess,
what's on the other side of that door?
You know,
I think it's alerted by the flock
oh. Backing up.
I'm backing up.
I'm backing the fuck up.
Anyways,
I think it got alerted to anything.
Do you
do you do anything except back it up?
I thrust forward.
Oh, really? When, when, when?
Right now.
You look who's in front of me right now.
Look who's in front me right now.
I think I like that.
Whatever, OK?
I think that somebody has to activate
because I managed to get past him,
but I heard you guys getting slaughtered.
It's I came back for you.
I had. To recite an entire passage
from one to the.
World of the. Soul. OK.
Another five if boxing show for time.
I'm not going to lie
here's what I was doing.
I was standing behind Vox
and I was flickering my flashlight on
and off,
and I heard that. And he attacked.
Oh, god.
Oh. So
you see, the first time.
The first time I approached that door,
I thought it must be Jesus.
On the other side, it's
not Jesus, it's another door.
Where He wants to take the guests away
from the other side of that door.
I'm dead.
Yes. Jesus.
OK. OK.
Well, hello.
OK, good.
We got it. Seems like we're good.
I think so.
I know I am.
Are you guys hanging in the trees?
Hello?
Hello. I'm
I know.
Where I am.
Standing cowardly.
Welcome back.
Is there anyone I might. Come back. To?
Uh, ok.
I think we need to go over here.
We never made a pass here.
If you go down there, I think you find us.
I'm pretty sure that's where I found it.
Yeah, if you had down here, I think.
I don't know if there's any other.
Paths
is there another path.
And see us?
Yeah. And there's these statues.
Yeah. Yeah,
that one got me to
hell. Yeah.
A little jump
all right, you little.
Man. I'm dead.
I can't pay electric bill.
Isn't fucked up.
I'm laughing. I don't know
where are they?
Oh, no.
Like they told you.
Tell you to, like, stand still,
but doesn't
really work.
Like, works when it feels like it.
Oh, crawl to me.
I can't see anything.
I don't know where you are.
Man. I'm dead
or I got less.
I gotcha, gotcha and less.
And unless.
Yeah, you're not dying on me.
Oh, dude, you're huge. Huge.
Are you in the eye? I am sorry, folks.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry.
Like, are you in the bushes right now? I
a friend for years in the bushes.
That's not got someplace else.
Like, a long way.
That's a very bad idea.
Let's go back how we go back. OK.
Do you guys know the way back?
Where do we go?
I'm just going to go this way.
I think it might be fun.
Yeah, sounds good to me.
Sounds good to me.
I really. I really enjoyed the first one.
I really enjoyed that experience
because we just walked out and we saw
you two walk out and your character model
just begins again.
Oh, this is the axis area for
you guys.
Just scared me, so. Yeah, no, that was.
Nothing in this game. It scared me so far.
Oh, my
dear one.
I got scared by. He did.
She did a little jump.
But when he saw I was so adorable.
I said I didn't even know
you could jump in this game.
The XY is at the end.
We already were here.
No, it's just me to get past the dude,
you know.
Really?
It's like the moment you hear him,
you don't really have a choice.
When I got you.
Oh, poor Vox.
The zam ification.
All right, grandpa, where are you?
What do
oh, this is bad.
Oh, that's not good.
It's damned if you do.
Damned if you don't.
If you don't move
and he walks into you, you're dead.
And if you move to get stand
out of the way,
you're dead.
That's all I have, like, 3 seconds.
Thank you.
Holding. Oh.
Love oh,
my God.
We are three people.
Hello?
To all
kinds ok.
OK. Where the wait.
Where's where's the way out?
Where's the way up on the sound?
Here is not the way
you would go down.
We let's to go down this way.
That's where you went. Exactly.
That's where we have to go, though.
And we turn here.
I think.
You and I don't think.
This is look familiar.
I think
I think you need to hide in the bushes
yeah.
I think you're supposed
to stand off to the side here.
It doesn't matter.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I
you're right.
Show oh.
Oh, my God.
She caught me.
I didn't see him.
Oh, motherfucker.
I told you to write my right.
You mean my right
or your right? No, right.
Like God.
Way. Yeah.
This is the way out here.
This is the puzzle.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's the way. Out is the way out.
You want it out, you want to end.
You want to go back in.
But we have we have six letters, right?
Oh, really?
Oh, yeah. We need the middle three, right?
Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's true.
Oh, my God.
Where are the middle? Three letters.
Do that. Squeezebox?
Oh, yeah.
Where is he? Heard him.
I think I heard him yelling.
Oh, my God.
Yeah.
I'll go back and get on
I miss.
I miss him.
I'll go back for the boy.
The demon needs
the help of the demon slayer.
Imagine that.
Vox Vox
Vox, are you there?
VOX Well, if he's already back
on, if he's already back, like,
he just slipped by.
There's no way did he go check
he could already
be back, and I just, like,
you know, look like an idiot, so.
But it's the thought that counts, right?
The thought that counts
all hello.
Hello.
I'll wait.
Why is it so long?
Oh, my God, you.
The cornfields.
Ah, these aren't even cornfields.
These are just trees.
I feel so lost right now.
This is insane.
Yeah. Yeah, it definitely is.
Yeah. All along, the three. Hi.
All I want.
I want back to.
Look for Vox, and he was already back
here, OK?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. He that he died.
Or you were looking for. Me.
Yeah, I thought your back of the cavern
by your cell phone.
I was. I was thinking some quick facts.
But that's a company.
Equifax.
Tim English.
You you equate how do you say Equinox?
You're like in English.
Where. What is it?
And what even is like Equinox.
Know it. When?
When the sun. Equinoxes.
Yeah. Yeah, it might be that.
Let me try.
That. I've never even heard of that. Word.
Oh, wait.
I heard it in Avatar on it series.
Yeah, it's like you ever heard of the
spring equinox and the summer solstice?
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
If everything is going to die
because of the fire station.
OK, ok, ok. I've heard it in Swedish.
Non English.
Everything changes.
It, isn't he?
Q I mean, the duties of fire.
So that kind of makes sense.
You know, by nature, the dude has like
five tattoos in his body.
Kind of makes sense. Yeah.
Yeah.
Quit Knox's and.
Oh, yeah, that would that would
kind of make sense, wouldn't it?
And so I'm so is my.
Your would you go oh.
Let's go find a ship.
Fuel gas.
Also.
Apparently the books are collectable,
so we should pick up the books
or something like 00.
What are the loading screen jumps Skip.
Yeah, that's. True to me.
What we have a. And go.
Lancer now.
Oh yeah. We got a lot of pain.
Oh this is so much better.
I mean my radio is not working either.
It can move further into the maze
if I can get a signal.
Drove him to system.
Joanne, Joanne.
Joanne from June one wrong.
Fear.
My one.
I like it, but I can make you
guys laugh with one of yours.
Imagine imagine unironically being called
Juan and just.
Just being that horse.
One point
was this a potato or no slot potato?
I love how it is.
Like, slowly getting to know Spanish means
I love it here.
Well.
It's something you don't get lost.
All right, all right. I'm coming.
Up. Let's get us. Lost.
Why are the paths so much wider now?
This is not a scary.
It might narrow out.
It may be the new monster
was like a different mechanic.
Yeah, maybe he maybe he's a thick boy.
We'll have those six.
Oh, yeah, we did.
A thick boy.
Oh, I said, no.
I go. I think there's.
Something behind the gates.
I can hear it breathing.
One. One.
One, one. Oh.
Fuck you.
Oh, my God.
That's my fucking guy. But
you laugh.
You really should stop here.
Now, you do realise you're asking a bunch.
Of people
that are traumatised by that nice.
Guy huh?
It's definitely of all the fun and games.
Definitely out of the gate.
It's definitely the funniest jump scare
noise.
Like, it just sounds like someone
getting flattened by a car.
My guy.
Who is the animatronic,
that gave me the most trouble.
I'm betting it's either like it's
oh, it's always balloon boy.
It's always. Balloon boy. Balloon shit.
And what else?
Balloon boy?
Oh, yeah, that's a be quiet.
Shut the fuck up.
That new guy I think it's a new guy.
I'm different.
Yeah.
What was that?
You dropped it still.
What's he doing?
Why is he dropping the dump?
We got to stop him.
This is a public place.
He can't do. That. I don't think.
I think I thought he was pooping.
And me, not one. Ain't anything. Pooping.
Oh, it's so dark down here.
It's behind the gates.
I guess we're face faced. Safe for now.
Yeah,
I think. I think he's behind the gates.
If anyone else finds themselves
locked in here.
I'm sorry. I'm closing the gate behind me.
That thing has been travelling me
through the maze
ever since I pull the lever, I can hear it
thumping steps and it's raspy breath.
I need to get away from it.
I'm not sure I can keep going.
That's following me.
One. Guys, the other tape, I got to say
unlocked. Unlock the main gate.
Get him in the maze.
Farm field, take greenhouse
cages, take playground.
Oh, managed to get.
Through the first gate.
So to go to the greenhouse and around
playground, whatever but this second.
Gate now.
There's
open space that I can see behind it.
Which I'm willing to take.
Doesn't really say much.
He's just like, I solved a puzzle and
I got him, but I can't get any further.
OK, now, Felicity.
How can I get the damn thing open.
I hear the tape is over, but the tape
didn't really didn't share anything.
Like, he was just like, Oh, Dwight.
He sounds constipated.
The tape is overrated.
You hear that?
There comes
notes like a mummy.
Sounds like.
It. Sounds like it's right in front of us.
Yeah, he's probably walking
through the corridor, past the trees,
one on the right
come on.
Reason why they gave us lanterns
instead of flashlights.
They're so much worse.
I don't know.
If you like the way more. It's just maybe.
It looks like lanterns.
I see.
I see the person
more like the actual person better.
I see. I see more with the lantern.
I feel like we connect better
when I use a lantern.
Oh. Collectable.
Collectable.
All right.
It's highly collectable.
All right, Glowsticks.
Thank you.
You guys have a watch guys
watch Jemmy Neutron.
I, i it's breathing down my throat.
I mean, my, my, my neck.
Why? My throat?
My neck.
I meant. Yeah.
Was breathing. What it's like.
Who is fucking Carl Weasley?
Is he wheezing down your throat?
I Jimmy's mom.
What's wrong? Shout. That shouldn't be.
You're craving my cat.
So she do want a cross honouring.
The book of.
I ah, the extra button.
Is a monster.
Wait, I just have one more and then.
That'll be it.
Every remove reminder
yeah.
Where the fuck do you go
I'm searching for?
Think she went to the forest?
I wasn't.
That bad.
Fuck off your scary stop the
bastard. OK.
Push British man you British man get back
here,
please. I
I partner.
I lost my life partner I cannot canin
my essay I.
Like.
He's off.
OK, here. Hold on My goal.
Mike All.
The game loves winning
I thought What the fuck is that?
More I It's not back here
take it back now it's not back there.
I think he turned out
he want my one down this way.
Professor,
my lab partner is nowhere to be found.
We found exposed stick.
Oh, blue.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wait, I did go down this way.
Left a trail.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Evil
what was that?
Look behind you.
We we got lots of all VOCs.
Is that what happens?
I think he got locked.
She all know.
I think in late, I heard a guy.
All in all, we're stuck.
Do just take the stay off me yourself. Me?
I don't want to get locked away
behind some roots over here.
I think
I do those creepy.
You are super creepy.
And remind me of Harry Potter.
You remind me of everything.
What's it called?
One. I'm in
the one of a part of EB.
When Gary and
Gibbon Mary got separated.
The trail stops here.
Which will stay here.
I don't think it would have said a
player has died.
I found the house.
Hello?
Someone locked in here.
Oh, is that Ike?
Hello.
Oh, no.
Guilties
hello.
Ah, I think I'm.
I'm the all.
All. That's not good.
I just put my glowsticks
to let people know I was here.
Is pretty bad.
Blow.
Why not find my glowsticks
i think he might have died.
I think the monster got remote. OK,
I'm the only one here at the moment.
The mixture evaporates.
What mixture?
Odds and vines reacts.
The common pesticides just to make my own.
Is this.
Chloride?
Low, low?
The fuck was that.
Chloride reacting of yellow and green dye?
Need to swap it with another bottle.
Need some move.
What is that?
C-H seven from red to yellow
sulphate.
I sell sulphur oxygen in green chickens
nationally.
So far the valve on red leaking
do not use a cell or stage seven
blue dye holding up
well should be ok to leave
C chloride in their
CB breaking down an all balls except red
guys.
Give me an update.
What's happening
with the others right now.
And all is VOCs is VOCs I can remove good.
I do chemistry
box died.
Ah wow.
That's bad.
While the game split us up
it's mixture evaporates what's.
What goes off blue.
What I start with
yellow and green
yellow
and green my objective updated
what did I do?
I do something.
I don't know if I did anything or not.
It's a swap off another bottle
mm hmm.
All right.
I'm really confused.
I need their help right now
because I know if I need more bottles
or a light I'm just going to head back.
Like, please hope I can find them.
They found each other.
OK, good, good, good, good, good.
Oh, now
I feel so lost.
It's here.
I feel so goddamn lost.
In this maze
oh, no.
Should I just die
so I can regroup with them?
Where is it
where is the creature oh.
Hello.
What is this clue?
Oh, yeah, they've been here before.
It's like there's like Glowsticks
gone into this direction.
But well.
This is a dead end.
OK, I'm going to.
Yeah, I'll quickly die so I can regroup
with them since I don't know.
Right now, being separate feels
not so good.
It's probably not the best idea right now.
Uh, where is the.
Hollow. Creature?
Do you hear me?
Hello?
I'm a human close by, but.
I don't or
what the.
Fuck was that?
Oh, my God, guys, I lost you.
I got you
you got me.
I found you.
Where is everybody?
I lost them like I was by myself for
the longest time, so I had to come back.
Yeah, find somebody to me to all the shit
I saw.
You get clobbered. By him
from the distance.
That was crazy. What is that?
Does he have a clone?
No. He's
some kind of a terrifying tree spirit.
All right,
I guess it's just you and me now.
Yeah, they're really far in. They're.
I'm apparently, I think one of them
or a couple of them died.
Unless I was you that died multiple times.
I I've re spawned manually.
One think he would help me
find people, but.
OK, so I think that means that I think
I died.
And Ramu also died.
Oh, now, I don't know, brah.
I saw a couple deaths.
Yeah. Did you ever die?
No. I avoided him there all.
Way if we can just go back.
We should just go grab him.
Yeah, I grab everybody.
What happened. Though.
Was, like,
me and Raymie were going through the maze,
and there was like, a vines
that grew up behind us and separated us
from everybody else, and then.
Oh, OK.
I'm OK. They both died.
They both type. OK.
So the game like, wants to separate us.
I think it should be a round about here.
Or there back at the. Ah.
Hello.
Hello?
Hello? Hello.
You guys hear
Raimo Ik?
Do they have a new save point?
Did they find it like a different area?
There's no way.
Hello.
Tre, go.
I'll. No, I'm here.
Ominous sound effects.
I feel like this is the wrong way.
Yeah, stuff.
Definitely the horn with the fuck out.
Wait, that's them.
Oh, my God.
Friends we thought we found one steal,
and then I found another puzzle room.
Yeah.
I found the chemistry area. Hmm.
They said Nick is a. Naked.
Lady runs towards you.
Yeah. And I got beaten up.
I got beaten up by a naked man.
Yeah, I watched it happen.
It was pretty terrifying.
He's huge.
I think. I think. I think there would be.
If this is not a face,
you can stand still.
I'm sorry.
You guys hear that?
There she is. Oh, she's coming right out.
Oh, let's get out of here.
OK, so.
I'm not ready to die again.
And it works with the flashlight.
I say point the flashlight at her. Oh.
God, you bitch. Oh.
You shall. Not really.
It doesn't work that well.
Oh, it kind of does.
Oh, it does. One.
Oh. Oh, oh. Old rock through.
Running box box.
Back up, back up, back up.
She's giving everyone.
She got a triple kill.
What's
what is that?
I mean, the flashlight kind of works.
Please. I guess you can all go near her.
Oh, your theory of, like,
blinded motherfucker.
Would you go back? She was.
She was. Spooked by the light for a. Bit.
Yeah,
she was, like, trying to cover her eyes.
Yeah.
Was it flashing it on and off?
That helps her. I don't know.
I think I just. Pointed out
you just got a point. Out.
OK, that's to you.
I think. I think it stops there for a bit.
Yeah, OK.
She's there.
There's another dude. There's another guy.
He just.
There's two.
There's two. They're coming together.
Yeah. No, no.
Switch over to the lantern.
That works
she's so fucking slow.
Look at her.
OK, maybe it doesn't work.
OK, I'm going to go into the
ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Hey, hey.
I thought it worked.
It did not.
Guy got my balls.
She dropped them off.
I got you.
I got you. I got you. I got you.
I got you, I got you. Oh,
then I got. You.
Oh, no,
I grabbed your dang it.
Cock and ball.
Ow, ow, ow.
All of us died.
Yeah, we.
Got quadra killed.
All right, everybody, welcome back.
We're back in the cabin. Oh, man.
That is.
That is one tough cookie.
I feel like.
Like they're blinding.
Thing only works sometimes.
Yeah. And then when it works,
it gives us enough time.
So, you know.
The access game and all that.
Oh. We remove all there.
There we go. We just slide.
Low flying along.
Oh, you just kind of folded
it folded up like a deck.
Do we got?
What we need to do is
you use the flashlight, not the lantern.
The flashlight, and
then you blind blender, and then you run.
I think that's the only thing.
Yeah, we got a blender
and then one she, like, cowers for a bit.
Yeah, we can.
We have time to run away and make distance
because we can't just, like,
chill inside the tree.
Know, I was pretty far away from Ike,
but she still got me, so I think we just
need to blend in, then run.
OK, but
we got to make it back to the puzzle.
Me and. The puzzle. Yeah. I also find.
My puzzle two left glow sticks things
I have.
Puzzle one. You.
Oh, I just have a sense for like.
She said, I said he lied.
I see
there they are.
Here they come
and Run.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
I'm with her in this corner.
She left to turn left.
Yeah, but then she left.
Kind of an. Upper left.
You look at my. Look at my bike.
Hey, he's turning left.
Oh. When I go the I go left.
I don't know where I went.
I went somewhere else.
Oh, no.
Either.
Oh, my God. She's chasing ice.
Guys, I've had a puzzle.
Oh, no.
You found a puzzle.
Where
puzzle
I just like trying to blame her
and then actively running away from.
Yeah, he's hiding her really well.
OK, guys, got to tape. Tape to tape.
Oh, there is a tape here.
For I think he's doing.
Is he still running?
You can burn.
All are you to the.
Spiders.
You've been attacked by a virtual world,
literally on your own.
You have handled it like OK.
OK, maybe this isn't a puzzle.
Maybe it's just me.
I think because.
It was kind of
more like a collectable area.
Rather than a puzzle.
Got a tape galore.
That's what we're here for, right?
Oh, no.
Vox. Vox Fox.
Hello? Fox.
Fox. I think we got separated.
Oh, no. Vox Oh, shit.
Dude, that's bad. Fuck.
Vox I think we got separated.
Oh, no.
I can't get to you.
I can't get to you. I'm separated.
The vines are in the way.
Oh, no,
how do I get you there?
I don't. I don't think I can.
You'll have the chemical
oh, this is so sad.
I can we get ten gifted sobs all there.
What do I do?
What I do, I go
What is that?
Who is that guy?
I think.
I think it's Gigi for me.
Well,
well,
I'm back
I got crushed by that giant,
towering beast.
There's two monsters
inside this labyrinth.
I didn't think that was going to be like,
two of them.
I thought it was just going to be one
new one, but now there's two
we have to watch out for.
That's really creepy.
I got separated again and know.
And then I was all alone.
You can have nice things.
Yeah, we can have nice things.
Oh, I hear.
I hear people.
Hello, friends.
Yeah, we're. In the puzzle room.
Probably like
hooking up with the lady.
You the the
the monsters right in front of me.
The monsters right in front of me. OK.
Guys, guys,
what do I do? He's he's. Right.
It's just coming from, like.
All they're dying.
All my friends are getting massacred
right in front of me.
I can't do anything about it.
Hold on.
Let me see mhm.
I'm. I'm quite.
I'm kind of confused about how the vet can
make it over there in time to to revive.
Maybe. Maybe. Hello? Hello? No.
Make it in time.
Run! Why are you running?
Why are you running?
Because I'm running to save my friends.
Objective. Updated. Wait.
They. They solved something.
Oh, that's pretty good.
I got to make it over to them.
Like, I'm, like, so lost right now.
I'm so lost. Player just died.
Wow. Bloggers.
Actually, that's not bloggers.
Maybe I can go back and retrieve
them. Hmm.
We'd like respond.
Hi. Hi. Hi.
They expect you to do this stuff,
which were my dad's.
Are you serious?
Yeah, dude,
that's why I'm. That's why they told me.
To turn off. Permits after dad's. No way.
We would have. We would have, like, guns.
OK, I saw. I saw the tree guy.
I think both of them work the same way.
They see you
from a really far away distance,
but I don't think the flashlight works
in the trade.
Few moments. Later.
Yeah, there's basically two of them.
Also, they have, like, a certain rule,
and they go all the way
back to the puzzle room.
Yeah, I figured out what to do for, like,
the puzzle that me and him have found.
It's just going to take me a while.
And I don't remember where to find
the chemistry puzzle that I had earlier.
It's. That's.
That's like throwing me off.
The whenever Vox went.
Ah. Vox So, I mean, there.
Oh, boy.
Yeah, he's somewhere in there.
Did he figure it out? I'm sorry.
Did you guys have what's it called?
A decided objective? Got updated.
Someone solves a puzzle or.
Yeah. I didn't solve.
Oh, yeah.
There she is.
My highlights.
No, she says she's coming
off you.
Run, run. Run, run, run.
Oh, no.
I got separated.
You got to be kidding. Me.
You got to be kidding me.
No, no, you got to be kidding me.
You locked me away.
Fuck off the tree, guy.
To me.
Where is this.
Oh. Oh, God.
I'm alone.
I need help.
What are your children?
Oh, this is so.
Oh, my God. This is bad.
This is really. Bad.
Oh, oh.
Oh, hey, there.
Hey, buddy.
Hey. Hi.
Oh. Well, I found a different area.
That's a that's. That was weird.
That was like a playground
or some type of shit
is cool, though, but
who else died?
I know.
I said somebody else died, but
I heard children laughing.
All the lights went out.
It bursted in front of me.
That was not fun.
And then locks me away again. Why?
This game is fucked up.
It likes isolating me
it really enjoys isolating me.
I think I heard them somewhere.
That's either
got their own lights, sex, drive, all that
the monsters want me to themselves.
Like it's more like
they want to are my friends.
Oh, I know. I just want back in circles.
What. Bro?
I just want back in circles.
Holy shit.
I didn't even realise
I went back into a whole circle.
Oh, my God, man.
OK, knuckle.
I though the tree dude looks kind of nice
like his. Ah,
like a style
I ah. I miss Voxer.
It's been a while since we saw Vox.
The hell he go
I can smell him
because like,
it seems like he would go down this way
oh, maybe
actually.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
There's a Gary here.
Very been down here till I see red
is follow the red.
All all
hello.
I'm lost.
I'm. I'm just some lost boy.
I don't.
I'm, I, I got a family.
I, uh.
Hello, friends.
Hello.
Oh, shit.
That's pretty bad.
This is pretty bad.
Oh, wait on me.
Maybe I can all all Ike's drill
I can re drill.
OK, ok.
I think again.
Megan, closer.
Am I going closer?
Am I going further?
Dude, I honestly can't tell.
I can't tell at all.
Where are we going?
The fuck am I going?
Am I am I even at it's
or it's the right direction now or. Or
oh, fuck that.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well.
Our cock involves
cock involves oh.
Oh, I know. Shout out.
No. Died at the exact same time.
Yeah, I saw the chance of death and I was
like, OK, I don't, I don't see anybody.
I was alone again. Mm.
Yeah.
I ran into a similar problem.
I found two of the disks.
We got two disks now.
I was out the objectives updated.
Yeah, yeah.
POG you know, actually, the objective
was updated because we found, like, this.
Grassy field.
It with the big the big moss man in it.
Oh, did you guys find the guys
from the playground yet?
Mm. Yeah, I found the playground.
That's where I found that. The disk. Yeah.
I was there too.
It was it's pretty creepy.
There's kids laughing and everything
like that.
Think they excited to go back to Resident
Evil.
Resident Evil seven. Yeah. I saw you.
I've seen the little girl running around,
but she hasn't done anything
and it freaks me out.
So you finished you beat up
what's her Margret beat Marguerite.
Yeah, I really fucking love
dramatic villain.
Deaths like that make me very happy.
Like when you just had it
with the flame thrower,
and then she just kind of, like,
splutters out and turns did fucking dust.
I was like, yeah.
Yeah.
I was like, Oh, Ike Ramo.
He got another seal thinks.
He'll need two more SEALs.
Gamers. Hello.
The other place.
There's a monster near you, I think.
Watch out.
We. Yeah, the the the tree guy.
Oh, this is a dead end.
I think fox is dead. And here, here.
All children shall watch out, watch out,
watch out.
Oh, yeah, my glow.
Oh, hey. Hello.
I gang's all together again.
OK, where's the altar?
Where's the altar?
The altar. Like, which altar?
Where I put the seals.
It's really, really close to here.
I'm not 100% sure where, but we'll find it
dude.
The mount of like, I don't know, euphoria
I get when we all finally regroup together
God is so.
Yeah I had such an amazing moment
where I was completely lost in the maze.
And then all of a sudden
I see Damon. I'm like.
How did you find me? And she just said.
I found your. Glowsticks.
You haven't found the glowsticks I'm here.
But then it's just like we.
Got we got two discs in here already.
Oh, yeah. Here. Yes. Ta da!
OK, ok, now we just need some more.
We can ok.
We can not get into the greenhouse
because we need a place in.
Yeah, that's the thing. I don't.
I was trying to figure out the
the what's it called?
The pesticide formula.
It doesn't make any sense. To me.
Do we need to get something else?
We need to get to that
chemistry room, so, like,
so we can understand
what she's talking about.
Yeah, I tried. Yeah,
I didn't understand it. My.
Hold on. Is it? I know it's.
Remember how you got there? Shelter.
I know it's this way.
I know it's
definitely this way of ghosting,
but be careful.
The game might separate us.
And this is like where?
I don't know, like,
which. Way to go. The vines.
The vines just, like, pop up sometimes
yeah.
And it forces us to just stay separate.
So I think we should stick together
really close.
So it can't, like,
keep us from getting cut off.
Oh. I'm will get.
I'm over door.
I've been building.
Yeah.
Anyway.
OK, what's this?
This looks familiar.
I've been here before. This is close by.
This really lights of the chemistry.
Yeah, I think.
OK, I'll take my glowsticks from here.
All out.
There it went. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We all.
But we're all together.
We're all together. Again this time. Good.
Oh, things together.
What does that sound like?
I think it's just us singing.
No, like the thing with your soul.
Me What the fuck?
OK, now I don't know where to continue.
But I love you singing.
Oh, great. Leave it. To me. Hello? To me.
You might end up with what
I'm on a bit of.
I don't know what you know.
If I follow this, I horse it.
You said I need your plastics
to write my career.
Thorough.
Mama.
Honestly,
that sounded like a fucking incantation.
I thought as a demon, I would have been.
What is this shit?
Oh, hello.
Bounce. Hello, gamers.
Guys, guys.
Well, say hi to the clown. Oh, hi. There.
That was one of the freakiest things
I've seen in a game in a long time.
Oh, I hated that.
They all were getting ingredients
for potions.
They all like.
I got the tape.
Fucking froze up on us. It's weird.
OK, that's good. We found one.
Now we off on the last one,
which is at the greenhouse, right?
Human skin on these motherfuckers.
Oh, my God.
So creepy.
OK, I can't take these guys seriously.
They're doing the facial expression of,
you know, the to, like, whoa.
Jack's, like, pointing behind them.
Yeah, look.
Yeah, yeah, I know exactly.
What you're talking about.
Like, oh, my God, it's this.
I don't know. I'm not a tea party.
That's it.
The tape just cut out.
I don't know. In the video,
OK, so I think Melanie's.
I think that's one ingredient
for the poison. That must be it.
You found cheese?
What's.
Yeah, I don't know. Cheese faces.
Really ugly cheese.
OK, well, I guess that's an ingredient
for the poison.
How about we go the other way?
We go the other way.
They'll because there's another.
It's off.
No, it was that cheese. It was.
I think that was it.
That was a seal.
Oh, that.
No, that. Was a seal. You sell.
Have you thought
that was a wheel of cheese?
Yeah. It is. Yes.
I heard them.
Always coming from this side. Right.
We go back. We go back where we came from.
Yeah. Yeah.
Because if from the
I think. I thought that was cheese.
I think we can go down this way.
Yeah, it looks like cheese.
And then it look at the objective. Said
it was like four out of five.
I like. Wait.
You think it was? Yeah.
Let me ask you something.
Do you think it was cheese
or was a teeny bit.
Guys, guys, guys. Cheese.
I need to run out.
This place is. Burning.
Oh, my God. He's going.
To shine the light shine the light shine.
Right.
Oh, no.
Hold on, guys, guys,
I shit.
I had to run. I had to run.
I think I found it
oh, this is just.
It's just the fucking trees again.
All my friends are dying.
Oh, I could flip pasture.
Fuck, no, dude.
I thought we could just.
Slip faster after, like,
flashing her with the lights on. It's
and on.
Oh, my gosh.
I tried to flusher
than, like, slide by by.
Couldn't do that.
Yeah, I got jumped by the big dude,
and I don't think that there's.
Others die from.
Yeah, everyone died. Hey,
that's good, though.
I don't think you can stop him.
We did find something new.
We found a table we.
We did find a table with a rib cage on it.
A rib cage.
Where? Yeah. Huh.
I think we need a box.
Are you OK, Foxy? Good. Yes, I jobs. Nice.
I'm going. Nigel, move.
I yawned and I almost like I yawned really
hard, and I almost went like.
Oh, you. Oh.
Oh, oh, I like that.
And I miss the lasagne.
I still. Oh.
The cheese.
You got to go over them now. We only got.
One to break from the.
Ads. They were done.
They want a break.
For. Oh.
Now the watch is short. Oh.
My God.
Was like your grunts very aggressive.
That's right. That's right.
Just watch a short
ad and get 30 seconds of ad free.
Right.
Considered to be sold all.
Round. As like Alex does with my.
Favourite sound effect is the one
who is like 11 to break from the ads.
One of my favourites.
Many like a clip.
It's a video I called Pan talked before
and it's just like a pair of hands
flying towards the camera
and then it fades to white with the.
Weird sound effect.
But you cheese here.
Put it in and put the cheese.
I got one.
Yeah, but the cheese.
And it looks like a cheese. Yeah.
I mean. She's.
A cheese. Do you.
What kind of fucking cheese.
Hold on. Fucking cheese.
Cheese. Cheese, cheese, cheese.
I'm kind of concern now.
She's cheese.
Fucking cheese.
Next week we'll be looking at egg.
Thank you to oh, yeah.
I know exactly what he's referencing.
Is there another European thing?
I don't know.
No, I mean.
You know.
Technically, I guess.
OK, just James, maybe oh.
My God.
We need to find the greens with the sweet.
All right, go to the greenhouse house.
I will.
I will be the green house.
I've never even seen it.
You never seen the green house?
Haven't I?
Oh. Has gone there. Before. Yeah, I don't.
I don't remember.
OK, we went down this way like the one.
In the field with all the dry grass.
No, no, no. That's where I got the seal.
And you are walking over the trees.
I know.
Yeah.
The first time I got to the greenhouse
was when, like, everybody separated
and got super fucking scared.
It was like
I was trying to look for Ike, and then.
Oh, no.
Oh, you were with me,
and then you disappeared.
And then I just saw a player
that I was like, oh.
Wait a second down here. Oh,
One of the few places where I'm.
Like, breathing.
Trying to communicate.
Yeah, I remember
I was falling asleep, all gone.
All right.
I remember I was following Ike's thing
because I was like, oh, shit.
I see his his lights on.
We follow it,
and then I think I split off here.
No, not here. We hear
because, like, I didn't
end up following the lights at some point.
Folks.
Sorry. Sorry.
I think
OK, now I don't know where to go.
I'm going to lose my glow.
Big chunk. This is very close.
Yeah.
This is a big boy.
Big, big I.
Hate this game.
We I can't even get in.
This is playground.
It's wall place again.
Where do we go from here?
Because we found you places.
For our follow me follow me. Follow me.
I think I saw another area.
Unless it's a dead end.
I'm not sure if it's a dead end or not.
This monster's over there.
Or the big guys.
Like he's
on. He's on the other side of the trees.
It's OK. It's ok.
Oh, this is a dead end.
A fuck. Oh, lovely.
Oh, we need to go to the big guy,
then mm hmm.
Or kill.
You. Oh, Kony, you are.
Hiding the master.
I'm not you. You need to run.
We just got you the fun, right?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess. I guess so.
Yeah, down here.
He's been.
Down here.
My God, this game is hard.
I wish we had, like, a man.
He was. Really there.
Ow, ow.
Ow. Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Well, is this is this, like, baptism?
What that tells me, Daddy?
I mean, the.
Opposite of what whoa.
Waffle.
Daddy.
Father. Excuse me.
Excuse me. It's baptised me, father.
And said father.
So I'll check the board, guys.
We all heard what she said.
Forgive me, Daddy, for I have sinned.
Oh, you are, bitch.
What sakuma you are fucking bitch.
I really hope
this is the way I see my girls.
Y'all, let's go. Let's go.
We found it.
Yeah. Ok.
We like some sort of acid.
There's, like, a body inside.
We shit. Yeah.
Now we got to, like, make the make
the pesticide solution somehow.
Yeah, it's on the other side.
There's a there's a chemistry table,
and then you have to follow the
instructions and mix the shit together.
OK. Ok, let me see
sam behind.
We have to come on. Pesticides
just make my own.
The fuck is this?
I feel chemistry twice. Yes,
I see.
Oh. Yeah.
I took.
I took AP, and I don't even remember
any of this shit.
It's a blur.
I, like, threw it out my head.
It was over.
Canvas and jet.
Yeah.
Any chemists and shot
guys?
How do we how do we how do we make liquid?
What is cb
t. D i
we had these yellow and green dye
and you just drop it with another bottle.
It just kind of reminds you like.
CBT. Like resident evil.
Hey, know, key yogi.
If this game was
if this game was forgiving
we could just hop through the ceiling
like this.
If it honestly, I feel like I would
I would rather just do that.
Just jump up and no, we have like is zero
athletic abilities apparently.
At age
seven from Brett to yellow need a bottle
so we need to find bottles.
Oh let's divide colour bottles.
We have to find more
we have to find more shit.
Yeah of course
we need to find the chemical anatomy.
Hide, hide, hide company.
Come with me. Hide, hide, hide.
Overzealous. No, you see some. Stores.
I see source. Oh my God.
It's all in my purse.
I heard his little all.
Famous.
Oh, I think he's gone.
He's gone. Yeah.
I think the trick is just say Ryan
and then just let it one day.
When we know the different coloured
bottles are right here.
These are the bottles contain.
Green shaking occasionally.
So far,
this is a mixture. Evaporation evaporates.
Yellows that mean you do. It
evaporates, it becomes gas.
You know what evaporates? Yes,
I know what it means.
Do you know what some. Of the water has?
You know what?
Sublimation. Oh, wait.
We don't need to find anything.
All the ingredients
are right in front of us.
That's all.
Saying.
What the hell.
I ain't notice it basically fed this.
Stuff.
The volume bottles are literally right in
front of us.
And I need to swap it with another bottle.
Yeah, coverage nine from red, yellow.
Seven feet.
I don't.
One person that's not here, dude.
All the solutions keep evaporating
this blood.
C, c b breaking down in all.
But is it separate this a lot?
I think I need to, like, write them
all down in, like, a big notepad.
So I don't forget.
I keep lying.
Oh, I love cock and ball torture.
Where is this? You stay here.
Oh, shit. Run.
I've got a solution.
This lady. Oh, no, I don't. Come here.
Come here.
I don't think. Lady screams
when you see us. We can hide.
Little lady is going to.
She sees us. There's no way to.
Ever get.
Sunlight.
Shine the light shine.
OK, OK.
Daniel, I've been worried.
I think
damn.
Oh, my God.
He caught me.
I can't hide from her. No.
Damn, it's me.
Oh. Ha ha ha ha.
All God damn it, man.
All three people died on her.
What happens like.
That? Like, fuck.
Do we solve any of this?
How the fuck do we do that chemical thing?
I don't know that that makes any sense.
Everything else has made complete sense.
That one just doesn't.
Think it's a crime.
I should speak with that manager.
You don't say. All you want to.
All you want to sell them
like we asked for.
No pickles.
Excuse me?
Sure to ask for no pickles.
You are.
Are you the type of person to just tell
them, like, hey, I don't want pickles?
Or, like, you know, you order it, but then
you take it off after you've ordered it.
Yeah, it depends. I mean.
I mean, if I'm in, like, a restaurant,
then I'll just be like, oh,
yeah, I'd really like this.
Oh, fuck, can I have this instead of that?
And in a restaurant, because it takes so
long to prepare the food, then they don't.
They usually it's like, not, it's like,
really not, not a problem for them.
Whereas in, like, fast food,
I will just be.
I'll just take it off.
Yeah.
I just take it off as a matter. I don't.
I really don't like pickles.
Oh, you don't like pickles?
Nah, you'll like like pickles, like,
not even pickled
like I'll open yours or like. No.
Like pickled radish. Pickles just loose.
I just don't like pickle.
Just the. Texture.
Dichotomy. Mostly the texture of a pickle.
Like when I bite into it, you're
not expecting it to be there in a burger.
It's like, look.
Have you
ever had, like, other pickled stuff
that's not like, you know, the cucumbers,
like, daikon radish or like kimchi?
I don't know
what kind of pickle.
I think
we removed in die
or Removed and Die.
And she's still communicating.
All right.
My favourite thing about the voice chat in
this game is the fact that you can hear it
just cut through.
Yeah, we hear them like Oh.
What's the fuck is this, bro?
What is. This?
Wait, what the fuck is this?
What is this?
I've never seen this part before.
Apparently it's already solved
because like, I think they got it via
already, but.
Oh. Interesting.
It was another.
All in the cage.
Nah. That
close behind me or just kind of
just kind of fantasise about getting me.
I'm like getting back by about having
my back against the wall for one second.
Or both in the cage now.
Oh shit. Are both in the cage now.
Are we going to do.
What are we going to do?
But they're not here.
They're not listening. They don't know
they're not.
We're in the cage.
They don't know and all the time
the monsters aren't even here either.
The moon's high in the sky at all time.
All the time in the world.
Yeah, yeah.
No rush, right?
We're never going
to leave.
That's just the gentle swaying of a cage
upon the branches of a tree.
But the way you articulate things, it's
very sexy.
You know, like the gentle
swinging of the trees and the
land and buzzing on high
wealth of branches dangling
through the the bars of the cage.
And your beard is like brushing
against my head.
Bush push.
It's like I'm getting, like, you know,
those those head massagers, like,
those weird long ones.
You just, like,
go in and out of your head. No.
Oh, yeah. It's like a spy. Like.
When you use them on a cat
in the Catholic.
Movies. You've used on a cat before.
Yeah, you can.
Yeah,
that's what I thought I was talking about.
Like this note
like the sort of the metal prong thingy
that when you push it on someone's
head, it kind of spreads out OK.
Anyway, stick your pants off
Jesus.
All right. Ha ha ha ha ha.
You're. Like, flabbergasted for.
I was really talking, like,
I was expecting it earlier.
And then we got into this cat massage
discussion, and I was really aggressive.
Oh, hey, this is the rib cage
that they're talking about it.
Is that a pun?
Oh, it's a rib cage.
Inside a cage.
You know, that's pretty clever.
I see. I see. That's a felony. Yeah.
You got to take credit for those.
Very good. Very good.
Months and months.
Not something I associate with you
on the best of days.
Well, come on, bro. We like have you.
We played through the entirety
of its excuse.
The other, it takes of, like,
a considerable amount of grey matter.
Yeah. You know, chief, such a feel.
Like you did have me. You did have me.
What the fuck it was?
It was a dual effort.
I mean, you had to.
It was like. Yeah, it's like saying. Well.
I mean, yeah, it's like saying.
You're the one.
The only ones in the entirety of the show
probably.
Isn't allowed to do, but, you know,
all they got the chains.
All they were back here.
What's that coherent arse neighbourhood.
Yeah.
They're facing their arses
towards each other.
You give them.
Both bottles because they're facing
their arses towards each other.
I might be right.
And the how that works.
I don't know
I don't know.
The back of your shirts.
A staff
and a staff.
Are you just
you got to check in my pants for that.
Oh, it's impressive.
I seems kind of flaccid right now.
I think so.
Colour flaccid.
Is probably cause I'm around you.
All. You are your bitch. OK, goodbye.
Welcome back.
Fuck you. What the hell?
Get back here. I'll
you little bitch.
I see you.
You all right?
Oh, you finally decided to come
crawling back?
No, I decided. To come crawling back.
I just don't want to be alone.
Oh, boy.
You should shut the fuck up, Vox.
I just don't wanna be. All.
That fucking thing.
Don't look at me, dudes.
I'll look around you lot of people.
Oh, well, that was a close one.
Yeah, I would have been really bad,
especially after I said, Oh,
I think they figure. You did it. Yeah,
they figured it out.
I think they did it while I was trying
get back to the main place.
Yeah, that's.
Well, we decided to just fuck around
inside a cage for, like, 10 minutes.
They solve the puzzle
I guess we. Have our own little story.
OK? OK. Yeah,
it's like in the until dawn.
There were plans.
Although I did. Yeah, I've played.
I mean,
I don't think I've played it myself.
I think I watched somebody play it, like,
three years ago.
This is the right way.
I think it is. Yeah, it's familiar.
All this, I think, is the way back to the.
Scenes from me.
OK, Morgan Freeman
to the thing again.
I do believe
we've gone the wrong way, my boy.
Yeah, I think there's probably not
the Morgan Freeman.
Oh, I found it.
What's that one out of 75 young men
on this? Wait, wait.
Haven't we already been down this way?
We just come down here.
One out of two young men is a bottom.
I'm Morgan Freeman.
One out of 20.
Hello, hello. Hello.
All good thing neither of us are that one.
Artsy two, right?
We're like a statistical anomaly
or like an alley. Is
it's like that fucking thing
of, like, you know, about one in three
people are a bottom.
And we look at that.
We look at them either,
and they just stare.
We just look at the screen. Yeah.
And the in this case,
I just you to look at them.
Mm hmm. You know,
one and two people are bottoms.
I'm not a bottom.
I'm not a bomb either.
No, no, just don't look anywhere.
One and two. Mm
I couldn't even see your face.
It was, like,
obscured by the fucking shot.
No, no, the joke's ruined. Fuck
and we're actually the lost boys.
Well.
This is back at the.
No, this is the.
This is just one point. Yeah, what's.
I'll cabin in the woods.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm going.
So I'm going to I, you know, I feel like
like just ripping out a rotisserie chicken
right now.
I'm just, like, eating it with my bare
hands.
I like you being.
Like, the dude on that Australian
news thing where he's like,
yeah, you know, that creature
just kind of came out was like,
you know, can you eat it like that?
I wish I could.
Mr. Fox, you know, where he just sits down
to kind of fold his newspaper.
He's all dressed, all smart.
It's like, Darling,
this dinner looks fantastic.
And he just looks at he goes, Well,
has to, to shreds like that,
like an actual fox and goes,
and then he just kind of like.
Mops his mouth.
Oh, oh, nah, nah.
Our friends just die our Amaar
from my knee. Ron
loves my way the right way.
All this does
this do look like the bloody right way.
Oh, my goodness. Holy shit.
Harry, pull out all you fuck me.
Did they call me the Harry Potter?
Wait. Did you find Ike?
Do you know where I was?
I think I died.
I was with me, and then we got separated.
And then I opened this, and then.
Boom.
I was were.
Like. We.
I just found Volks, like, Nazi long ago.
Yeah, he just got.
So I guess I was the one that died. Yeah.
I think he'll be back soon.
We chill here.
We for the boys can wait here. I
ike. I think I see him coming home.
Oh, yeah, that is him. OK.
Let's go.
Oh, I'm so.
I looked away for a split second,
and you vanish.
Things like that.
So I guess I have the blessed child
of this game who aren't you.
A blessed child?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank God for our
and God for our ghost.
What is that achievement?
What was.
What treatment?
Did you. Get one? Is it green?
50 shades of green.
It's 50 Shades of Grey,
but it's starring Shrek.
Oh, boy.
I mean, are you doing in my boxer shorts?
Yeah, I are.
We got
I don't know, it looks like a swamp.
We might actually be on to a swamp.
I love Shrek. I love T-Rex. So much.
I had all of the DVDs. Oh.
I see.
Oh, there's another house.
Hello. Salem is a safe house.
It's another thing.
To point to leaf in Japanese.
Stick symbols
whispering to me on the phone.
Oh, my God, my poor head.
When I grabbed it, disintegrated
in my hands.
Oh. I have a question.
How did you guys solve the puzzle?
How do you solve the pesticide puzzle?
I wrote each puzzle down,
and then I figure with the
with each note, we're like,
which chemist and which chemist?
Which solution was in which.
You pulled. Out your notes for this?
Oh, my God, you're insane.
Yeah. Dude, I'm so proud of you.
I'm so proud of you.
All this was a job.
My phone.
I thought I was alone for
when I was warming up near the bonfire,
but that thing, it just ignored me.
Like I wasn't even there.
Guys, guys, guys, gather up, gather tape.
If you're reading
this, stay near fire or indoors.
Oh. Stay near fire indoors.
OK. OK.
Noted
guy died
because another guy set in his face
sitting on face down yeah.
When I was working up near the bonfire,
I stay near fire or indoors.
OK, that's. Why.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, this is Dr.. Franklin.
I'm Sergeant with the Hapsburg
Illinois Police Force.
At least they have a shifter
and coming me.
What time?
What about you?
Willing to bet that there's the plumbing.
Leaks that are somewhere, right?
Busting all bitches.
No bitches.
Nobody's and don't be near bitches
and you'll be OK.
What do you what do you guys want to do?
I think.
Do you want to you want to solve this one
and then call the night
after we solve this one?
Am I the only
one like, OK, so if you look at the grass
graphics and all the trees here, doesn't
this look like slender, the eight pages?
Oh, my. Oh,
my God. You're right. The tree.
Holy shit. You're right.
What a classic. Oh, my God.
Did you just give me a nostalgia?
Footsteps even sound similar.
All we need is the ambience,
like the boom, boom.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Boom.
Oh, my God.
Where are we going?
I wish I was talking my friends around.
My favourite guy, you know, Slender Man.
Would you fuck Slenderman?
Yes. Tentacles.
What is that kind of question?
I mean, he has. He has, he has.
He does have tentacles.
I know that's.
That's a pretty Bay State to be honest.
Yeah, he has multiple angles.
Oh, can we just jump over?
All we know, there's a gate here.
There was an entrance, right?
I thought I figured something
revolutionary.
This where we came from.
Yeah. This is he from. Oh, yeah.
We went around in circles.
Oops.
Jesus.
Well, hey,
you know, I thought I was on to something.
OK, come on, Isaiah.
Did we go here? Maybe down here.
There's another.
20. Anything.
This flashlight is kind of garbled.
Oh, yeah. OK, there's a bonfire.
Oh, the lantern.
Oh, I love this.
But I wish I would have been here
involuntary.
Oh, hell,
I computer does not like this dog.
I know, I know.
I'm flying around the campfire.
And senior campfire song.
Oh, see, I'm sorry. A song.
Oh, now, I was known
for how much it turned from SpongeBob.
I could just. Oh. Man.
Whoo ho.
Follow the ball.
For the bonfires.
All there's more. All your right.
There are more.
The whole of all
of all of all of the voting bonfire
there.
Well, this one's a. Lot more earthy.
Oh, no. It's this exact same because.
Because because
because one of our friends.
I just know, like, if there's a monster,
we have to stand by this.
Folks, just. Like our studio.
We're off to see the wizard
the wonderful Wizard of Oz.
That did not work.
I ain't seen no bonfires.
I hear an owl.
I hear a owl. Owl.
Friends
friends.
Although they are now lost for a second.
No, leave that for good luck.
What is that?
Fire.
I was at the monster.
All that's the monster. You
made was based off.
This is not the first play.
This might be the first one.
I'm oh, my God. Oh.
I think I heard the
creature come by.
I think I heard something, too.
But then I thought that was box.
Well, what was that noise? Oh.
An abandoned house.
This town is indoors.
I think it does count as indoors. Yeah.
So we could probably go inside here
and stay away from.
Going to the attic.
It says. A man. Attic.
This guy looks like some science
some sort of writer.
Keep. OK.
All this is a lie.
You know what I look like?
All these guys having sex.
He doesn't
this is like your father.
Father? Oh.
Is that a foetus?
What is your father's name?
Is it Spike Island?
No. This is, I believe, Popeye.
Yeah.
Pike's like.
Popeye. Popeye. That's cute.
Sure, son.
I can check inside the drawers
again.
I turn that shit off.
I'm not.
Yes. Turn around. Oh, my God.
The British guys turned down.
It's a rave.
It's a rave. Job.
For the people in the 1900s have raves.
There's a locked. Door
and they're very important.
To me. But I'm bad at it.
Every time it rains it rained as.
I vox. Surely. Good.
Yeah, I thought that was the actual radio.
I think. I think we were laughing.
Oh, that rain fell from heaven.
She'll be Irving.
She'll be Doobie.
A doctor that's on fire.
That's not funny Box.
Nothing.
And what happened was not box.
Something done no, no, wait. I was.
Singing. Oh.
Oh, that was a monster. OK.
I don't think.
No, I already opened everything in there.
Eat something.
We need to go outside. I don't get this.
God, I love the cake.
That was not any of us, that's for sure.
Sorry. I think I forgot.
I forgot a key.
Oh. No way. The one Jordan, Shaq.
Ozaki.
You just picked it up already.
I picked it up.
OK. Let's try it on one of the doors. Hmm.
Another door over there.
I might be the one for the upstairs.
Yeah.
Get him open this one.
Maybe the one upstairs.
Yeah, the one up here.
It's like we're playing.
I'll kill me if I open the door. Yeah.
It's like I only.
We we we we. Wee.
There's a lot of bearded man
yeah.
I'm washing me in my clothes.
What I.
There's a y. There's a bed.
And there's a bed.
I'm I'm just being an idiot.
Oh, got a bed.
I found a key, though.
You're very, like,
I don't know, enamoured by the bed.
It was. That sounds amazing.
I want to see one of those gifts,
which is that
which is it
just says bed jump scare. And it has.
I just kind of walking around
that a bed appears and it goes back.
So my God.
It's a very
crunchy bed, if you like, walk around it.
It sounds like you're.
Cleaning the grass. Sound effects. Yeah.
That's funny.
Why the hell is bathroom?
Kind of nasty?
You know, just
I I think this is just.
Basically hearing somebody breathing
like, oh.
No one.
No one should be coming inside this house.
I doubt it.
No, I think. Don't you have a key? Like.
Yeah, I do.
I think it's for the one downstairs. Wait.
Who turned out?
No, no, it would have been from the one up
here, right?
Who turned that turned on.
That was on. The first floor. Oh.
One second. Close.
The door is shut.
Shut, close.
Locked.
OK, this place is haunted.
Yeah. The surprise, the fucking nobody.
It's a horror game. Damn, son, speed up.
I mean, they. Run into a fucking
running block
in Samarra
from the ring in the forest. Man.
Where's is other door so bad?
This door.
That's the one.
Nice. You know.
Which one is it?
Oh, there's, like, spices
and and like, tinctures in there.
Oh, it's another locked door.
Wow. Amazing.
I found a key. Oh, you found it.
Oh, I'm happy for the store.
For this store.
Oh, no.
It must be for something else.
Really. The other door
that was locked on the first floor.
We're going to.
We're going to go back upstairs
or maybe this one back here.
I'm just going to say.
Ah, I think I heard something outside
the house.
I'm pretty sure it's, like.
Stuck in the box.
Yeah. Was that you?
Oh, yeah. I'm still upstairs.
The sound is confusing me.
I thought you guys were up.
Did you just hear that super loud noise?
Yeah, I saw someone else is. Yeah.
Something's outside the house right now.
Yeah, that was loud as heck.
I think it can't.
It can't come inside.
So did you try it on the door
down downstairs?
Like the house is like
the house is like a condom.
It can't really come inside, so.
Or any in the room. Oh.
These guys.
The boys.
Oh, this. One's a white new.
New room. Oh.
In here.
This room.
For a second,
I thought that because of the way.
The drawers.
Lock and the drawers, the phones,
it looked like he was bold.
And I thought that they were just
images in this house was just him
gradually losing his hair.
Oh, my God.
Oh, he's. Pissed. Already. Use
the key was was.
This was the room that I found was a key
that I found at this room.
There's other locked doors over here.
I tried already,
and none of the doors open.
The ghost really wants us, by the way.
Holy shit. All
right, fuck off.
Boom, boom.
Boom.
The doors just keep closing abruptly.
In front of us.
No, I think we already in this.
I see your dumb arse outside.
Use my key to someone to.
See your dumb arse walking around.
Only the person who picked it up
can use it.
Now, do you open the new
boom?
You open the new.
Room.
Where is this DMCA music?
I hope it's on.
No, I doubt it.
OK, now it's super old.
We should be good. OK, cool.
You have to
a bit.
Yeah.
Would you do this thing?
Yeah, at the birthday.
Mr President,
happy birthday to you.
I swear to you,
I think you guys use my key.
Don't even see my inventory.
I think you can.
Hello. Luckily, Tora Korea. Tora!
Tora!
You're out there.
Oh. They may suppress it in.
Oh, I think I see him.
Oh. Sorry.
I was yawning. I'm sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm very, very woozy at the moment.
The alcohol's getting so big.
I found a key.
Nice. OK, I'll close the door.
I think I'll feel now.
I can't even close the door.
I'll close the door. I tried.
You cannot close the door.
I got you upstairs.
Yeah. Oh,
which did you find where?
I found some sort of key.
I'm going to try it on the door again.
Dude. It keeps getting me.
Yeah. It works. Nice.
You guys heard that, right?
Yeah.
He's not a happy boy.
Oh, there it is.
Nice. OK.
OK, now we're just knocking, right?
There we go.
That's not Vox.
It's just the game, right?
The ghost. Or.
Yeah, ok.
OK. It's none of these doors.
So it has to be one of them downstairs.
I think it's the one on the first floor.
Yeah, that's the connecting door.
This one was really loud last time.
Yeah, this is the one. OK.
Oh, that's nasty.
That's kind of gross. OK,
but there's a key inside his mouth.
Oh, I use my key on this one.
He's like a. Wing.
He's like an when I got a key when
ok, I got a key.
I also.
I open the door, roll this door.
I open it with my key. Oh.
You cannot see shit in this.
Where am. I?
You know, each cloud contains, man.
There's room there, and she made me do
I think.
No, I just open.
If we have another. Key here
before I just.
Open the door.
It's connecting the kitchen to the side.
That's the thing.
I think there might be a
the key is probably for upstairs.
You're going to go back upstairs.
Upstairs to this house
has us going running around left
and right on the open the door. Yes.
Up, up, up, up, up.
Zap is using my collar.
Show you using my collar.
I said, why am I putting.
There's only three colours for all.
You guys heard that, right?
Yeah, I heard that.
It's locked.
Yeah.
That was.
What I. Thought. A key
for this one.
I I'm on my way home eventually.
Get out of this house.
Come for this.
Oh, shall we end it right now?
All right, guys, I got it.
All right. You're already in it.
I feel like a different icon,
like the unlock.
I was like, oh, I did it.
The store's open, too.
I did all the time.
Never mind all these doors
just, like, lead to this area. OK.
There's nothing in here. Dude.
Imagine we just like waiting.
Oh, the the books.
The books.
It's a puzzle for the books.
We need to go search
for the rest of the books in the house.
Yeah, like,
I just pulled out one of the books.
It must have unlocked something somewhere.
There might be another secret entrance.
Oh, up here. Up here. Attic. Attic.
Oh, door knob.
Oh, oh.
OK, now what's I was just say. Oh.
Everybody. Oh, yeah, I saw that.
I saw that.
I will need three.
African effigies made from wood to create
the hex for the crypt door in the story.
These two get back in.
Eventually,
these effigies should be hung up.
Somewhere in the forest,
I crafted a ceremonial dagger
to go with the final ritual.
I can use this to break the seal.
OK, I've seen one of those things out
in the woods.
Yeah, we saw one. Yeah, me too.
Yeah, I just grabbed one.
I think that was just, like, up here.
Right on.
Let me see how touching my inventory.
Mm hmm.
Mm Da da da da dum.
Oh, no, never mind that.
That was an effigy.
Do we have the axe?
Always. We're supposed to get the axe. Oh.
I guess we go out there and look for it.
Yeah.
OK. There's all this. OK.
I was going to say,
if this house had us, like,
fucking around and running around for,
like, nothing, I've been, like, the worst.
Oh, my God. This is a crusty Ben.
Yeah, it sounds like crushed up leaves,
like, you
all right, let's get out this house.
We're done here.
You're so green. Colour, bitch. Pink.
Wish this would shut up.
But I have to use the green colour.
FYI, in this right flick.
Whatever I ever brought all
ever.
Mom, you understand me?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's not. Fake. God.
How do we find our way back?
You put a lot of sticks.
I you were the only one that passed.
Yeah, you do.
I think we follow you
how are you?
Are you all right
to. The bonfire over. Here?
Well, I.
It's my decision making so bad.
I you sure you're not drunk, too?
Is this where we started?
Mm. No.
Different one.
Put a lot of glow sticks
at the first part,
and if you follow one of those, we'll
get to one of the
I think.
I think the monster is gone.
No, no.
I heard something breathing upfront. Oh.
You guys hear that, right?
Yeah, I hear it.
Yeah.
Because it's an effigy.
Oh, that was the effigy
that was making on the noises.
Oh, you broke.
You broke it.
I think we need to run
that was.
You didn't.
Oh. Oh, my God.
Oh, the foot.
I love that.
It gets shot, though, every single time.
Everybody shut up.
I need to listen.
Penis.
Like I'm not talking, sweetie.
Sweating.
Shut the fuck up.
So here's.
That.
Glass. That was just grass.
Oh, that's a no.
That's gas. Yeah.
Oh, my God.
We haven't gone outside in so long.
We can all recognisable.
I know. Oh, grass and so long.
Oh, guys. Morning.
Oh. Oh, is it this entrance?
Yeah, it might be.
Oh, we went back to the vacuole.
We actually went back to the entrance. How
what is that.
00 it's coming, it's coming.
Run to a bonfire, run inside
or to a bonfire a beast.
Follow me, follow me into the house.
We all get to the house.
Quickly
everyone to the confines of our houses.
Safe house what you do best, guys us
do what you do best.
Stay inside.
Dogs go.
Down.
I love that.
Every time we go in here,
we get Resident Evil, save music.
I mean. It's actually the safe.
It feels like the safe room music.
It's very reminiscence.
Here.
We can go back to the first one,
find that we didn't
find the the effigy that we find
that was on Facebook.
Yeah,
but how did we get
to the first bonfire from here?
You know, we just go to the right, like,
outside of the house.
I don't think we went from the backyard
to look from here.
Oh, we got run.
We got to run.
I get the fuck away.
I'm going back inside the house.
To the house.
I'm going back in the house.
I got usually he was like, very.
He's why we do not touch grass.
He's right behind
you. He's right behind you.
Oh, no, no, no.
Close the. Door.
Close the door. Closed your fucking forest
spirit.
Dude, you're kind of cool.
I can save him.
I can see. I still alive.
I got you. I got you.
Oh. No.
Why are you closing the door?
You fucking all like.
For us e to revive.
Like me.
Part of me thought that there wasn't
going to be an enemy on this map
because we didn't see anybody for so long.
I guess it just waited for us
to get to the attic.
This one.
Oh, my God.
The bonfire is outside.
We went to the right.
We're going hunting down by forest.
Spirit and type for spirit group.
I'm pretty
it's go time.
I mean.
We're here.
We're we.
In the.
Fruit.
I don't
even remember where the first bonfire is.
Oh, yeah?
You guys are making me yawn, you know?
And this. There's the first one fight.
Well, there's something.
Oh, ha ha. Ha.
OK, the one fight.
We're safe here, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It was so I. Can't see him.
I cannot see him. Either.
I can just hear
you walking.
I want to leave my glow sticks right here.
I know that.
Next month I think we lost.
I think we are lost. Is Brussels.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Oh, I'm
following you.
Like the look on
Soto's face, like his character
model looks so tired and horrified.
And he sat there going.
Oh, I'm just. Stretching.
I'm just stretching.
Rah, rah, rah, rah, rah, rah, bro.
And talking, like, an Indy girl idea.
What do you really think? Yeah,
I feel like, oh, one way.
I think that's a mistake.
He's a he's over there.
If you would just like to go over.
We just got to be better.
Watch this.
We're going to die.
No. Aren't you going back to the house?
Is this back to the house?
No, no, no. This is someplace different.
You know, this is a different area.
ALL Let's go this way.
Is this back to the house?
Oh, I see.
Ghost like.
I know. Every.
This. Oh, this is the aisle.
This is the other house. OK, so left.
OK, so what if we just continue down
this path?
Like we didn't go down here.
A bonfire. A bonfire? Oh.
Yeah. I'll put some
glow sticks down, too. Oh,
ok. I know how to use those.
The exam palace.
Yeah.
Now, do we are we here in effigy?
Anywhere?
I found one over here last time.
OK, all right.
Drop some sticks.
I'm on the way to the Sistine Chapel.
Effigy. Effigy? Yes.
All Parker's been pondering that one,
which is find the one more that we saw.
I mean, one more,
and then we're done. On the ground.
Yeah. Yeah, it.
Was the first one that we saw.
We found the other ones,
but we haven't seen the first one.
The first one.
Was it, like, near the house, maybe? Or.
OK, so when we found the first bonfire,
then we went to a second one
and from there, I dropped down glow sticks
on the entire way when I found it,
but I haven't been able
to, like, rediscover them.
All right, let's if we can go back
to, like, the big house,
you know, the one
we were finding all of the shit
that I reckon that will help us find
the other bonfires. The house.
That the original
our original haunted house
that we were gone through.
The house.
Where we found all the shit and the what.
Is this place
oh, is this a mausoleum or graveyard?
Yeah, this is a graveyard.
Graveyard mausoleum.
These not.
OK. Oh, what the fuck is this
one thinking?
The gates of hell.
Oh, maybe this is where we got to go.
The man, the myth, the legend.
This smoke.
That's Glowsticks.
Gone. It.
The flashlight is not doing me
any favours.
Lonnie ls.
Mm hmm. Okay,
here lies Baden together.
Why the fuck does that mean?
Zeke again?
Something about the difference
I can't tighten.
Oh, my God.
Oh, stop.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
I thought all I was removed.
Know that was me.
Sorry. So instead.
Of. Oh, my apologies to both of you, then.
Oh, my goodness.
Why not? Let's not talk about it.
Let's not.
I thought.
OK, ok. Not not. Don't look at me.
Look at me.
Leg here.
Let's go.
I know. I'll come back.
I'm sorry.
OK? This should be close by right.
Around this area.
I think we just got more far away. Really?
And if anybody can see anything,
because I sure as heck can.
I'm blind.
Free now.
Do it my way.
I mean, it's health centre.
Someone's to the right I.
All right.
Sounds like a sound.
I hear the sounds of off
is the purple on you.
Where did
It was nice knowing you all.
Coming after. Us.
Well well, tonight it's been.
It's been an honour.
It's been an honour serving.
Goodbye for you
I bucks
follow the classics to.
Follow the classics. Get the fuck out.
Oh, bonfire, bonfire, bonfire, bonfire.
We ha.
This is our Siebert circle fucker.
Get out of here.
Yeah, oh.
Oh, my God. We just need one more.
We already found it.
Please.
Just one more.
One more.
Please. Just.
My goodness.
I don't.
I don't know how to find it again.
Yeah, I really.
I really just want to find it,
and then that's it.
And then we dones off
but the question is, where the fuck is it?
Was it a.
Leading us to a haunted house?
That's the haunted house that.
I want to go back to.
The first bonfire we ever found
oh, you're kidding me.
Yeah. I think it's coming after me.
Oh, it is.
Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Circling us.
See? Bear, see, bear.
Ants.
Does this kind of thing go away?
My IQ inside this house right ike.
I'm sorry for being loud. I, i.
Are you in here? Ike?
Oh, he's out here.
I had a chat i think.
He went back to the original house.
Yeah.
It'd be a pick up box.
Mm hmm. Just him updated.
Oh, keep out the effigy. Oh, he found it.
He found it. Oh, dude. Well, now.
Where do we have to go
now? Do we? We got to the mausoleum.
The ritual I think we need.
Yeah, we need to go back to the cemetery.
Oh, oh, oh, whoa. Six.
I keep looking.
Over on.
Thank you so much for the raid.
Who raided? Hold on.
Somebody read it, and I didn't get to say
thank you for that.
Thank you so much for the raid.
Whoo hoo!
Who's here. Huh?
Best dish raid. Only guilty.
Thank you for the raid, dude.
Hello? Hello, Ike?
I found it.
I found it. I got it. I got it.
You got it. Nice.
We just got to get back to the house
now, right?
I was in it.
The ah, the mausoleum that we have to go
to, that's the thing that.
Was there, like a blade up there
that we needed again or something.
Or was it.
Was that what we needed? I don't know.
To the haunted house?
You won't go back to the haunted house,
right?
Well,
I thought there was still something there.
I is there.
I thought all we had to do
was just I grab something from there,
and then we read the book,
and then we got the outline.
You know, if we grab anything, OK,
maybe we need to go back then and to the
the cemetery or whatever
the heck it wants, right?
Yeah. The mausoleum. You know, the master.
Because there's a door that was sealed off
I think that's where it is.
Demon remove.
I was actually, like, in front of me,
but she didn't come back for some reason.
Hmm. Couldn't hear us
was he here?
Oh, no, that's fine.
Smocks, my hair.
Thank you so much for the radar
on the graveyard.
A great stream.
I'll come here. Just reviving afar.
I've never even seen that thing
very close up.
It looks like a deer.
I think.
Yeah.
And long arms.
We oh,
you're cute when you're young,
both of you.
Very adorable.
Oh, yeah.
That's.
That's how, like, you do it again.
Is it, son?
He's like.
Deep.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Now, that.
That was some Ranger
you're having.
We're having, like,
some kind of a commune.
Anyway, I like squeak battle
squeak off.
I hear reamer, like,
cutting in and out from the distance.
Yeah, the game does that.
The game does that.
Occasionally. You just had, like, a
yeah,
but. Oh.
What what happened?
What did you do?
What did she do?
All now. We're.
We're kids.
There it is.
Zoo were getting clamped by this.
Look at that here.
What is that?
Hello? Oh.
Oh, that hurt my stomach.
Oh, my God.
It's OK.
Can't touch us here.
He's like, dum dum dum dum dum dum.
You got a friend in me?
I guess we're going to go.
He's pretty far away.
Let's try to find the.
The cemetery or the mausoleum,
whatever the heck you call it.
The for and near miles.
And you're
she just did it for us.
I'm pretty sure
Raymond just did it for us.
Baby River. Oh, my God, Raymond.
We were just chilling.
And then suddenly,
where did you get to the next area?
Did you go to the mausoleum?
We got stuck.
The monster kept circling us.
Oh, my goodness.
I like it.
I think my heart
can take much more of this.
Yeah,
I think this is a good place to stop.
Yeah, this is a good place to stop.
To be honest, we did a lot today. Oh.
Oh, my God.
For a. While, it was a lot of fun.
Making
chicken complete
this game one of the day, though.
I'm really curious of the other chapters.
Yeah, I think.
Like Dame of Carrie at the end there.
Yeah, you carried us.
We couldn't go anywhere, so thank. You.
Yeah, we were surrounded by the big deer.
Bitch.
We just hanging out here?
Yeah.
He's deer. Bitch.
I don't like. That you
ok. OK.
Well, how do we exit this?
I don't know how you exit this arm.
Oh, go to sleep.
I don't think it's a safe lane.
It is. I'll go to lobby intended.
I think that's all.
Hello. Here we are.
There he go. Lobby.
Yeah, I think this is right.
You may go back to this court
just to say bye.
Yeah. Yeah, I can see that.
Hold on.
Let me put your guys's volumes
back to normal again.
Yeah, I remember to turn off,
like, your voice activity in the game.
Yeah. Push it out.
Push.
It's OK.
Hello?
Hello.
Oh, oh, oh.
There we go.
Oh, my goodness.
Whoo! Boy! How was something?
That was a lot. I do.
I don't know. How finnane on Lucca.
They did this in, like, six and seven.
They played this for 7 hours
or something like that.
Yeah, I would have guy and died.
They just they just, like,
continued on, like it the entire night
and, like, made it to the end somehow.
Built this. Friend. Yeah,
I could not do that.
Did they clear the whole game?
Yeah, they clear the whole game. Oh, wow.
Well, we have we're not going
to let ourselves be outdone.
Let's do this again
sometime. Yeah, definitely.
We can finish this.
And because we have two more chapters
left, right, it looks like two or three
more chapters off.
Yeah, I think it looks like it. Yeah.
If you look on the board. Yeah.
If we can look at the blade
through.
Three, more. Like.
Through productive voice.
Actually.
I take a look at it.
We can finish this
and in a second livestream yeah.
Yeah, for sure. We can have chapter four.
Look at that. Yeah,
we did literally. Yeah.
Next time we can like end this off
since there's only one seat.
Yeah,
there should be only six chapters, right?
Because yeah, it looks like
there's only room for six chapters. Hmm.
Chapter four. But
is it really long before you let me chat?
So I think we just finished this
in the, in the next collab.
I guess yeah.
Yeah.
Sounds good. Sounds like a plan. OK, yeah.
All right. Thank you guys for coming by.
It was really fun going to play with you
all again.
Yeah, it was something that wasn't,
you know, like we promised.
Oh, my God.
I remember that was like,
oh, let's do this again.
Just not, you know. Yeah.
Oh, thank you for inviting us.
It was really fun. Yeah.
Thank you for wanting to play.
It was really.
Yeah, I love that.
That was a lot of fun. Really. It was.
OK. I'll see you guys around.
Bye, guys.
Bye bye.
Take care.
OK, let's see
Gonna go back to the bedroom, guys.
So give me a second.
Oh, oh.
Oh. Well,
I guess saw the bedroom overlays.
Don't want to show off
for some reason. Unlucky.
What the heck, brah?
Yeah, they just don't want to show up
there.
All right,
And my music's not playing.
It's, like, up
rolling. OK.
Oh, we gotta play for a long time.
I'm really glad that everyone enjoyed
that.
Sorry, I wasn't talking or chat too much
because I did want to focus on the game
and some just, you know,
make sure that we were getting through
or, like, make sure that everybody was.
I was giving, like, my full attention
to the the game in the collapsible aisle.
We were through some of the donations
and stuff right now
because I didn't get to see that.
All of that while I'm
everything was everything was going down
because all the monsters, dude.
All the fucking monsters.
Oh, my God.
The Miyagi, they for the $3
carbon boxes for any of you
that really got your heart off
I like Alec.
Having those little moments were far in.
Not just with me both. Like I can remove.
It's really fun, right?
I think that's like a part of, like,
the appeal, that scheme.
When you do get separated, you're
kind of like forced to have a, you know.
Of a little.
Fun interaction with whoever
or what kind of buddy
you get some locked up with
you uniting you for the sub.
Oh, there's a lot of subsidy,
a lot of sobs.
Oh, my God.
Thank you for all the subs
and for all the new subsidised channel.
It's means a lot.
And again, only thank you for the be great
hope your stream was good.
Zoe, thank you for the talent.
You come back after you finish your exams.
Good luck on your exams and let's everyone
that's, you know, also gone through
exam week as well.
Kochel thank you for the bits and
the on the thank you for the bits as well.
Next time tonight was really fun.
I hope you have fun too.
I'm glad you guys enjoyed it.
Also Gil thank you for the five guest
subs on antelope.
Thank you for the 200 bits on the monthly
for the five zone gift songs and koala.
Thank you for the 1000 bits too.
Thank you. Thank you guys so much.
And Yuki thank you for the 1000 bits to
build up the paper.
Let me see I lost myself.
Did lose myself.
Lose yourself in the music moment.
Leon Heights, Leon Hart,
thank you for the.
Oh, no. Yes,
it was your birthday. Oh, happy birthday.
I didn't get to say happy birthday.
If you did say something last time.
My apologies, but, um.
Yeah, I hope you had a great birthday.
And so I thank you for coming by our yummy
thank you for the bits as well,
Linus.
Thank you for the 100 bits.
There's a lot of bits.
Oh, my God, Gail, thank you for another
five yourselves and love you.
Thank you for the get our bits as well.
In June, Herman,
thank you for the bits and file.
Yeah.
Thank you for the bits as well.
And Ernie, thank you for the deal.
Now, uh, you asked me to sing a song.
I don't think I can sing a song
now given how many voices
as we've been talking a lot.
But next time maybe
Hebner is and he wrote 5000
bits of noise I'll be having a great day,
Adam.
I thank you for the resolve.
And Buzzy,
thank you for the Zaino as well.
And just thank you for this.
And give yourselves off.
You're having a great day and have been
enjoying the stream and midnight.
Thank you for the 49 year
one gifts of Midnight Light
I'll know if you're still around.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much for all the gifts
I've been getting recently.
It's really sweet.
And Zion Nazi.
Thank you for the nine sirens as well.
And QED with Zeno
and I really thank you
for the teacher ones as well
good nights.
Yeah. Thank you guys for coming by.
It means a lot
and hope you enjoyed the collab with Vox.
I can remember.
Be sure to go support them
and follow their journals
if you haven't done so already. OK
go. Thank you for the gift sub.
And my god
papa I can't see you out. Name.
I can't see that name
mandy.
Thank you for the gifts for the five kids
loves.
OK and fearless.
Thank you for the $10 donation.
OK, tomorrow, guys, we are
gonna have another stream
because this week is our busy week.
Tomorrow we're going to be playing power.
We're playing tomorrow.
Stanley Parable. Right.
So reason why we re playing the game
is because we didn't get to finish.
We didn't get to finish the game last time
because we got cuts.
Looking forward to the collab. Again.
Now we got some last time.
We tried to play it because of like
a bunch of internet issues.
So hopefully this time
there's going to be no issues.
We try to play a game again.
Let's just hope it doesn't,
you know, mess itself up.
Also, ah ah ah ah.
Thank you.
For that's l know
the club was very interesting.
It was really fun.
I love getting to play with these guys
and I hope we get to play a different game
sometime in the future.
It's until I say hey,
thank you for the five year old gift subs.
I got it here yeah.
Pre manifest.
No Internet issues.
Please stream please
no more internet issues.
Excited for upcoming collabs
upcoming collabs.
Yeah.
So I think we're going to be playing
ah, we're going to be having our Valens
collab with SHU, Lily Picchu
and a few other people on on Friday.
Yeah, and on Saturday we're going to be
playing ah, Operation Tango with Yuuki.
So yeah, hope
you guys are excited for that because men.
Your next collab exclamation mark.
That's really fun.
You and Vox are really cute
I guess.
I guess he's OK or whatever.
I don't know.
I guess. I guess Vox is fine.
He's, he's, he's all right or whatever.
Yeah, he's all right.
OK, but yeah,
I look forward to the collabs this week.
Finally gets to play something off shoe.
And we've always wanted to play around
together because he's cracked.
I, I feel like I'm just a
mid is out with the kids.
So these days. Middleton whatever ends on
what else we're playing with
lily because me and Lily really wanted
to play us some stuff together, too.
Like the other,
it'd be a league or violence,
and she's inviting a couple other people,
too, so.
Yeah, we'll see. We'll see what happens.
And, ah, on Saturday,
it's going to be my first call.
I was lucky.
Yeah.
A lot of purple boys this week,
so that's really high.
Bright purple club.
Lots and lots of purple
polka. Lots of purple,
which is fine.
You know, I've been waiting for this
some day.
I got to get,
you know, Celine Boogie and shoe together
for one, like for person collab.
So it's just all, you know, for purple.
OK, go live for Sunset right now.
So I'm going play an ad break,
but for people for a news here,
be sure to follow our discord.
Janel Joyner, Joyner
Discord, discord, tragedy slash total.
And that's where I'll post announcements
I might go live next time.
If you're a subscriber to the channel
or on YouTube, you'll get additional
perks on us
sneak peeks and such like that.
And also follow me on Twitter.
We're almost at 500 K on Twitter and also.
We're all.
We've already hit like 400 K on YouTube.
So thank you again for that big milestone.
Appreciate it, guys.
Been growing a lot lately and
I really hope that we can keep this up.
I'm going to. Upload a video later.
Today on YouTube. It's really good.
Please
keep your eyes out for the new upload.
OK, like, oh my.
It's, it's some highlights
from the overcooked collab.
They have a box,
so I think you guys would like it.
It's really, it's really fucking cool.
So yeah, I'll upload that later today
like in about 6 hours.
So keep an eye out for that. Purple Heart.
Arts.
Purple Hearts.
Hearts. Purple Hearts.
All right, let me go
play an ad and I'll look for a song.
OK, Barbie,
OK, who's around.
All gossip to belong gossip.
The Nana are cute.
Oh, yeah.
Mm mm mm.
I'll send
Margate.
They're gonna the nugget gone.
I think we can go and read who?
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Now, a lot of people are alive
at the moment.
I could just look around.
The tributes are maybe on
Polly's still alive.
I mean, you can go read Polly again,
but we are afraid of Polly recently.
Jamie Foxx
yeah. Let me look around.
Let's see,
who can we go and share some love with
I i-i-i-i-i.
I'm hot, hot, hot, hot.
You're so cute. I love you.
I love you guys. Yeah,
I guess they beg for a second.
I like a one big
some people like one big deal.
Not, you know, that that way, but,
you know,
I mean, we're big, OK?
I don't see.
And everybody.
No, I'm
an all white.
You know what I think
I think we're just going to go and ride
actually, Louise live.
I don't think we've rated Lumi in a while.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's all.
Let's read Lumi.
Momo is also live. Fuck.
Oh, there's only two options.
OK, ok.
You know what? I'm just going to slide.
Eeny, meeny, my name.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Let's read Momo.
Go, go read Momo.
I think they all be nice to check them
out there.
They're an artist.
They draw really cute boys
and really cute girls.
You guys like you boys and girls, right?
OK, have a good night, guys.
Sleep well and take care.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And thank you
for coming by to the collaboration.
Be sure to support my friends as well
on their respective YouTube channels.
They're wonderful people and it's
always a pleasure to play with them.
Cute puppy. Tilda
may I get a happy birthday from you.
Thank you.
Him there's it's your birthday.
Happy birthday.
Do to have birthday.
Happy birthday. To you.
You know happy birthday. Man.
Thank you so much for,
you know, always supporting the general.
And we have a great one.
Take care. OK.
None of that.
That's OK. Let's go.
Good night, guys. Bye bye.
See you next time. OK.
Love. I.