Maybe也许
I just.我只是。
Take my headphones off.摘下我的耳机。
On. Give me a second在。 你稍等一会儿
Hey, guys.大家好。
Good morning.早上好。
I actually woke up我真的醒了，今天很早就醒了一次。
and woke up pretty early today for once.
That's kind of surprising.这有点令人惊讶。
I didn't think I would wake up so.我没想到我会这样醒来。
Early today for a stream,
but I don't know.今天为直播早起，但我不知道。
I think I just had
I had a lot on my mind also.我想我刚刚也有很多想法。
Oh, yeah.哦耶。
Does the这个
does the microphone sound OK?麦克风声音好吗？
I think some good.我觉得有些好。
So I sound fine.所以我听起来不错。
So I sound OK.所以我听起来不错。
I don't know, because I just hooked it up,
so I'm not sure if it's like我不知道，因为我只是把它连接起来，所以我不确定它是否像
it's all good, like last time.一切都很好，就像上次一样。
Sounds great. OK.听起来很棒。 好的。
Nice.好的。
Oh, sorry.哦对不起。
I was. What's it called?emm。 这叫什么？
We can get a lot of time necessary
to talk after the stream, but I was so我们可以在直播后有很多必要的时间交谈，但我是如此
so tired after the collab.两场合作后我好累。
I just wanted to hop off and go,我只想跳下车走。
like, relax and eat some food.像放松，吃点东西。
So yeah, it was a lot of chaos and所以，是的，这是很多混乱和
very hectic and all over the place,
but I had so much fun.忙碌，到处都是，但我玩得很开心。
So thank you guys for coming
by and supporting both of us.所以感谢你们的光临和支持我们俩。
Did I sleep well?我睡得好吗？
Yeah, I did sleep well.是的，我确实睡得很好。
I think I slept pretty early tonight too,我想我今晚也睡得很早，
but I only got like 7 hours, but yeah.但我只有7个小时，但是是的。
Yeah,是的，
it wasn't that. Much sleep, but I.不是那样的。 睡了很多，但我。
Still like.还是喜欢。
I feel super refreshed, like more
so than usual.我感觉超级神清气爽，比平时更加​​神清气爽。
So that's kind of crazy.所以这有点疯狂。
Hi, guys. Good morning.嗨，大家好。 早上好。
Welcome, everybody.欢迎大家。
Ah, good.啊好。
Good evening.晚上好。
Yeah, good evening to some of you guys
because it's like,是的，你们中的一些人晚上好，因为它就像，
I know it's Night-Time
for quite a few of you right now, right?我知道现在对你们中的很多人来说是夜间时间，对吧？
Yeah.是的。
Also, I.还有，我。
Did want to say.确实想说。
We did.我们做到了。
Hit 300 K on the on twitch.在 twitch开关上达到 300 K。
Like not too long ago. I think we hit it.就像不久前一样。 我想我们成功了。
Within one before stream started.在直播开始之前的一个内。
Or maybe yesterday. I don't know.或者也许是昨天。 我不知道。
I just took a look.我只是看了看。
Right now
because people are talking about it现在因为人们都在谈论它，我想，哇，我们已经有 300k 人了。
and I was like,Wow, we're already at 300 here.
So that's crazy.所以这很疯狂。
And bronzer 400 on Twitter too.Twitter 上还有 400。
So guys, that's fucking insane.所以，伙计们，这太他妈疯狂了。
I mean, it's rigging.我的意思是，它真的。
That's like almost half a million.这几乎是一百万。
And that's like really those are really
big numbers and they don't这就像真的那些非常大的数字，他们没有
it's it's scary.可怕。
It's, it's awesome.就是，太棒了
But, you know, it's also scary.但是，你知道，这也很可怕。
But I know you guys understand, right?但我知道你们明白，对吧？
Because it's like, it's a lot因为它就像是很多人，但我总是很高兴结识新朋友。 所以
it's a lot of people, butI'm always excited to meet new people. So
I'll tell them, you guildies, I welcome
you with my open arms我会告诉他们，你们这些公会，我张开双臂欢迎你们，希望你们在这里度过愉快的时光
and hope you're having a wonderful timeseeing here
congratulations. Thank you.祝贺。 谢谢你。
Thank you, guys.谢谢你们。
Thank you so much.非常感谢。
That being said, I think.话虽如此，我认为。
I will have a. Karaoke.我会有一个。 卡拉OK。
Celebration next week to say下周的庆祝活动要感谢大家，你知道，
thank you to everybody for, you know,
just for all the support recently只是为了最近的所有支持
and the fact that I haven't had
a, you know, karaoke in a while.而且我有一段时间没有唱卡拉OK了。
I wanted to sing a song.我想唱一首歌。
No, not just a song.不，不仅仅是一首歌。
I'll just sing many songs我只会唱很多歌
next time we had a karaoke session.下次我们有卡拉OK会议。
So I think.所以我认为。
You can expect one probably be你可以期待一个可能是
next week and around like.下周左右就好了。
Friday.星期五。
Let's say maybe Friday or Saturday.假设可能是星期五或星期六。
Yeah. Mm hmm.是的。 嗯嗯。
So excited.好激动。
Me too. Dude, I'm so excited.我也是。 哥们，我好激动。
It's been a while
since we've gone to sing anything.我们已经有一段时间没有去唱歌了。
I really wanted to, you know,我真的很想，你知道，
I've even I've had, like, the what's it
the motivation to sing again recently.我什至有过，比如，最近再次唱歌的动机是什么。
So that's I've been just, like,
trying out different songs and stuff, but,所以这就是我一直在尝试不同的歌曲和东西，但是，
yeah, I want to是的，我想
I want to do karaoke since we haven't done
one, you know, a bit.我想做卡拉OK，因为我们还没有做过，你知道的，有点。
And everybody's been doing.而且每个人都在做。
Karaoke lately, so it's been kind of
inspiring me to also do some karaoke too.最近卡拉OK，所以我也去唱卡拉OK，这有点启发我。
Right.对。
Oh, yeah, right.哦，是的，对。
Did you guys want to.你们想不想。
Did you guys want to guess?你们想猜吗？
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
If you're so weird.如果你这么奇怪。
Going back for, like,
was it kissing the ear on the microphone?回头看看，是不是在麦克风上亲吻耳朵？
I'm still trying to get used to it, but.我还在努力适应它，但是。
Uh. I'll get there eventually.呃。 我最终会到达那里。
Like, one of these days,
it'll feel a natural, and, you know,就像，在这些日子里，它会感觉很自然，而且，你知道，
you'll feel good.你会感觉很好。
Yeah, you'll feel really good.是的，你会感觉很好。
Like, it's right if you're not good, but就像，如果你不好，那是对的，但你会感觉对，我做得对。
you'll feel right and I'm doing itcorrectly.
That's why. That's when I'm nervous.因此。 那是我紧张的时候。
Because Not feel.因为感觉不到。
Good. Yeah.好的。 是的。
That's the wrong word.那是错误的词。
That's the wrong word to use.那是错误的词。
Okay, hold on.好的坚持住。
Let me give another kiss.让我再给你一个吻。
To OK,拿，
But hopefully everyone's
been having a great weekend so far.但希望到目前为止，每个人都度过了一个愉快的周末。
I have a lot.我有很多。
To do today and tomorrow.今天和明天要做。
So your boys can be quite busy.所以你的孩子们可能会很忙。
Um. Could you write?嗯。 你能写吗？
Let me read
through some. Of the donations.让我通读一些。 的捐款。
Thank you for the little 500, by the way.顺便说一句，谢谢你的 500。
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
I'll see you guys in a lot of
you might have我会看到你们很多人可能有一些新的，新的子，因为有很多给予一些。
had some new, new subbecause there was a lot of give some.
Yes, very. Again, big.是的，非常。 又是大。
Thank you to consider and give notice
for all the gift subs.感谢您考虑并通知所有礼品订阅。
From yesterday.
It means a lot, guys. Really从昨天。 这意味着很多，伙计们。 真的
Eve, thank you for the deal. No,夏娃，谢谢你的捐赠。 不，
Akari, thank you for the bids.Akari，谢谢你的比特。
Thank you, Kate. Congrats. Thank you.谢谢你，凯特。 恭喜。 谢谢你。
Thank you for the congratulations
to see Sadie.谢谢你见到萨迪的祝贺。
Thank you for the five months, five months
since one feels like just yesterday谢谢你的五个月，五个月以来，当我发现你因为太平间助理而疑惑时，感觉就像昨天一样。
when I found you wonderingbecause of mortuary assistant.
I'm glad to know that you've been.我很高兴知道你一直在。
Around for that long zero你知道，从五个月前开始，你一直在享受我的同意。
it and you've been enjoying my consentsince, you know, five months ago.
That's almost half a year.也就是将近半年。
Have you been having fun?你玩得开心吗？
It's been fun, right?很有趣，对吧？
Also, just thank you for the 10,000
bits as well.另外，还要感谢您提供的 10,000 位。
Just thank you for the 10,000. Oh, my God.只是感谢你的10,000。 我的天啊。
Hope you're having a great day too.希望你也有一个美好的一天。
Good morning.早上好。
And Kimura, thank you for the Jono
Pavi thing for the eight months.还有木村，谢谢你八个月以来的 Jono Pavi 事情。
Dear Linh, thank you for the dono
and the 10th year and give subs亲爱的 Linh，感谢您的捐赠和第
around thing for the donation as well.10 的捐赠，也感谢您的捐赠。
Shuttle. Woof, woof,穿梭。 呜呜呜
woof, woof.呜呜呜
Thank you for the donation.感谢您的捐赠。
Best part of every day is hearing
your voice.每天最好的部分就是听到你的声音。
My exact anxiety would break down
disappear in the short period of time我的确切焦虑会在短时间内消失
or two.或两个。
Or really.或者真的。
That's so sweet.那太甜了。
I'm glad.我很高兴。
I don't know. It's just like.我不知道。 就像。
I guess I understand
because there are like some things I do我想我明白了，因为我会做一些事情，你知道的，放松一下，从漫长而艰难的一天中消除焦虑。
to, you know, relax and just take awaythe anxiety from a long, hard day.
But I could never imagine, like,
my voice or, like, just me talking但我永远无法想象，比如，我的声音，或者，比如，只是我在说话
or just me being here and talking to you
guys would be enough to help that much.或者只有我在这里和你们交谈就足够了。
It's like它像是
it's really cool to know, like,知道真的很酷，比如，
I don't know, just my presence我不知道，只是我的存在或我这样做对你们有治疗作用，
or me doingthis has a healing effect on you guys,
and it just makes me feel so much better
about myself.它只是让我对自己感觉好多了。
And makes me feel so much better about,
you know, doing what I'm doing right now.你知道，做我现在正在做的事情让我感觉好多了。
So thank you. Really?所以谢谢。 真的吗？
I don't.我不。
I don't get to hear that enough from,
like, anybody.我从任何人那里听到的都不够多。
So thank you.所以谢谢。
So I feel like the.所以我觉得。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
Give me a.给我一个。
Second.第二。
Like, this might be too high.就像，这可能太高了。
I'll bring it down lower.我会降低它。
It might be better.可能会更好。
Yeah.是的。
That's good enough.这已经足够好了。
OK. OK.好的。 好的。
Oh, wait.等一下。
Is the music still on?音乐还在吗？
I just realised. Oh, my God.我才意识到。 我的天啊。
I just realised the music was still on.我才发现音乐还在。
Holy shit.天啊。
I guess I took off my headphones.我想我摘下了耳机。
I forgot my Spotify was open.我忘了我的 Spotify 是打开的。
So I just let my Spotify keep going.所以我只是让我的 Spotify 继续运行。
On and all.开和所有。
Until somebody in chat told me like,
Oh, it's still on.直到聊天中有人告诉我，哦，它还在。
OK, thank you for telling me.好的，谢谢你告诉我。
Oh my God. OK,我的天啊。 好的，
I appreciated Hopefully we don't get our我很感激 希望我们没有得到我们的
I don't get TMZ from that. Hmm.我没有从中得到 TMZ。 唔。
OK, all right.好的没问题。
So is everything good now?那么现在一切都好吗？
And he's fine.他很好。
You guys can hear me.你们可以听到我的声音。
It's just me and you.只有我和你。
There's no music now. Right.现在没有音乐了。 对。
I think this is better OK.我认为这更好。
Oh. Sorry.哦。 对不起。
Excuse me.打扰一下。
That's like, hold back a sneeze.这就像，忍住一个喷嚏。
As hold it back because, like,阻止它，因为，就像，
I don't know, like, sneeze into your ears
or whatever.我不知道，比如，对着你的耳朵打喷嚏或其他什么。
That sounds really gross and loud
appearing对于二比一的礼物潜艇，这听起来真的很恶心而且很响亮。 和
under youfor the two to one gift subs. And
anything for the five to one.五对一的任何东西。
I guess I'm still interviewing
for the Don on Anthony.我想我还在为安东尼面试唐。
Thank you for that tone. Yeah.谢谢你的语气。 是的。
Could you close your eyes
so I can kiss you on your face?你能闭上眼睛，让我亲吻你的脸吗？
I mean, if you want to.我的意思是，如果你愿意的话。
OK, come dark.好吧，黑点来吧。
Come here then.那你过来吧。
I. I guess一、我猜
Did you do it yet?你做了吗？
Did you.你是否。
Hello? Did you.你好？ 你是否。
Did you do it你做了吗
I'm sorry.对不起。
I guess you. Did it我猜你。 做到了
Also, Gracie, you are not.另外，格雷西，你不是。
Allowed to dono our dude.允许捐赠我们的家伙。
My mods are like the last people I feel
like should be donating to me right now.我的模组就像我觉得现在应该捐赠给我的最后一个人。
But I got it.但我明白了。
Congrats on three, bro.恭喜三哥
Today marks one year
since I first followed you.今天是我第一次关注你的一周年。
Thank you for your smiles,
loss, and good times.谢谢你的微笑、失落和美好时光。
I appreciate you beyond words.我对你的感激之情溢于言表。
I'm so glad to have found this community.我很高兴找到了这个社区。
One treat yourself. I will.一个对待自己。 我会。
Oh, God.天啊。
Guys, mods.伙计们。
You can't do this. Roll你不能这样做。
You can just你可以
do so much.
You don't need to give anything.做这么多。 你不需要给任何东西。
If anything, I feel like I should be
giving to you guys because you guys keep.如果有的话，我觉得我应该给你们，因为你们保留。
You know,
you help out so much in the back,你知道，你在后面帮了很多忙，
during the streams,
and, like, for the server.在直播期间，并且像服务器一样。
I guess you shouldn't be doing that.我想你不应该那样做。
For real.真的。
But thank you so much for the downloads.但是非常感谢您的下载。
It means a lot. Just please.那意义重大。
You. It make me feel better if you use.请你， 用这笔钱好好招待自己。
This money to, like, treat yourself让我感觉更好。如果有的话，就像对待自己而不是我对待自己一样。
rather than me to myself, if anything.
So please. Just No more.所以，请。 别再做更多了。
No more of that. All right?好吗？
And that goes for each
and every one of my months.这适用于我的每个月。
Like, I'm watching you guys.比如，我在看着你们。
Ash, thank you for the donation.阿什，谢谢你的捐赠。
Congrats on the work you've been doing.祝贺你一直在做的工作。
So long,
given so much support to the guilties,这么久以来，对fans们给予了如此多的支持，你绝对值得这么多的爱。
you absolutely deserve so much love.
Hope you have a good time in a weekend.希望你在周末过得愉快。
I will have a great weekend.我将度过一个愉快的周末。
Thank you, guys.谢谢你们。
And I also have a great stream.我也有一个很棒的直播。
Oh. All right, well, um,哦。 好吧，嗯，
I did a.我做了一个。
I did have some prompts written up.我确实写了一些提示。
Not a lot.不是很多。
I might repeat one of the problems
from last time, too, because I felt like,我也可能会重复上次的一个问题，因为我觉得，你知道，这是一个很好的提示，而且超级安慰。
you know, it was such a good promptand it was, like, super comforting.
So I thought,
why not? I'll take a, like, a,所以我想，为什么不呢？ 我会拿一个，像，一个，
I'll do a redo of it我会重做它或喜欢它，你知道的，再试一次。
or like, you know, just try it again.
With more effort这次更加努力，因为我现在有点自信了。
this time since I'm, like,a little bit more confident now.
I don't know. Right.我不知道。 对。
I have one prompts here.我这里有一个提示。
That's like,就像，
Oh, I just got home from work
and you're worried about me哦，我刚下班回家，你很担心我
and we're about to cuddle
or something like that.我们即将拥抱或类似的事情。
And then there's another one that's.然后还有另一个。
I, I don't think.我，我不认为。
I want to do this one because, like,
I was writing it last night我想做这个，因为，就像，我昨晚睡前写的，我有点困
before I went to bed,and I was kind of sleepy
The thing about this prompt
is that it has.关于这个提示的事情是它有。
It's like sub dog boy.这就像子狗男孩。
Um, and I call you master嗯，我叫你主人
and I don't think I want to do that.我不认为我想这样做。
Just for.只为。
How about this? How this这个怎么样？ 这怎么
if if somebody如果有人
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
I know if somebody. Gives 50 subs.我知道如果有人。 提供 50 个潜艇。
I'll. I'll do that.患病的。 我去做。
The the dog.那条狗。
Boy one bite男孩一口
a little later.一会儿。
Yeah, I'll do a little later.是的，我稍后会做。
It's just.这只是。
Really, I don't know.我真的不知道。
It's like when I write these late
at night, it's,就像我在深夜写这些的时候，
I don't realise it's like when you draw
or when you do work at Night-Time, right.我不知道这就像你画画或在夜间工作时一样，对吧。
And you wake up the next day
and then you look at it or like然后你第二天醒来然后你看它或喜欢它
one more time you look at it one more time
and you're like wait this is a mistake.再看一次，你会觉得这是一个错误。
I shouldn't have done this or like,
oh, this looks so bad.我不应该这样做或喜欢，哦，这看起来很糟糕。
Or like, you know,或者像，你知道，
you kind of like pull back
and want to like fix it, but你有点喜欢退缩并想修复它，但是
Yeah, but I feel about this one right now.是的，但我现在对这个有感觉。
I have another one
that's kind of like Gouda inspired我还有一个有点像豪达启发的
because, like,
she did this on her steam one time.因为，就像，她曾经在她的蒸汽上做过这件事。
It was like some kind of Cinderella thing.这就像某种灰姑娘的东西。
So I thought, should not be fun.所以我想，应该不好玩。
Yeah.是的。
Never a mistake.永远不会出错。
What do you mean,你是什​​么意思，
it's just super, and.它只是超级，而且。
It's really, really embarrassing, dude.真的，真的很尴尬，伙计。
Like,像，
it's.它的。
There's so much here that I feel like.这里有很多我喜欢的东西。
Oh, it's.哦，是的。
It's so embarrassing.这太尴尬了。
I only ever get even stomach
doing this one.我只做过这个。
Even even if I did reach that goal.即使我确实达到了那个目标。
Okay, I'm going to.好的，我要去。
I'm going to. I'm我要去。 我是的。
yeah.
We'll all look back. On that later,
though.我们都会回头看。 不过，稍后再说。
We'll look back on that later.我们稍后再回顾一下。
Maybe I'll feel okay about it.也许我会觉得没事。
Oh, Mitzi, thank you for the five.哦，Mitzi，谢谢你的五个。
Thank you for the 50.谢谢你的50。
Congrats on the educate.恭喜受教。
You deserve every single number
and more. The shrooms.你应该得到每一个数字和更多。 蘑菇。
Also the perfect time for me.也是我的最佳时机。
Shelia, since it's almost 11 p.m..Shelia，因为已经快晚上 11 点了。
Here, I'm glad I get.在这里，我很高兴我得到了。
To do these kinds of things for everybody
when they're, you know, about当每个人，你知道，即将在世界的另一端睡觉时，为他们做这些事情。
to sleep in the other side of the world.
Since I do feel like, you know, for the
past year plus, I've only been ever been因为我确实觉得，你知道，在过去的一年里，我只去过
streaming直播媒体
for, like, one time zone.例如，一个时区。
So getting to, you know, to a little bit
more for other time zones is nice.所以，你知道，对于其他时区多一点是很好的。
Alright, thank you for the donations
and thank you for your content.好的，谢谢你的捐赠，谢谢你的内容。
Thank you for existing感谢您的存在
also.还。
Thank you for the donations Hill. OK,感谢希尔的捐赠。 好的，
are you kidding me?你在跟我开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding me?你在跟我开玩笑吗？
Guys, guys,伙计们，伙计们，
well,好，
guys,伙计们，
oh, my God.我的天啊。
Both of you.你们俩。
Both of you like.你们两个都喜欢。
OK, I guess我觉得可以吧
Oh, see, I didn't think of it.哦，看，我没想到。
Of course it's course hidden.当然，它当然是隐藏的。
Or is it do it tell. And look here.或者它告诉它。 看看这里。
Thank you both for.谢谢你们俩。
50 from each of you.你们每个人50个。
OK, fine. I'll do it.好的。 我会做的。
I'll do it.我会做的。
I'll just我只
call and let me just put it back
in the document real quick打电话让我快速把它放回文档中
because I got rid of it因为我摆脱了它
because I was so
sure I wasn't going to do that one. But.因为我非常确定我不会那样做。 但。
All right.好的。
No, you guys prove me wrong不，每次你们证明我在任何事情上都错了，你们就证明我错了。
every time you guys prove mewrong on anything.
You for the five artsy ones as well. OK,你也为五个艺术的。 好的，
Well down, guys.好吧，伙计们。
God damn该死的
I don't know what it is我不知道让每个人都生气的狗男孩是什么，
about the dog boythat gets everyone riled up,
but ok, I'll try my best
when we get there.但是好的，当我们到达那里时，我会尽力而为。
All right.好的。
Just do it now.现在就做吧。
You guys just want me to do it now
so I could get out of the way.你们只是想让我现在就这样做，这样我就可以让开。
It's like ripping off a bandage, right?这就像扯掉绷带一样，对吧？
It's like when you rip off a bandage.就像你撕下绷带一样。
It's my as well,
so I don't have to, like, do it later.这也是我的，所以我不必像以后那样做。
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
OK. Through the ears.好的。 通过耳朵。
Jesus.耶稣。
Puppy.小狗。
Yeah, puppy. It's puppy.对，小狗。 它是小狗。
OK, I got a dog into the puppy mindset
right now.好的，我现在让一只狗进入小狗的心态。
Yes, I can我可以
I am dog.我是狗。
I am talking and talking and talking
like Oh.我说啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
Oh, oh, oh.哦哦哦。
But I agree to this.但我同意这一点。
What compelled me to do this,
I don't know.是什么迫使我这样做，我不知道。
See, this is.看，这是。
I don't. Trust.我不。 相信。
I don't trust. One.我不相信。 一。
A thought shop or two to do like a proper
job at, you know, thinking properly.一个或两个思想商店做一个像样的工作，你知道，正确地思考。
OK, let's just get into it.好的，让我们开始吧。
Hey. Hey, master.嘿。 嘿，主人。
Hey. Master.嘿。 掌握。
Well, plus, hmm.嗯，另外，嗯。
Hey, master.嘿，主人。
Hey, son, wake up.嘿，儿子，醒醒吧。
Come on, get up.来吧，起来吧。
Master. Hmm?掌握。 唔？
Oh. My sir.哦。 我的先生。
Can we go walkies?我们可以步行吗？
Come on.来吧。
I know you're awake.我知道你醒了。
Get up.起床。
Don't ignore me.不要不理我。
I see you smiling, too.我也看到你在笑。
Hmm. Fine.唔。 美好的。
Yeah. Oh.是的。 哦。
I master主人
to that.到那个。
Get you up让你起来
Come on.来吧。
Hurry and get out of bed.快点下床。
Oh, come on.哦，来吧。
Get up, please.请起来。
Get up.起床。
wolf, wolf（狗叫）
Did you sleep well, master?主人睡得好吗？
Are you going to make me breakfast?你要给我做早餐吗？
Are we going for a walky?我们要去散步吗？
Today too?今天也是？
please请
Can I maybe get a head pat, too?我也可以拍拍头吗？
Please.请。
Just.只是。
Just one.只有一个。
Head pat拍拍头。
OK. Maybe a hug too.好的。 也许也是一个拥抱。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
OK. OK.好的。 好的。
OK. Maybe.好的。 也许。
Can I get some kisses too?我也可以亲一下吗？
And some还有一些
cuddles? Hmm.拥抱？ 唔。
Hmm. Please.唔。 请。
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm.唔。 唔。 唔。
Hmm. Hmm.唔。 唔。
You will你会
Uh. Uh.呃。 呃。
Uh hmm.嗯嗯。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm. Hmm hmm. Hmm.嗯嗯。 嗯嗯。 唔。
Thank you.谢谢你。
I love you so, so much.我是如此爱你。
Mm You make me so happy.嗯，你让我很开心。
So soft and warm.如此柔软和温暖。
I love how you smile till.我喜欢你一直笑到的样子。
Right.对。
You feel so good till.你感觉很好，直到。
Thank you for taking care of me.谢谢你照顾我。
And thank you for loving me. Till谢谢你爱我。 直到
I'm your puppy.我是你的小狗。
I'm your good boy.我是你的好孩子。
You'll call me good boy, right?你会叫我好孩子，对吧？
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Do you like it when I kiss you like that?你喜欢我这样吻你吗？
Tell me one more再告诉我一个
Can you.你可以吗。
Can you call me a good boy till.你能称我为好孩子吗？
I do it?我做吗？
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Hmm, hmm, hmm.嗯，嗯，嗯。
Hmm. Hmm, hmm.唔。 嗯，嗯。
Hmm hmm嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Hmm Oh.嗯哦。
Oh. And my哦。 和我的
am I doing good?我做得好吗？
Master掌握
love, love.爱，爱。
OK, I did what you asked.好的，我按照你的要求做了。
Now, can we go on walkies?现在，我们可以继续步行吗？
Please, please, please.请，请，请。
Please.请。
Walkies, please.步行者，请。
Hmm. Hmm.唔。 唔。
Thank you.谢谢你。
Thank you, master.谢谢楼主。
Let's go.我们走吧。
I'll even put a collar on this time.这次我什至会戴上项圈。
If if you want如果你想
huh? No, it's
not like I wanted you to put it on me.嗯？ 不，我不是想让你戴在我身上。
Shut up.住口。
Let's just go. OK,我们走吧。 好的，
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
I'm done. I'm done.我做完。 我做完。
I'm done. I'm done. OK.我做完。 我做完。 好的。
OK, it's done.好的，完成了。
I finished it.我完成了。
God fucking damn.该死的
Like my heart with all my heart.全心全意地喜欢我的心。
I was like I was digging.我就像在挖掘一样。
My fingers into my leg
this entire time I was doing that.在我这样做的整个过程中，我的手指都在我的腿上。
Jesus. Oh.耶稣。 哦。
Oh, my God, bro.哦，天哪，兄弟。
Oh, I, I.哦，我，我。
I'm so sorry.我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry. Or you're welcome.我很抱歉。 或者你不客气。
I don't know what to say.我不知道要说什么。
I don't know what to say to that.我不知道该说什么。
What the fuck did I do? Huh?我他妈做了什么？ 嗯？
What the fuck was that?那是什么鬼？
What?什么？
What did I do, guys?我做了什么，伙计们？
What did I just do?我刚刚做了什么？
I don't know what I did.我不知道我做了什么。
I'm so sorry.我很抱歉。
Aw, you're welcome.哦，不客气。
I don't know. I don't know.我不知道。 我不知道。
Here is your Selby.这是你的塞尔比。
Selby dog boy, puppy boy content, whatever塞尔比狗男孩，小狗男孩内容，随便
it's called. Man.它被称为。 男人。
Oh, you did great.哦，你做得很好。
Thank you.谢谢你。
Thank you, guys.谢谢你们。
Appreciate the欣赏
I appreciate the the pep talk我很欣赏鼓舞人心的谈话
even though was really embarrassing.尽管真的很尴尬。
I r I don't think I'll ever
I don't think I'll ever do that again.我 r 我认为我不会再这样做了。我认为我不会再这样做了。
I don't think I'll ever do that
ever again.我不认为我会再这样做了。
OK, I'm taking the talking yourself. OK,
that's enough.好的，我自己来说话。 好的，这就够了。
They're gone.他们走了。
I don't know who that was.
I know who I was.我不知道那是谁。 我知道我是谁。
That wasn't me.那不是我。
That was not though.但事实并非如此。
That was a something else.那是另一回事。
Uh, Maggie, thank you for this honour.嗯，玛吉，谢谢你的荣誉。
I'd say back what I had said. Dog boy.我会回馈我说过的话。 狗男孩。
It's scary.它很可怕。
I'm foster children.我是寄养儿童。
I'm glad you enjoyed it.我很高兴你喜欢它。
I so honoured.我很荣幸。
Thank you for that. Done as well.谢谢你。 也完成了。
When I rub your ears and by U.S.当我揉你的耳朵和美国。
pancakes, I want sushi so bad.煎饼，我太想要寿司了。
Yes, thank you.是的，谢谢。
And make a
thank you for the gift sobs and pound on.并感谢你的礼物抽泣和冲击。
Thank you for the donation, HP.谢谢你的捐赠，惠普。
Thank you for the five to ones as well.也谢谢你的五对一。
The man男人
uh. Guys, guys.呃。 伙计们，伙计们。
Guys.伙计们。
Uh, that didn't happen.呃，那没有发生。
OK, that's.
But that's between. Me and you.好的，就是这样。 但那是介于两者之间。 我和你。
That was Dylan's between me
and you guys are.那是我和你们之间的迪伦。
Don't that don't so don't tell anyone else不要那样不要这样不要告诉别人
about what we just did today, ok?关于我们今天刚刚做了什么，好吗？
What what happens in the stream
stays in this stream.直播中发生的事情留在这个直播中。
What you guys heard
and what you guys know.你们听到了什么，你们知道什么。
It's like it's like forbidden knowledge.就像是禁忌知识一样。
You keep it here, ok?你把它留在这里，好吗？
We don't we don't tell anybody
else. We don't talk about it.我们不我们不告诉其他人。 我们不谈论它。
You know
that song like we don't talk about Bruno.你知道那首歌就像我们不谈论布鲁诺一样。
Yeah, it's exactly like that.是的，就是这样。
Just don't talk about it, OK?只是不要谈论它，好吗？
Just don't talk about it.只是不要谈论它。
I'll bite your hand off我会咬掉你的手
oh, god damn, bro.哦，该死的，兄弟。
Stupid soul.愚蠢的灵魂。
So stupid. OK.这么笨。 好的。
Well, I'm.嗯，我是。
I'm flustered now.我现在很慌张。
I'm I'm really flustered
from whatever just happened.我真的对刚刚发生的一切感到心慌。
So my my brain is kind of like所以我的大脑有点像
broken.破碎的。
I'm like, I'm like,
mind break tagged it at the moment.我很喜欢，我很喜欢，此刻已经标记了它。
You guys, the guilties.你们这些罪人。
I've have mine break tagged me我有我的休息标记我
and it's only been l how long is it.它只是我多久了。
It's only been 30 minutes.才30分钟。
Unlucky, dude, unlucky倒霉，哥们，倒霉
do not kill the part of you
that is cringe kill the part that cringes.不要杀死你畏缩的部分杀死畏缩的部分。
Thank you for the donation
and wise message Noa感谢您的捐赠和明智的信息诺亚
I'll take that to heart我会铭记于心
Asla thank
you for the fight the ones in the cage阿斯拉感谢你的战斗笼子里的人感谢你的50，感谢你的30
thank you for the 50and just thank you for the 30
am I practise blowing.我在练习吹。
Yeah I can blow是的，我可以吹
like blow.像打击一样。
Into blow into your ear not you know you吹进你的耳朵，你不认识你
you know I can try again
but I don't think it's你知道我可以再试一次，但我不认为这是
I don't think it's going to go too
well I'll try Lleyton Murray.我认为这不会太顺利，我会尝试 Lleyton Murray。
No, maybe.不，也许。
I don't know我不知道
it it's so obvious.它是如此明显。
Why be embarrassed.为什么会尴尬。
I really admire your bravery
and confidence.我真的很佩服你的勇敢和自信。
Thank you.谢谢你。
It takes confidence to be somebody's
dog. Boy成为别人的狗需要信心。 男生
or puppy boy, whatever you call it.或者小狗男孩，不管你怎么称呼它。
OK. Oh.好的。 哦。
Well, that's done.嗯，这就完成了。
I let me see.我让我看看。
Let me check something.让我检查一下。
I do want to try something我也想尝试一些东西。
as well.
Like, I'm
going to go through like a string of words就像，我会像一串词一样经历
or like a string of phrases或者像一串短语，试着，你知道，带来一些安慰
and try to, you know, bring some comfort
to people that might feel
a little doubtful of themselves.给那些可能对自己有点怀疑的人。
Or maybe there are some days where
you just feel like you can't I don't know.或者也许有些日子你只是觉得你不能，我不知道。
You feel like you have a你觉得你有很多答案，而不是你有很多期望。
lot of answer on notyou have a lot of expectations.
And, you know, sometimes you just don't而且，你知道，有时你只是不
want to想要
it's sometimes it's too much, right?有时是太多了，对吧？
There's a lot of expectations on everybody
and it can be so heavy.每个人都有很多期望，它可能如此沉重。
And I understand that so我是这么理解的
I guess this is like my little thing
for people我想这对那些肩负重担的人来说就像我的小东西
that have so much on their shouldersand they are
they don't know what to do,他们不知道该怎么做，
I guess.我猜。
So hold on.所以坚持住。
Can you hear that?你能听到吗？
Yeah, OK.是的，好的。
All right.好的。
Yeah, it's cuddle time.是的，现在是拥抱时间。
You want to call it that?你想这样称呼它吗？
It's cuddle time.现在是拥抱时间。
Sure.当然。
Yeah, my heart is beating fast.是的，我的心跳得很快。
I'm embarrassed, dude.我很尴尬，伙计。
You're doing great.你做的很棒。
I believe in you.我相信你。
You're doing your best.你正在尽力而为。
And I'm.我是。
I'm really proud of you.我真的为你感到骄傲。
That's it.这就对了。
And you guys can hear me swallow, too.你们也能听到我吞咽的声音。
I hope that's not embarrassing.
I don't know.我希望这不是尴尬。 我不知道。
Can you hear me? Swallow, huh?你能听到我吗？ 吞下去吧？
I never thought about that.我从来没想过那个。
It's OK.没关系。
Everything will be OK.一切都会变好。
I'm so, so proud of you.我是如此，为你感到骄傲。
You're going to do amazing.你会做的很棒。
I'll be here with you all the way我会一直在你身边
murder's OK.杀人没问题。
You can do it.你能行的。
And don't worry, I'll stay by your side别担心，我会一直陪在你身边的。
till the very end.
I couldn't help myself.我忍不住了。
I had to say it.我不得不说。
It's like that one.就是这样。
Mean, you know,意思是，你知道，伙计们，我喜欢，这是。
guys, I'm like, this is.
I'm like a whole package, OK?我就像一个完整的包裹，好吗？
Just remember that.记住这一点。
You can't.你不能。
You get, like, the mirror and you get the,你得到了，就像，镜子，你得到了，
you know, the soft side,
so you got a yardstick.你知道，柔软的一面，所以你有一个衡量标准。
Take it for what it is. Boys and girls.把它当作它是什么。 男孩和女孩。
OK, you好的，你可以做到。
can do it.
Keep moving for it.继续前进。
All right.好的。
I got your back我掩护你
you'll succeed.你会成功的。
I know you will.我知道你会的。
Trust me.相信我。
You're beautiful.你很美丽。
And you shine brighter than the stars而你比天上的星星和月亮还要耀眼。
and the moons in the sky.
I believe in you.我相信你。
OK, I'm好的，我很自豪。 你。
proud of. You.
Oh, yeah, OK.哦，是的，好的。
Yeah, I know. My heart break.是的，我知道。 我的心碎了。
My heart rate is high.我的心率很高。
I'm just nervous.我只是紧张。
I'm just really nervous, that's all.我真的很紧张，仅此而已。
All right.好的。
That's enough.足够了。
Get off my chest now.现在离开我的胸膛。
I hope that was good.我希望那很好。
I ah.我啊。
I just want to try something
akin to, like, you know,我只是想尝试类似的东西，比如，你知道，
a nice hug, a nice cuddle一个美好的拥抱，一个美好的拥抱
and having somebody there
to tell you you're doing great.并且有人在那里告诉你你做得很好。
And you're doing OK.你做得很好。
All right, all right.好吧，好吧。
So we drink more tea.所以我们喝更多的茶。
Tim, thank you for the.蒂姆，谢谢你。
Oh, thank you for the doll. No,哦，谢谢你的娃娃。 不，
and Nancy, thank you for the towel.和南希，谢谢你的毛巾。
No. Is well,不，很好，现在直接哭了。
straight out crying right now.
No, you can go. Please don't cry.不，你可以走了。 请不要哭。
Nauseated. Don't worry.恶心。 不用担心。
All of you are doing great. Trust me.你们都做得很好。 相信我。
I don't know what kind of battles each我不知道你们每个人都有什么样的战斗和
and every one of you have and
that's why I want to talk about, like,这就是为什么我想谈论很多时候，我试图进入一种你不认识任何人的心态。
a lot of time, I try to go into a mindsetthat you don't know anybody.
I don't know you.我不认识你。
You don't know me.你不认识我。
And, like, we have a lot going on而且，就像，我们有很多事情要做
behind what we show everybody else, right?在我们向其他人展示的背后，对吧？
And so you guys are better at lying所以你们更擅长说谎
than other people and, like, hiding,
you know, what you're going through.比其他人，比如隐藏，你知道，你正在经历什么。
So for those of you that are, like,所以对于你们这些人来说，像，
hiding that
I don't know what you got going on, but隐瞒我不知道你发生了什么，但是
it's like a little这就像我要说的一条小消息，嘿，你明白了，好吗？
message for me to say,hey, you got this, OK?
I don't know what you're going through.我不知道你正在经历什么。
But I feel like you'll be able to do it但我觉得你能做到
because you're my guild members.因为你们是我的公会成员。
I believe in you.我相信你。
You're here at the Avengers
Guild for a reason, right?你来到复仇者联盟是有原因的，对吧？
I don't know.我不知道。
I don't think my guilds or whatever,
you know,我不认为我的公会或其他什么，你知道，会被一个小挑战所超越。
gets get overtaken by a small challenge.
So I have more faith in
you guys than they might think.所以我对你们的信心比他们想象的要多。
Some other people might think其他一些人可能会认为
of you.你的。
Thank you for the donation as well.也感谢您的捐赠。
Do you remember the song Before
I Close My Eyes?你还记得在我闭上眼睛之前那首歌吗？
All right.好的。
I still can't believe you remember that.我还是不敢相信你还记得那件事。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
Do I remember?我记得吗？
you want me to humm it?你要我哼哼吗？
I think I remember how it goes.我想我记得它是怎么回事。
Hmm. Hmm, hmm唔。 嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯。
It's an odd song.这是一首奇怪的歌。
It's like it repeats the same melody over
and over again.就像一遍又一遍地重复着同样的旋律。
Name it down to sleep.把它命名为睡觉。
I pray Lord my soul to keep.我祈求主保佑我的灵魂。
I hope it's not too late for me.我希望对我来说还不算晚。
Yeah, I think it goes like that.是的，我认为是这样的。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Changing in the heart.内心的变化。
Then come那就来吧
hmm. Yeah.唔。 是的。
It's been awhile.已经过了很久了。
Isn't it an old one?不是旧的吗？
I can't believe you remember that.我不敢相信你还记得那件事。
Yeah.是的。
It's been so long since ever since I sang
anything related to that, but, hey,好久没有唱过与此相关的歌了，但是，嘿，
that's really. It's really nice, dude.那是真的。 这真的很好，伙计。
Thanks for reminding me.谢谢你的提醒。
I used to like it a lot more back
then than I do now, I guess.我想我以前比现在更喜欢它。
But you know,
you grow out of certain songs.但是你知道，你是从某些歌曲中成长起来的。
You really do. And你真的会。 和
I know now I'm listening to a bunch of我知道现在我在听一堆
a bunch of ki pop and rock,一堆 ki 直播行音乐和摇滚，我会说 R&B
and I'd say an R&B
my music tastes
change a lot over the years.这些年来我的音乐品味发生了很大变化。
It happens, right?它发生了，对吧？
Yeah.是的。
Happens发生
you'll miss hum Isabel's lullaby.你会想念哼伊莎贝尔的摇篮曲。
Oh, is it.哦，是吗。
Is that the one that's from a那是从一个
that's the one from Promised Neverland.那是来自Promised Neverland的那个。
Right.对。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
How did he go again?他怎么又去了？
Fuck.他妈的。
It's been so long
since I've watched The Enemy.好久没看《大敌》了。
You kind of went like.你有点像。
Hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm.嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
It was like that, and I don't remember the
rest for some reason.就是这样，出于某种原因，我不记得其余的了。
Yeah,是的，
it's been
a long time since I've watched it.我已经很久没有看过了。
It's a it was a great anime.这是一部很棒的动漫。
I love the the first arc of that series.我喜欢那个系列的第一部。
It's really beautiful.它真的很漂亮。
Yeah, that lullaby is.是的，那是摇篮曲。
I'm. I can't continue.我是。 我无法继续。
I don't know how to. Continue, though.我不知道怎么去。 不过，继续。
I don't know how to continue.我不知道如何继续。
That's been.就是这样。
I don't know.我不知道。
And, uh, you brought you.而且，呃，你带来了你。
Bring back a lot of memories
about the show, though, so不过，带回了很多关于这个节目的回忆，所以
I'm not karaoke stream, by the way, guys,
so I don't the顺便说一句，我不是卡拉 OK 直播，伙计们，所以我不
I can sing anything,
but I can, you know, just do a little bit我可以唱任何东西，但我可以，你知道，只是做一点点
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
I think,我认为，
I think some people want more,
more attention我想有些人想要更多，更多的关注
so give me a sec.所以给我一秒钟。
How Oh, yeah,哦，是的，
yeah.是的。
Yeah.是的。
Oh, uh,哦，呃，
uh, mm mm mm嗯，毫米毫米毫米
mm well.嗯嗯。
Wow. Mm哇。 毫米
mm mm毫米毫米
mm well.嗯嗯。
OK. Oh, oh.好的。 哦，哦。
OK, oh.好的，哦。
It's.它的。
Just not there because my lips,
my lips are going to, you know, to what只是不在那里，因为我的嘴唇，我的嘴唇，你知道，你的年轻人会做什么，做什么
your young will, to what
I really hope
the Iraqis sound good to you guys.我真的希望伊拉克人对你们听起来不错。
Like,像，
I've been trying my best
to find the right spots,我一直在努力寻找正确的位置，希望我能找到正确的位置
and hopefully I'm hitting the right spots
for that.为了那个原因。
You know what they say.你知道他们说了什么。
Practise makes perfect. Yeah.熟能生巧。 是的。
Or practise或者练习
more.更多的。
Thank you for the donation.感谢您的捐赠。
Today's or one month
anniversary of liking you今天或喜欢你一个月的纪念日
are welcome back from one month tour欢迎从一个月的旅行回来，捐款很好而且很细。
and the donation is well and mincey.
Thank you for the demo.感谢您的演示。
Glad you found my strings.很高兴你找到了我的琴弦。
You thank you for being so amazingly kind.你感谢你如此善良。
And so the voices. So call me as well.声音也是如此。 所以也给我打电话。
I'm glad
that you find comfort in these times我很高兴你能在这些时候找到安慰
when we do get like a moment like thisand it's not like all the time chaotic
and yelling when we play like overcooked
or a whale or like it takes two or.当我们像煮过头或鲸鱼一样玩耍时大喊大叫，或者像需要两个或一样。
I don't know. Something我不知道。 某物
where I am like我就像被撞到墙上的球，你知道，
balls to the walls, you know,
I'm glad I get to have moments like this
so you guys can just chill back.我很高兴我能有这样的时刻，所以你们可以冷静下来。
And I can also chill back since I'm我也可以冷静下来，因为我
I don't want to.我不想。
Oh, no.不好了。
I want to be,
you know, yelling all the time,我想，你知道，一直在大喊大叫，
like, loud all the time.就像，一直响亮。
I enjoy my quiet
I feel like everyone enjoys their quiet.我喜欢我的安静我觉得每个人都喜欢他们的安静。
So it's nice to take some time
like this and所以很高兴能像这样花一些时间
embrace some solace once in a while.偶尔拥抱一些安慰。
And that's what we're doing right now.这就是我们现在正在做的事情。
Just enjoying some moments of solace只是享受一些安慰的时刻
also I'm running out of tea.我也快没茶了。
T Oh, my God, bro, I'm running out of tea.T 哦，天哪，兄弟，我的茶快用完了。
Ahh.啊。
I think我认为
I just drank too much earlier on
because I was nervous我只是喝了太多，因为我对狗男孩的东西感到紧张。
from the Dog Boy stuff.
I think我认为
there is another prompt.还有另一个提示。
Yeah.是的。
Here we go.开始了。
There's another prompter还有一个提示符
I did want to try out.我确实想试试。
It's not very on它不是很亮
ASMR leaning, butASMR 倾斜，但它就像 Cinderel。
it's like Cinderel.
It's kind of cinderell这是一种灰姑娘
because I saw a video因为我看到有人在做这样的事情的视频，我想，哦，
of someone doing something like thisand I was like, oh,
I'm going to try this我要试试这个
so I guess I'll give it a try.所以我想我会试一试。
Oh, God, yeah.哦，天哪，是的。
Oh, God.天啊。
OK, give me a second.好的，请稍等。
OK, I'll put on the face好的，我会敷脸
I mean, there's a way to find the face.我的意思是，有一种方法可以找到脸。
Check it on.检查它。
Cut off. OK,隔断。 好的，
how do I approach this我如何在不让自己尴尬的情况下解决这个问题？ 好的。
without embarrassing myself? OK.
Oh, a simply, I didn't know.哦，一个简单的，我不知道。
You walk this way.你走这条路。
Oh, I'm very in front of your house, huh?哦，我在你家门前，嗯？
Oh, no, I.哦，不，我。
I wasn't looking at it
or looking for you or anything.我不是在看它，也不是在寻找你或任何东西。
I just.我只是。
I happened to be walking by
and and I noticed我碰巧路过，我注意到
Mark, I was, like, walking by,马克，我就像，路过，
but. OK, OK, fine.但。 好的，好的，好的。
The truth is.事实是。
I wanted to give you something.我想给你一些东西。
Listen, don't get. Me wrong,
but I was just up till two. A.m.听着，不明白。 我错了，但我刚到两点。 是。
making lunch for school today.今天为学校做午餐。
And I know.而且我知道。
Hamburgers steak just happens
to be your favourite, and I was making.汉堡牛排恰好是你最喜欢的，我正在做。
Some, and I want to know if you would like
some, and I had extra.一些，我想知道你是否想要一些，我还有额外的。
Be grateful.非常感激。
Like, OK.喜欢，好的。
How do I know it was your favourite?我怎么知道这是你最喜欢的？
I, i,我，我，我没事。
i ok.
That's it.这就对了。
Ah. Oh.啊。 哦。
I don don't look at me.我不看我。
You did.你做到了。
And my.和我的。
Ears are so red.耳朵好红。
My ears are so fucking red from that.我的耳朵因为那件事太他妈的红了。
You guys have no idea.你们不知道。
My face is so hot.我的脸好烫。
I am. I'm flustered beyond imagine.我是。 我的慌乱超出想象。
How did that get
me more. Flustered than. The.那怎么让我更多。 慌张比。 这。
Jesus are. The.耶稣是。 这。
The screaming.尖叫声。
Yeah you know, it's it's it's called
you got to put in some.是的，你知道，这就是所谓的你必须放一些。
An embarrassment factor so I like a一个尴尬的因素，所以我喜欢
got to be flustered.得心慌。
Shut up.住口。
Don't look at me shut up.不要看着我闭嘴。
Don't, don't look at me.不要，不要看我。
I'm just kidding我只是在开玩笑，如果你愿意，你可以看着我
you can look at me if you want
but since some people asked但是既然有人问是的，你可以听但是
yeah you can listen but
I don't know if, like, people ever我不知道人们是否曾经
to just, like, a stream of thought.只是，就像，一个思想流。
Like,
they put the microphone up to their heart.就像，他们把麦克风放在心上。
It's like, oh, poor me,就像，哦，可怜的我，
you've had a bad day.你度过了糟糕的一天。
And I'm coddling you in brackets.我在括号里哄你。
You're laying on my chest and can hear my.你躺在我的胸口，可以听到我的声音。
Heart rate or heartbeat.心率或心跳。
Yeah,是的，
you know, I mean, bro,你知道，我的意思是，兄弟，
you know what I mean? Did.你知道我的意思？ 做过。
Yeah.是的。
Gail Foster.盖尔·福斯特。
Yeah, I did.是啊，我做了。
Stop sobs.停止抽泣。
You don't have. To say it like that.你没有。 就这么说吧。
If you want to say it like that.如果你想这样说。
Just going to call me out OK?只是想叫我出去好吗？
Oh, that's really stuff on YouTube.哦，这真的是 YouTube 上的东西。
Wow. Really?哇。 真的吗？
That's really cute.这真的很可爱。
Did I know about that?我知道吗？
OK, this next prompt that I wanted to try好的，我想尝试的下一个提示
leaned along the lines of沿着线倾斜
what's it它是什么
as opposed to last time.与上次相反。
It's more like它更像
this time I'm going to.这次我要去。
It's it's.它就是它。
Something similar.相似的东西。
It's something similar, right? So这是类似的东西，对吧？ 所以只是更健康的狗屎。
just more wholesome shit.
Something more wholesome.更健康的东西。
Again, nothing lewd,
just only wholesome vibes.再一次，没有什么淫荡的，只有健康的氛围。
Derrick song
but no, I don't believe in that.井架歌不过没有，我不相信。
Say so. It's not real to me.这样说的。 这对我来说不是真实的。
I firmly believe Say So is a cult.我坚信 Say So 是一种邪教。
It doesn't exist它不存在
everybody.大家。
Everybody is lewd to a degree.每个人都有一定程度的淫荡。
Even the most special person即使是最特别的人
you might have, you might have seen right你可能有，你可能没看错
especially me.尤其是我。
What OK,什么好，
so let me see.所以让我看看。
What are we doing now?我们现在在做什么？
Give me a second.你稍等一会儿。
I'm looking for it.我正在寻找它。
OK, here it is.好的，就是这样。
OK, oh, boy.好的，哦，男孩。
Oh, boy.好家伙。
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.好家伙。 好家伙。
Only time, only time.只有时间，只有时间。
Only time.只有时间。
On their time. On their time.在他们的时间。 在他们的时间。
On their time, on their time.在他们的时间，在他们的时间。
I mean, sister on me is our brother right?我的意思是，我的姐姐是我们的兄弟，对吧？
When my friends are, I was like, chilling.当我的朋友们在的时候，我就像，不寒而栗。
Chilling off each one of them.让他们每个人都冷静下来。
And I kind of brought it up我有点提出来了
and they were telling me to say it
in like in different ways.他们告诉我要以不同的方式说出来。
And one of their favourites was like他们最喜欢的一个是当我用一种质疑的语气做这件事时，就像我想的那样。
when I did it in like a questioningtone, like I think those.
All on that song,都在那首歌上，在那首歌上，
on that song,
on that song.在那首歌上。
Oh, I need some.哦，我需要一些。
Like in it yeah.喜欢在里面是的。
Like asking them something
or like asking something from them.喜欢问他们什么，或者喜欢问他们什么。
It's like a,它就像一个，
I don't know.我不知道。
I don't know what the appeal of it was.我不知道它的吸引力是什么。
OK, oh, OK.好的，哦，好的。
I think I'm good to try this one out.我想我可以试试这个。
Oh boy, oh boy.哦，男孩，哦，男孩。
Oh, boy.好家伙。
Oh. Hey, baby.哦。 嗨宝贝。
Sorry I got back home a little late抱歉我回家晚了一点
where can we stay?我们可以住在哪里？
A little longer than I wanted to, but比我想的要长一点，但是
I brought back some ice cream
as an apology gift.我带回了一些冰淇淋作为道歉礼物。
Oh. Is everything OK?哦。 一切都顺利吗？
I didn't make you sad or anything, did I?我没有让你难过什么的，不是吗？
Did I worry you again?我又让你担心了吗？
Oh, sorry, honey.哦，对不起，亲爱的。
You know how busy I am.你知道我有多忙。
It's not easy, but这并不容易，但
I promise I'm not overdoing it.我保证我不会做得过火。
I just.我只是。
I really
want to impress my co-workers, and我真的很想给我的同事留下深刻印象，并且
I want to make you happy till.我想让你快乐直到。
I mean it.我是认真的。
Yeah, I mean it.是的，我是认真的。
Don't sell yourself so much silly.不要那么傻地推销自己。
I want nothing more than to come home我只想回家
as soon as possible to my darling尽快给我亲爱的
oh, come here and cuddle me, OK?哦，过来抱抱我好吗？
That's it.这就对了。
Yeah.是的。
How'd you sleep today?你今天睡得怎么样？
I wish I got a little more chill,
but it doesn't help.我希望我能再冷一点，但这并没有帮助。
I had a nightmare我做了一个噩梦
you know, I've been having你知道，我最近一直在做最奇怪的梦。
the weirdest dreams lately.
No, I'm not going to.不，我不会。
Just tell you.只是告诉你。
It's embarrassing.这很尴尬。
You'll make fun of me.你会取笑我的。
Oh, you'll have to pretend哦，你将不得不假装你也不知道。
like you don't know either.
Besides the nightmare.除了噩梦。
It's not like I really dream
about anyone else.这不像我真的梦到别人。
Besides, you除你之外
don't have to tease me so much.不必逗我这么多。
You know that你知道的
you're bully你欺负人
fine.美好的。
I just want to follow you.我只想跟着你。
Then how about that?那怎么办？
Oh. You want it that badly?哦。 你那么想要吗？
Oh, I'm sorry.哦，对不起。
OK. OK, sorry.好的。 好的，对不起。
Sorry.对不起。
I don't tease you like that again.我不会再这样取笑你了。
Fine.美好的。
Come here.过来。
I'll hold我会抱着你的。
your can you.
Know, I worry.知道，我担心。
About how you treat yourself till since关于你如何对待自己直到那时
I'm not the only hard worker here.我不是这里唯一的勤奋工作者。
Take it easy.别紧张。
Once in a while. OK,偶尔。 好吧，也许我们应该一起去春节约会。
maybe we should go on a dateto the Spring Festival together.
The flowers are all blooming
right now and.花儿现在都在盛开。
To. Be great.到。 很棒。
Take pictures together, right?一起拍照对吧？
Yeah.是的。
I want to see the flowers.我想看花。
So feel所以感觉
you're really beautiful, too.你也真的很漂亮。
More beautiful than any of them.比他们中的任何一个都漂亮。
Was that you? Cheesy.那是你吗？ 俗气。
Sorry.对不起。
But, you know, I mean that, right?但是，你知道，我的意思是，对吧？
You make me so happy你让我很开心
and you smell good.你闻起来很香。
And you look so stunning in the sunlight.你在阳光下看起来如此迷人。
OK, ok.好的好的。
I think that's enough cuddling, though.不过，我认为这已经足够拥抱了。
I think it's about time
we make dinner soon.我想我们很快就该做晚饭了。
Right对
now, it's ok.现在，没关系。
You can rest a little while longer.你可以多休息一会儿。
I can take care of dinner tonight.我可以照顾今晚的晚餐。
No, I don't need any help.不，我不需要任何帮助。
Please just rest if you need it.如果需要，请休息。
OK, babe,好的宝贝，
you can help out a little later
with dessert如果你愿意，你可以稍后帮忙吃甜点
if you want
now, close your eyes.现在，闭上你的眼睛。
That's it.这就对了。
Good.好的。
Good boy.好孩子。
Good girl.好姑娘。
You've always liked forehead
kisses, right?你一直喜欢额头亲吻，对吧？
Yeah, I know you do.是的，我知道你知道。
And I'll wake you up soon.我很快就会叫醒你。
Sleep well, baby.睡个好觉，宝贝。
I love you.我爱你。
Goodnight.晚安。
OK, that was.好的，就是这样。
Yeah, that was one.是的，那是一个。
My friend我的朋友
wrote for me.为我写的。
Because I had no idea what to do.因为我不知道该怎么做。
And she was like, you know,
I think something a little.她就像，你知道的，我想了一点。
A little cheesy romantic would fit.有点俗气的浪漫会很合适。
And then I was like, sure, why not?然后我想，当然，为什么不呢？
So, hey, I tried.所以，嘿，我试过了。
I didn't我没有
I just like my first, like, you know, time
reading through the entire thing我只是喜欢我的第一个，就像，你知道的，时间阅读整个事情
since he gave it to me.自从他给了我。
He's really cute.他真的很可爱。
That's really cute, though.不过，这真的很可爱。
My two are我的两个是
not too weird.不太奇怪。
Sorry.对不起。
That's a stretch.这是一个延伸。
Really.真的。
Second第二
I think you should those right.我认为你应该是对的。
It felt so cheesy.感觉太俗气了。
It felt so cheesy, dude.感觉太俗气了，伙计。
Like, Oh my God, there's so much
mozzarella and and chowder everywhere.就像，天哪，到处都是马苏里拉奶酪和杂烩。
When I was reading through it当我阅读它时
I thought我想
it was cute though.不过很可爱。
Know as long as you guys liked it
then that's all that matters.知道只要你们喜欢它，那才是最重要的。
Sorry.对不起。
Cheesy is.俗气的是。
Good, Ivan.很好，伊万。
Yeah,
everyone likes some cheese, but, man,是的，每个人都喜欢奶酪，但是，伙计，
it's like它像是
there's.有。
You can have
you can have too much cheese, right?你可以有你可以有太多的奶酪，对吧？
You can have a little
too much cheese sometimes. So有时你可能会吃太多奶酪。 所以
it's on.它开着。
So take a shot every time. She says,
don't look at me tonight.所以每次都要拍。 她说，今晚别看我。
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
You're going to get very inebriated on你会非常陶醉
very, very inebriated.非常非常陶醉。
Indeed.确实。
Thank you for the $13 chateau.感谢您购买 13 美元的城堡。
You're Sookie.
I want to give you a big hug. Then do it.你是苏琪。 我想给你一个大大的拥抱。 然后去做。
How are you?你好吗？
Come here and give me a hug. Then
Oh, yeah.过来给我一个拥抱。 然后哦，是的。
I remember last.我记得最后。
Time there a song tell me to do a dipen.有时间有一首歌告诉我做一个dipen。
And then it came out really weak. Like然后它真的很弱。 像
it sounded really.听起来真的。
Ah, baby,啊，宝贝，
and people made fun of me for it
because it was so weak.人们因此取笑我，因为它太弱了。
But it's. I can't.但它的。 我不能。
If I do it too loud, then.如果我做得太大声，那么。
It's going to hurt your ears. Right?它会伤害你的耳朵。 对？
So I'm not going to do that.所以我不会那样做。
That's. I didn't want to do that.那是。 我不想那样做。
Yeah, it was like it was last time是的，就像上次一样
it's going to break anybody's
ears too early.它会过早地打破任何人的耳朵。
Right?对？
Something for the kids.给孩子的东西。
Oh, no.不好了。
Good morning to you
and good night to myself.对你说早安，对我自己说晚安。
Good night.晚安。
Did I hear any good one我有没有听到好听的
other? Thank you for the zone.其他？ 谢谢你的区域。
I, too, was so comfy.我也一样，很舒服。
I'm almost falling asleep.我快要睡着了。
How many of you guys are on your phone
right now?你们现在有多少人在玩手机？
I want to know again我想再次知道有多少人在他们的手机或 PC 上收听我的声音？
how many people are listeningto me on their phone or on the PC?
Yeah,是的，
oh, that's a lot of people
listening on the phone.哦，那是很多人在听电话。
Oh, my goodness. Wow.哦，我的天啊。 哇。
Yeah, a lot of phone users.是的，很多电话用户。
I mean, it makes sense.我的意思是，这是有道理的。
Some people are still in bed, right?有些人还在床上，对吧？
A lot of people. Just很多人。 刚滚到床上，他们可能会昏倒。 所以
rolled into bedand they might pass out. So
Sunset iPad. Wow.日落 iPad。 哇。
I haven't used an iPad in such a long
time.好久没用iPad了。
It's been like years.就像几年一样。
I think since I've gone to touch one我想自从我去碰一个
but I hope you guys enjoyed that但我希望你们喜欢这个小提示
little prompt
if you have any.如果你有任何。
What's it它是什么
if you have any small requests,如果您有任何小要求，可以通过以下方式告诉我
you can let me know either through
chat or through donations or whatever.聊天或通过捐赠或其他方式。
I can try and do them
if you want for the rest of the stream,如果你想在直播的其余部分做，我可以尝试做，
like something that's doable.像可行的东西。
Nothing like too much, of course,当然，没什么好说的，但我会通读它，如果我能做到，我会尝试去做。
but I'll read through itand if I can do it, I'll try and do it.
Like say a phrase like I'm our last time.就像说我是我们最后一次这样的短语。
So and try to give me a say
that skirmish line or whatever.所以，试着给我说一下小冲突线或其他什么。
And I was just而我只是
I free balled.我自由了。
It ends is pretty, you know,结局很美，你知道，
I'd say it was close, right?我会说它很接近，对吧？
Kind of miaow is it?是什么喵？
Everyone wants him yell.每个人都希望他大喊大叫。
I like miaow like miaowing.我喜欢喵喵喵喵喵。
I guess when I hear cats for我想当我听到猫的声音时
yeah.是的。
Yeah, yeah.是啊是啊。
I yeah.我是的。
Well,好，
you well.你好。
I don't know how to miaow dude.我不知道如何 miaow 老兄。
I don't think I know. I don't know.我不认为我知道。 我不知道。
It's it's not
it doesn't come as easy as like,不是它没有来得那么容易，
like, like dog does.就像狗一样。
It's hard to do both.两者都很难做到。
It's not like I'm pick and choose
voice actor.这不像我是挑选配音演员。
She can do a lot uh.她可以做很多事情。
A wolf一只狼
d wolves.d 狼。
Well, well,好吧，
well, well.好吧。
Oh, hold on.哦，等一下。
Give me a second.你稍等一会儿。
I think I我想我
yeah, give me a quick second.是的，给我一点时间。
Guilties hold on.罪孽深重。
Sorry.对不起。
I thought I heard somebody at my door.我想我听到有人在我家门口。
I don't think anyone was there.我不认为有人在那里。
On your on your on your在你的 在你的 在你的
buddy.伙伴。
Guys like.小伙伴们喜欢。
The O'Neals so much.奥尼尔太多了。
You know who I blame?你知道我怪谁吗？
I blame.我责怪。
I blame the boys我责怪男孩们影响了这一点
for for influencing that
yeah.是的。
All of are.都是。
All them are.他们都是。
Quite an influence in在中颇有影响
you know, that's ok.你知道，没关系。
It's totally fine.完全没问题。
It's adorable.它很可爱。
Oh. Katherine,哦。 凯瑟琳，你的朋友很快就要过生日和婚礼了。
your friend is going to have a birthdayand a wedding very soon.
Can you give them a happy birthday
and happy wedding blessing?你能给他们一个生日快乐和新婚快乐的祝福吗？
I can say. I can just say, hey,我可以说。 我只能说，嘿，
happy birthday.生日快乐。
And to help
you enjoy your wedding to your friend.并帮助您享受与朋友的婚礼。
Have a wonderful day.有一个美好的一天。
Did I'm not.我不是吗。
Thank you for the Tano
attending marks here.感谢您在这里的 Tano 参加分数。
Three months as being a guilty, holding
you and smiling you my imagination.三个月如作有罪，抱着你笑你我的想象。
No, thank you, darling.不，谢谢你，亲爱的。
Thank you for being around for so long.谢谢你这么久的陪伴。
I know我知道
some of you people of你们中的一些人的声音和文字以及心跳对我有很大帮助
your voice and wordsand your heartbeat helps me a lot
can you call me your little puppy, please?请叫我你的小狗好吗？
I thought I was the puppy here我以为我是这里的小狗
which 1 a.m.凌晨 1 点
I, owner or puppy?我，主人还是小狗？
You have an exam in two weeks
and in a week?你有两周和一周的考试吗？
In two days.
Can you bully you into studying?在两天。 你能欺负你学习吗？
You want me to bully you into studying?你要我欺负你学习吗？
How do I do that?我怎么做？
I don't look like.我看起来不像。
I listen to myself trying to be, like,
you know, assertive.我倾听自己试图变得，就像，你知道的，自信的。
And I could not take it seriously.我不能认真对待它。
Like, last time,
it made me so embarrassed guys.就像，上次，这让我很尴尬的家伙。
Like,像，
I heard it, and I was like,
no, that does not feel right.我听到了，我想，不，那感觉不对。
I can't.我不能。
I can't be like, oh, go.我不能这样，哦，走吧。
Go study right now
or go do your go to your work.现在就去学习或去做你的工作。
Be word, you know,是字，你知道，或者
or or
go a fucking去他妈的
be responsible.要负责任。
You a whore.你个妓女。
I don't like that
that Zaza doesn't come after that song.我不喜欢扎扎在那首歌之后没有出现。
And doesn't come out.而且不出来。
It's on to all它适用于所有员工。
employees.
I don't know.我不知道。
I feel like maybe it's not meant for me.我觉得也许它不适合我。
I try and.我尝试和。
I try and I try. Trust me, I do.我尝试，我尝试。 相信我，我愿意。
I really do.我真的。
But it always like, you know, comes back
up and just makes me feel like.但它总是像，你知道的，回来，只是让我觉得。
Well,
it doesn't feel it doesn't feel right.嗯，不觉得不对劲。
Doesn't feel natural.感觉不是很自然。
It's not even about tough.这甚至与艰难无关。
It's like involving a top or it's on.这就像涉及一个顶部或它在。
It's just like, you know. That being mean.就像，你知道的。 那是卑鄙的。
Or like degrading.或者喜欢贬低。
I feel like being mean
and degrading is not my forte.我觉得刻薄和贬低不是我的强项。
And even though
I tried it before, it's like即使我之前尝试过，它就像
doing it on the spot, it's kind of like.现场做，有点像。
Well, I don't want to be mean to you when.好吧，我不想对你刻薄。
You just, you know,你只是，你知道，
I mean, you did give me permission
to be means you.我的意思是，你确实允许我成为你的意思。
So I guess that's different所以我想这是不同的
well,好，
so are you going to hear me
stretching a lot?所以你会听到我伸展很多吗？
Because again,
I woke up not too long ago, so.因为再次，我不久前醒来，所以。
I need to.我需要。
Crack my bones and my back折断我的骨头和背部
yeah.是的。
Cracks a little bit.有点裂。
I I feel like when you stretch, you should
hear your bones crack like a little.我觉得当你伸展时，你应该听到你的骨头有点裂开。
It's because you're, like, getting rid
of all that pent up gas or whatever.这是因为你，就像，摆脱所有被压抑的气体或其他东西。
It's in between your bones.它在你的骨头之间。
OK, oh, we were one K away from好的，哦，我们离我们只有一公里
from 400 on.从400开始。
So they're really.所以他们是真的。
Really真的
hold on.坚持，稍等。
I didn't know a lot.我不知道很多。
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
We are我们是
oh, my goodness.哦，我的天啊。
Oh, my goodness.哦，我的天啊。
Did you write a really close你写的真的很接近吗
thank you, guys.谢谢你们。
That's really.那是真的。
Two and one day两天零一天
dots.点。
You milestones and ones a.你的里程碑和一个。
Pug. Pug帕格。 哈巴狗
oh, thank you for another dimension.哦，谢谢你的另一个维度。
Can you whisper in my ear
like last time? Hmm.你能像上次一样在我耳边低语吗？ 唔。
I think I can when I get我想当我得到
the last, like, I might read
through the script that we did last time.最后，就像，我可能会通读我们上次所做的脚本。
Again,再次，
for Fonzie'sFonzie's 因为那个真的很好。
because that one was really good.
I'm proud of that.我为此感到自豪。
I think it'd be really nice
to go through that again.我认为再经历一次真的很好。
Yeah,是的，
so it's a very it's
a very sweet little one.所以这是一个非常非常可爱的小家伙。
Little message小消息
for for anybody,
whether it's your first time here对于任何人来说，无论是你第一次来这里还是你再次听到，我觉得这是
or like you're hearing again,I feel like it's
it gets a它得到一个
comforting
idea or like a comforting message thrill.令人欣慰的想法或喜欢令人欣慰的消息刺激。
And that's all I want to do.这就是我想做的。
So on.很快。
Yeah, give me a second. I'll do that.是的，给我一秒钟。 我去做。
I'll probably do that.我可能会这样做。
I just need to clear my throat real fast.我只需要快速清清喉咙。
All right, hold on.好吧，等一下。
OK, I don't know if you guys can hear
that.好的，不知道你们能不能听到。
I think my我认为我的
there's like, something going on outside.好像，外面发生了什么事。
I was.我曾是。
I'd ok我会好的
am I eating我在吃吗
and my eating?我吃什么？
No, I'm not eating.不，我不吃东西。
I mean.我是说。
I ate before this, you know,
if that's what you mean.我在这之前吃过，你知道的，如果那是你的意思。
I'm not eating right now.我现在不吃东西。
You know?你知道？
Hold on, hold on. Give me a second.等一下，等一下。 你稍等一会儿。
I, I could, I could我，我可以，我可以
I could do this我可以这样做
yeah.是的。
Some people like.有些人喜欢。
The crunch right紧缩权
yeah.是的。
It's more pretzels.这是更多的椒盐脆饼。
People like.人们喜欢。
That's a这是一个
when I crunch on the
hard pretzels from my bag.当我从包里吃起硬脆的椒盐脆饼时。
I swore aloud.我大声发誓。
What do you mean?你什么意思？
I swallow loud? Well,
you can hear that to.我吞咽的声音很大？ 嗯，你可以听到。
Oh, my God, you can hear me swallow like.哦，我的上帝，你能听到我吞咽的声音。
Oh, God, dude.哦，天哪，伙计。
Holy shit.天啊。
I didn't know that OK?我不知道这样好吗？
Nah. It's water.不。 它是水。
I was just drinking some water. OK?我只是在喝水。 好的？
But I think I'm good to a read there.但我认为我很适合在那里阅读。
Another part, another prompt.另一部分，另一个提示。
So give me a second所以给我一秒钟
a swallowing is somewhere. No.吞咽在某处。 不。
All right.好的。
We did this one last time,
but I wanted to do it again.我们上次做了这个，但我想再做一次。
OK, so好的，所以
oh, you're still in bed, darling.哦，亲爱的，你还在床上。
It's been 2 hours,
and you've been scrolling已经 2 小时了，你整个上午都在浏览
through twitter and ticktock all morning.Twitter 和 ticktock。
Are you enjoying yourself?你玩得开心吗？
You had a hard day.你度过了艰难的一天。
Yessiree, babe.是的，宝贝。
Oh, I know you work so hard all the time,哦，我知道你一直很努力，
but if you keep working yourself
like this, you're going to burn out但如果你继续这样工作，你会筋疲力尽的
you've had a lot on your plate lately,你最近有很多事情要做，我们也没有出去太多。
and we haven't gone to go outmuch to get either.
This everything OK?这一切都好吗？
I know我知道工作很重要，但你应该记住
work is important,but you should remember that
you're the most important你是最重要的
don't try and overdo it, please.请不要尝试过度。
I know you can be a little too nice我知道你有时会有点太善良，承担太多
sometimes and take on too much
oh, I just.哦，我只是。
I want you to value yourself more, babe.我希望你更珍惜自己，宝贝。
OK, you know, you.好的，你知道的，你。
Mean the world to me.对我来说意味着世界。
Have you been eating enough lately to你最近吃得够后悔吗？
sorry?
I just worry about you a lot.我只是很担心你。
You know,你知道，
well,好，
it's nice to spend the morning
like this to ourselves.很高兴自己度过这样的早晨。
Yes, come here.是的，来这里。
Let me take care of you today, OK?今天让我照顾你，好吗？
I'll make you breakfast after this我会在这之后给你做早餐直到现在。
till now.
What does my love once eat today, huh?我的爱人今天吃了什么，嗯？
Omelettes, bacon,煎蛋卷、培根、薯饼。
hash browns.
Hash browns
actually sound really good right now.薯饼现在听起来真的很好。
Maybe I can make an egg souffle.也许我可以做一个蛋奶酥。
I can make some pancakes我可以做一些煎饼并尝试新的食谱。
and try a new recipe.
Sorry.对不起。
I'm just this hungry too. I guess我也只是这么饿。 我想也许如果你感觉好些，我们可以一起做。
maybe if you're feeling better,we can make it together.
If you want to make it together,如果你想一起做，
you're not feeling it.你没有感觉。
Oh, honey,噢，亲爱的，
you have to take care of yourself
tomorrow, OK?明天你要照顾好自己，好吗？
You know,
you can lean on me more too, right?你知道，你也可以更多地依靠我，对吧？
You love me, right?你爱我，对吧？
I love you, too.我也爱你。
It's OK to ask for help.寻求帮助是可以的。
It's OK to feel a little vulnerable
to shh.对嘘感到有点脆弱是可以的。
That's it.这就对了。
Let it out.说出来。
Good bye.再见。
Good girl.好姑娘。
You're amazing.你太棒了。
You're amazing你很了不起，也很特别。
and special.
In one of a kind.在其中一种。
Nights.夜晚。
I'll never want to see you hurt我永远不想看到你受伤
you too.你也是。
A lot every day.每天很多。
And it's okay to take some time
for yourself once in a while.偶尔为自己花点时间也是可以的。
It's OK to be a little greedy
and need some more affection.有点贪心是可以的，需要更多的感情。
All right.好的。
Just ask me and I'll be there for you.只要问我，我就会在你身边。
I'll always be there for you.我会永远在你身边。
You've been doing so well.你一直做得很好。
You don't need to try so hard
all the time.你不需要一直那么努力。
You're really inspiring.你真的很鼓舞人心。
Not only to me,
but to so many other people.不仅对我，对很多其他人也是如此。
You might not even realise你可能甚至没有意识到
I'm not lying either.我也没有说谎。
I promise.我保证。
So what would you like me to do for you亲爱的，今天你想让我为你做什么？
today, darling?
I can clean up while you sleep. Why?我可以在你睡觉的时候打扫卫生。 为什么？
I can make all the meals for today.我可以做今天所有的饭菜。
Maybe I can do all your chores till也许我可以做你所有的家务直到
you just want my company你只想要我的陪伴
you know you have all the time, right?你知道你有所有的时间，对吧？
Oh, on哦，开
sorry.对不起。
I thought I heard something outside me
that's on my room.我想我听到外面有什么东西在我的房间里。
You just saw my company.你刚刚看到我的公司。
You know,
you'll always have it all the time, right?你知道，你会一直拥有它，对吧？
Silly.愚蠢的。
As if I'm going to go anywhere好像我要去任何地方
OK? I can do that for you.好的？ 我可以为你做到这一点。
Anything for you.什么都给你。
My hard.我的硬。
Little worker. Hmm.小工人。 唔。
Deep breaths, ok?深呼吸，好吗？
Breathe slowly.慢慢地呼吸。
That's那是
good.好的。
That's my boy.那是我的孩子。
That's my girl.那是我的女孩。
Focus on my voice now.现在专注于我的声音。
I'm proud of you, baby.我为你感到骄傲，宝贝。
I'm so proud of you.我很为你感到骄傲。
Even if things feel like即使事情看起来似乎并不顺利，但它们是正确的方式。
they don't seem like they're going,they're a right way.
You'll get better.你会好起来的。
You'll get what you want.你会得到你想要的。
You know I'll be there.你知道我会在那里。
I'll be there beside you for it.我会在你身边。
Just.只是。
It's been stressful, right?压力很大，对吧？
And you've been doing your best而且你一直在尽力而为嘘。
right shh.
Shh. It's ok.嘘。 没关系。
Everything will be OK, babe.一切都会好的，宝贝。
Everything will be OK.一切都会变好。
Just first, your只是首先，你的头再低一点。
head down a little while longer.
And listen to my voice听我的声音
forget about everything else忘记其他一切，听我说。 好的？
and listen to me. OK?
Good, good.好好。
That's right.没错。
Good girl.好姑娘。
Good boy.好孩子。
I'm here now我现在在这里
and I'll always be here我会一直在这里
just call my name只要叫我的名字
I love you. Rest我爱你。 让那张漂亮的脸多休息一会儿。
that pretty face a little bit longer.
Darling,亲爱的，
darling, darling, OK.亲爱的，亲爱的，好的。
I love that word.我喜欢这个词。
It's really.真的。
It's really a cute little.真是个可爱的小东西。
I don't know.我不知道。
You call it like你把它叫做爱的期限。
term of endearment.
Yeah,是的，
I'm glad you guys enjoyed that.我很高兴你们喜欢。
Oh, hello.哦你好。
Thank you for all the scripture reading.感谢大家阅读经文。
Can I also ask you to hum coffee?我也可以请你哼咖啡吗？
You'll meet hum coffee for you.你会遇到哼咖啡为你。
Yeah, I can do that.是的，我能做到。
Sure.当然。
I I can hum coffee.我可以哼咖啡。
Just give me a second.请给我一秒钟。
All right?好的？
All right.好的。
It's a drink.这是一种饮料。
A little bit more water.多一点水。
Because I'm running out of water.因为我的水快喝完了。
Yeah, running long water.是的。
Got no more wah hmm.没有更多的哇嗯。
It feels weird to not even sing it连唱都不唱感觉怪怪的
so. Stay away for too long.所以。 远离太久。
Tom, go to bed.汤姆，去睡觉吧。
I'll make a cup of coffee.我会煮一杯咖啡。
For you, and.为你，和。
Yeah, we'll do that.是的，我们会这样做的。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
Tom. Stay awake for too long.汤姆。 保持清醒太久。
Tom called up and said,汤姆打电话说，
I'll make a cup of coffee for you,
and I'll get you up.我会为你煮一杯咖啡，我会扶你起来。
And go and out of bed and I.我和我一起下床。
Promise that. One day.答应那个。 一天。
I'll feel fine.我会感觉很好。
And I promise that one day我保证有一天
I'll feel all right.我会觉得没事的。
And I'll make a cup.我会做一个杯子。
Of coffee with the right amount of sugar.加适量糖的咖啡。
I like我喜欢
and I'll make a cup of coffee over there.我会在那边煮一杯咖啡。
I don't know no sugar.不知道有没有糖。
How you like can你喜欢怎么可以
how you like.你喜欢什么。
So know how.所以知道怎么做。
Long I'll stay for?我会留下多久？
It's OK.没关系。
Knock on your door.敲你的门。
Well, to come down.嗯，要下来。
And get me.并得到我。
Oh, I.哦，我。
Like it when you hold me tight喜欢你紧紧抱住我
You make me feel nice你让我感觉很好
The green in your eyes.你眼中的绿色。
Makes me feel where I'm in sign让我感觉到我在哪里
And I'll make a cup of coffee
with the right amount of sugar我会用适量的糖煮一杯咖啡
How you like get你喜欢怎么得到
and I'll make.我会做的。
A cup of coffee with the right
I'm gonna shake your hand一杯右边的咖啡我要和你握手直到我得到
till I get
how you like你喜欢什么
my. Baby.我的。 婴儿。
Yeah,是的，
it felt more proper to sing it rather.反而觉得唱起来更合适。
Than hum it.比哼哼。
Things on all so requested close to all.一切都如此要求接近所有的事情。
I can probably do that我大概可以做到
and it's a popular one.它很受欢迎。
You guys like a lot to someone
I like a lot. Tell你们很喜欢我很喜欢的人。 告诉
why two.为什么是两个。
Birds suddenly appear鸟儿突然出现
every time you ride in每次你骑进去
I love you a lot.我很爱你。
Yeah.是的。
Let me find it real quick.让我很快找到它。
Close to you跟你走的很近
lyrics歌词
Studio Ghibli songs.吉卜力工作室歌曲。
I think the only我认为唯一
Studio Ghibli song I know is我所知道的吉卜力工作室的歌曲是
the one from Spirit Away Way.Spirit Away Way 中的一首。
That's like how to go again这就像如何再去
a month.一个月。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm mm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯。
It was like,
yeah, I forgot what the name was.就像，是的，我忘记了名字是什么。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
Mm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯。
What was the name?叫什么名字？
One summer day.一个夏日。
Oh, it's one summer day.哦，这是一个夏日。
Oh, all right.哦那好吧。
Thank you.谢谢你。
Oh. Oh.哦。 哦。
Well.好。
Hold on, Anita.等等，安妮塔。
And you get another drink really fast.你很快就可以再喝一杯。
All right.好的。
Here.这里。
Oh. I felt really good.哦。 我感觉真的很好。
It's apple juice.这是苹果汁。
Yeah,
I just opened the thing of apple juice,是的，我刚刚打开了苹果汁的东西，仅此而已。
that's all.
Okay,好的，
now I need to consider before I forget,现在我需要在我忘记之前考虑一下，
and then we can do other stuff.然后我们可以做其他事情。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Hmm, hmm, hmm.嗯，嗯，嗯。
And hmm, hmm, hmm,还有嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm hmm.嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯，嗯。
Hmm hmm hmm.嗯嗯嗯。
Hmm. Mm hmm hmm hmm hmm唔。 嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm
Hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯嗯
Okay.好的。
Okeydokey.Okeydokey。
Uh, shut the by to all means
all of you in Chinese.呃，用中文把你们所有人都关了。
And also, it's the week after
which I have a few chances.而且，这是我有几个机会的一周。
What a shame.真可惜。
I study hard because of you,
especially learning English.因为你，我努力学习，尤其是学习英语。
You always bring me warmth,
and I love you forever.你总是带给我温暖，我永远爱你。
To the good luck of school, ok?祝学校好运，好吗？
And I believe in you. You got this.我相信你。 你得到了这个。
Don't work too hard, though.不过，不要太努力。
Are we doing song requests?我们在做歌曲请求吗？
No, no, no, no, no.不，不，不，不，不，不。
We're not doing song requests.我们不做歌曲请求。
I was just doing a couple for fun,
that's all.我只是为了好玩而做一对，仅此而已。
This is not like a这不像它不是卡拉 OK 直播。
it's not a karaoke stream.
Don't worry.不用担心。
That can wait until next week, OK?那可以等到下周，好吗？
Oh, congrats on the educated.哦，恭喜受过教育的人。
You make a P.O.V.
like urging you to go to sleep.你做一个POV。 比如催你睡觉。
They'll help you a lot.他们会帮助你很多。
I think I already did something like that
tonight.我想我今晚已经做了类似的事情。
Did I not just do that?我不就是这么做的吗？
I feel like I just did that我觉得我只是这样做了。
with the.
Other, you know, the other script
I just read其他的，你知道的，我刚刚读到的其他脚本
at least I think I did.至少我认为我做到了。
I don't know.我不知道。
Puff, thank you for that.噗，谢谢你。
So now,
because he'll buy your arse a Martian.所以现在，因为他会给你买个火星人。
Thank you for this sweet night.感谢这个甜蜜的夜晚。
Can you give us more pep our some ear
massage.你能给我们更多的鼓励我们的耳朵按摩吗？
Or pat that.或者拍那个。
On the ear like this耳朵上这样
like I'm.就像我一样。
Pat, pat, pat, pat, pat.拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍拍
Oh, yeah. Yes.哦耶。 是的。
So I was talking about
you're blowing stuff again.所以我在说你又在吹东西了。
I'm overwhelmed.我承受不了了。
I don't know我不知道
somebody said not too hard,有人说不要太难，但你也不能这样做，比如，低，因为他听不见
but you can't do it too, like, low, too,because he can't hear
right.对。
Because因为
I don't know what enough.我不知道什么够了。
I tried.
I didn't get a chance to practise.我试过。 我没有机会练习。
I did not get you instructors going.我没有让你们教练去。
I didn't anticipate doing
another one of these so soon.我没想到会这么快再做一个。
I don't know.我不知道。
Is that is that right?是这样吗？
Softer, softer.更软更软。
I don't. Are我不。 是
so-and-so's it sound like a typhoon?某某听起来像台风吗？
No, never. No.没有永不。 不。
No more.不再。
No more. No,不再。 不，
you're mean typhoon你的意思是台风或者你的意思不是。
or you mean not the.
I tried it.我尝试过这个。
Maybe it's
just that maybe I'm just not cut out.也许只是也许我没有被淘汰。
For it, you know,为此，你知道，
maybe I'm just not cut out for the ear
blowing stuff.也许我只是不适合吹耳朵的东西。
It's not my.这不是我的。
It feels odd to when I try and do it当我尝试去做时感觉很奇怪
uh, would you mind呃，你介意看看一些每日接送线路吗？
see some daily pick up lines with
the fuck.他妈的。
Boy what you want me
to lot of what you want me to say.男孩，你想让我说很多你想让我说的话。
Pick up lines in a fuck boy voice no,用他妈的男孩的声音拿起台词不，
no, I can't do that. Like不，我不能那样做。 像
I unironically我反讽
or whatever cos though
I don't think I could do that.或其他任何原因，尽管我认为我做不到。
Without like and yet somehow.没有喜欢，但不知何故。
I could do that all boy stuff.我可以做所有男孩的事情。
Crazy, right? Yeah. That's crazy.疯了吧？ 是的。 这很疯狂。
Yeah.是的。
Basically asking to me to be like,
oh, hey, girl, ha ha ha.基本上要求我像，哦，嘿，女孩，哈哈哈。
Fuck. Like, that kind of stuff.他妈的。 比如，那种东西。
And no,不，或者喜欢，我可以喜欢，你想让我问你什么？
or like, I could are like,you want me to ask for your what?
You want me to ask for your number?你要我问你的电话号码吗？
They only say, like, oh,
what kind of music do you listen to?他们只会说，哦，你听什么样的音乐？
I like I like catchy.我喜欢我喜欢朗朗上口。
Oh, what kind of
what kind of car do I ride?哦，我开什么样的车？
I ride a Lexus.我骑雷克萨斯。
I Well, what rank am I in? Legal legends.我 嗯，我在什么级别？ 法律传奇。
I'm Diamond.我是钻石。
Oh, I like I like Supreme.哦，我喜欢我喜欢Supreme。
I, I go to raves, right?我，我去狂欢，对吧？
I love Boba.我爱波巴。
I love Boba so much like that.我非常喜欢波巴。
That's pretty much what you're asking.这几乎就是你要问的。
Me to do right. Now.我做对了。 现在。
I don't know the that's.我不知道那是。
That's very much in. Yeah.那是非常重要的。是的。
At least that's my experience至少这是我对其中很多人的经验。
of a lot of them.
Yeah, that's the ah, I don't know.是啊，就是那个啊，我不知道。
From what
I've seen the Asian football experience.从我所看到的亚洲足球经历来看。
Well like, I don't know.好吧，我不知道。
Like most of them and most of them,
they always.像他们中的大多数人一样，他们总是如此。
Right. A Lexus and have a perm. Yeah.对。 一辆雷克萨斯，有一个烫发。 是的。
And have a perm.并烫发。
No, they have a perm. Right.不，他们有烫发。 对。
And then they say it's all is,
is, is a perm.然后他们说这就是，是，是烫发。
No, it's all natural.不，这一切都是自然的。
It's all natural curls.这都是自然卷发。
Like a liar.像个骗子。
OK, I'm done.好的，我完成了。
I'm done.我做完。
I don't want a clown.我不想要一个小丑。
I'm not clowning on people anymore.我不再拿人开玩笑了。
Kevin, you went, huh?凯文，你去了，嗯？
Yeah, pretty much a Kevin Nealon.是的，几乎是凯文·尼隆。
You guys know OK?你们知道好吗？
So, um, I'm not too sure所以，嗯，我不太确定
what else I could do right now.我现在还能做什么。
Do you guys have any suggestions?你们有什么建议吗？
Any suggestions at all?有什么建议吗？
You only say, Hey, girlie, who says that?你只会说，嘿，姑娘，谁这么说的？
Who says that?谁说的？
Who or what? Who the fuck says.谁或什么？ 谁他妈说的。
Oh, hey, girlie, stay still for me.哦，嘿，姑娘，为我别动。
Like it does.就像它一样。
Not come out really well, child. Ha不是很好，孩子。 哈
I had to put on my cologne.我不得不涂上我的古龙水。
That's put on my headphones for this
because I'm.因为我是，所以戴在我的耳机上。
I want to know till我想知道直到
is this is this the right video?这是正确的视频吗？
What are your你的是什么
I'm not going to listen to that.我不会听那个。
That's all I need to hear.这就是我需要听到的。
I'm not listening to that.我不听那个。
Sorry, guys.对不起大家。
As much as you would want me to.就像你希望我那样。
I don't think I don't think I could last我不认为我认为我可以在该视频中再持续 2 秒。
another 2 seconds into that video.
That's not the. Video.那不是。 视频。
OK, well, I don't care. That's not the.好吧，好吧，我不在乎。 那不是。
That's not the video.那不是视频。
What did
I what did you guys make me watch?我做了什么你们让我看什么？
Oh, no.不好了。
Mm can I have a kiss嗯，我可以亲一下吗
oh, sure.行，可以。
Thank you for the tone.
Oh, give me a second.谢谢你的语气。 哦，给我一秒钟。
Let me do more.让我做更多。
Believable sounds. Believable.可信的声音。 可信的。
Believable sounds.可信的声音。
What are believable?什么是可信的？
Sounds like听上去像
pop, pop, pop, pop.流行，流行，流行，流行。
Like that.像那样。
Was mine.是我的。
It sounds like a it sounds like a, um.这听起来像一个听起来像一个，嗯。
What's it a fish?它是什么鱼？
It sounds like I'm a fish.听起来我是一条鱼。
There's our kiss, though.不过，这是我们的吻。
I almost forgot.我差点忘了。
It sounds like a pop.这听起来像一个流行音乐。
Yeah, pops.是的，流行音乐。
Those are.那些是。
Pop noises.流行噪音。
I don't know if that's what you wanted,
but I.我不知道这是否是你想要的，但我。
I did that.我这样做了。
I hope that's.我希望是这样。
I hope that's correct.我希望这是正确的。
Yes, it was. OK, cool. Cool.是的。 嗯不错。 凉爽的。
Thank you.谢谢你。
You want me to pretend that I'm drunk,你要我假装自己喝醉了，
but I need to explain to my
partner that I'm not drunk.但我需要向我的伴侣解释我没有喝醉。
I don't know how to pretend to be drunk不知道怎么装醉
because. It's因为。 它是
I've never.我从来没有。
Had to, like, pretend to be drunk before
in my life because, like,不得不，就像，在我的生活中假装喝醉了，因为，就像，
why would you need to pretend to be drunk,
right?你为什么要装醉，对吧？
You just,
you know, when you're drunk, you're drunk.你只是，你知道，当你喝醉了，你就喝醉了。
You're just like. A little.你就像。 一点。
Tipsy and kind of, you know, out of it.醉醺醺的，你知道的。
And just don't you have, like,
no inhibitions and all that?只是你没有，像，没有抑制之类的吗？
Yeah.是的。
You know, I found out I found out that你知道，我发现我发现了
what kind of. Drunk was I? I'm not.什么样的。 我喝醉了吗？ 我不是。
I'm not like a sleepy I'm
not sleepy drunk, but I am a我不像一个瞌睡我不是醉醺醺的，但我是一个
I'm a我是一个
I'm like a happy, like, very happy.我很高兴，很高兴，很高兴。
Vibes drunk.醉酒之感。
And also just chill and happy.也只是冷静和快乐。
Yeah, I'd say I'm chill.是的，我会说我很冷。
I'm happy and ah,我很高兴啊，
you would think I'd be horny.你会认为我会角质。
You would think I'm a horny drunk.你会认为我是个淫荡的酒鬼。
But no, I'm not.但不，我不是。
All I really am is just我真的只是
I just feel I just feel like I'm here
to have a good time.我只是觉得我只是觉得我在这里玩得开心。
And I want a hug.我想要一个拥抱。
I get affectionate.我变得深情。
Oh, yeah.哦耶。
I get really affectionate. When I'm drunk.我真的很深情。 当我喝醉了。
I'm like, I want to hug.我喜欢，我想拥抱。
I want to hug people
when I get drunk, like,喝醉的时候想拥抱别人，比如，
and not even, like, get, you know, like,甚至没有，像，得到，你知道，像，
that type of vibe.那种氛围。
Just I want to just hold somebody
or, like, be held by somebody.只是我想抱一个人，或者，就像，被某个人抱住。
Either way, you know, body contact无论哪种方式，你知道，身体接触
it's the help of the top of the comfort它是舒适的顶部的帮助
even more, I think, just enhance it更重要的是，我认为，只是增强它
a lot of people
asking for goodnight kisses right now.现在很多人要求晚安吻。
Sure, I can do that.当然，我可以做到。
You worked hard today, darling.你今天辛苦了，亲爱的。
Goodnight.晚安。
Sleep well.睡得好。
Good luck tomorrow.祝你明天好运。
Come come that they're gone, buddy.来吧，他们走了，伙计。
Come up the hotel上酒店
I don't know which one it was.我不知道是哪一个。
Well, I need.嗯，我需要。
Well, I need what I need.好吧，我需要我需要的东西。
Oh, I in there.哦，我在里面。
I say.我说。
Well, OK. Good night, guys.好吧，好吧。 晚安，伙计们。
For those of you
that want to sleep, rest well, OK.对于那些想睡觉的人，好好休息，好吧。
Don't stay up too long.不要熬夜太久。
Yeah.是的。
Please don't stay up too long.请不要熬夜太久。
I'll be sad我会伤心的
these ones are the.这些是。
I was the.我是。
I'm not doing that again.我不会再这样做了。
The old Katie, go sit in some.老凯蒂，去坐坐吧。
Or. Go. Honey, sit your foot in these two.或者。 去。 亲爱的，坐在这两个中。
Sorry.对不起。
Don't know what she that bullshit.不知道她在说什么废话。
I. I can't some一、我不能
I don't know if it can if like.我不知道它是否可以如果喜欢。
Rips a part of me a rips a part of my soul撕裂我的一部分 撕裂我灵魂的一部分
on. I want to try and see that it's.在。 我想试试看。
Not I'm.不是我。
Sorry you guys only get the
one time in the one time ever对不起，你们一次只能得到一次
you just did.你刚刚做到了。
Know there's a difference.知道有区别。
Between reading it
and like you know during the whole.在阅读它和你所知道的整个过程之间。
A guy Katie Kyrie ill.一个人凯蒂凯里生病了。
Voice and.语音和。
And to.并。
Be all flirty,
you know, is there's a difference there调情，你知道，有区别吗？
yeah.是的。
And that然后
oh, what happen?哦，怎么了？
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
Are all. I.都是。 一世。
Issued thank you for. The are do.发出谢谢。 是的。
Thank you for those 52
and give some stupid holy shit感谢那些 52 并给一些愚蠢的圣洁狗屎
thank you so much太感谢了
help you enjoying the stream so far
and hope到目前为止，帮助您享受直播，并希望您度过一个愉快的夜晚
you're having a good night
you know I can say I can do more你知道我可以说我可以做得更多
I can see some stuff
in different languages如果你们想让我看的话，我可以看到一些不同语言的东西
if you guys want me to如果你们想让我
that is就是
that is not you know to does not bad it's就是不是你所知的，也不是很坏的事情。
you natural me
yeah it's not do not show me是的，它不是不向我展示任何类似的东西。 我不知道。
with anything that's like. I don't know.
Not like不像是。
who tongue you know whatever that你知道谁的语言
the Tagalog thing was他加禄语的事情是
nothing like that没有那样的事
here we go. Uh,开始了。 呃，
oh, yes.哦是的。
Here's a pug par pugi pugi I young（韩语）
pugi I pugi I don
t daughter boring.
You bet.
I think that's it.我想就是这样。
T daughter.
Putting. Your bet.
I don't know if I said that right.我不知道我说的对不对。
I don't know what the fuck that means.我不知道这他妈的是什么意思。
Again, I just know that it was it's very再一次，我只知道那是非常
it's very lewd, isn't it?这很下流，不是吗？
I know it's.我知道是。
Isn't that lewd?这不是瑟瑟吗？
I think that's pretty lewd.我认为这很瑟瑟。
It sounds a little听起来有点
foggy.模糊朦胧。
I am.我是。
Yeah, I think so.是的，我想是的。
And are并且是
my, my friend Allie我的朋友艾莉
ever since she told me about that,
I've had it there.自从她告诉我这件事后，我就一直在那里。
I forgot what it means.我忘记是什么意思了。
I have to ask
somebody. Can someone translate that?我得问人。 有人可以翻译吗？
Yes. It's
it just means let's sleep together.是的。 这只是意味着让我们一起睡觉。
That that's wholesome.那还挺好的。
It's like,
hey, let's go to bed and sleep, right?就像，嘿，我们去睡觉吧，对吧？
It just means that sleep together
that's all that's it's adorable.这只是意味着睡一起，而已，挺可爱的。
My alligator我的鳄鱼
and my.和我的。
Keeper守护者。
oh, I need to哦，我需要
oh. Was that哦。 那是
can you say that bucket?你能说那个桶吗？
What does that mean again?又是什么意思？
Oh, no, oh.哦，不，哦。
Oh, paging means.哦，分页的意思。
Good morning, baby.宝贝早安。
Oh, I see.我懂了。
It's just a very it's just more这只是一个非常它只是更可爱的爱恋条款。
more cute Terms of Endearment.
I don't know.我不知道。
OK, on,好的，
on on you, him韩语
muah， muah
yeah.是的。
And then there is, like,
something. Else to call off that I think.然后有，比如，一些东西。 否则我认为取消。
I don't know.我不知道。
If I. I don't, I'd see I don't know yet
you all.如果我不知道，我会看到我还不认识你们。
But don't people say like Depp但是人们不说像德普吗
or isn't that is that, like, kind of like,
you know, belittling?或者那不是那种，就像，有点像，你知道的，贬低？
I don't know.我不知道。
It's like saying, oh,
you look very handsome.这就像在说，哦，你看起来很帅。
You look very beautiful.
Are you something? I don't know.你看起来很漂亮。 你有事吗？ 我不知道。
Got it.知道了。
I don't know.我不知道。
I'm like that.我就是这样。
People would probably know that人们可能会知道
yeah.是的。
It doesn't mean beautiful. OK,不代表美丽。 好的，
LA on lemon mocha.洛杉矶柠檬摩卡。
Got it.知道了。
Llama on local.当地的骆驼。
Got it was.知道了。
Let me try that again让我再试一次
llama on mocha got it摩卡上的骆驼在当地得到了骆驼。 女孩
llama on local. Girl
that's Korean.那是韩国人。
What did I just say?我刚刚说了什么？
No, Did I say something bad.不，我刚刚说啥不好的东西了吗。
I hope I didn't say anything bad我希望我没有说什么坏话
all it's not.并非如此。
Oh, it just. Means
you want to eat ramen together. That's it.哦，它只是。 表示你想一起吃拉面。 这就对了。
OK, that's not that's
what's bad about that.好吧，这不是坏事。
Well, you guys are making it seem like
it's such a bad thing.好吧，你们让这看起来像是一件坏事。
Let's eat ramen.我们吃拉面吧。
Oh, OK.哦好的。
Play is it's the whole on.玩的是它是全对的。
Hello.你好。
It's the Korean version of Netflix
and chill这是韩国版的 Netflix 和寒意
it is.它是。
Has a bad meanning. What do you mean有一个坏酒。 你是什​​么意思
as of that?从那时起？
Meaning, guys, it doesn't
that doesn't seem to that.意思是，伙计们，这似乎并非如此。
OK, maybe all zen are.好吧，也许所有的禅都是。
Now I know.现在我知道。
What is your guys's languages
versions of like Netflix and chill.你们的 Netflix 和 chill 之类的语言版本是什么。
OK, well,
I guess I know it for it. I'm on.好吧，好吧，我想我知道这一点。 我在。
No go. Got it.不去。 知道了。
OK, for Korean好的，对于韩语
it's sexually suggestive. Oh.这是性暗示。 哦。
I mean that I mean.我的意思是我的意思。
Netflix they you want to Netflix and chill
that's OK.Netflix 他们你想要 Netflix 并冷静下来没关系。
We can we can get Cosby on the couch
and then they can be like,我们可以让 Cosby 坐在沙发上，然后他们会说，
oh, are you still there?哦，你还在吗？
Right where no no.正确的地方没有。
You want to say, 我爱.., I can do that
one more time.你想说，我爱，我可以再做一次。
Yeah.是的。
Oh, 我爱你，姐姐
Russian are lovely俄罗斯人很可爱
Russian俄语
masala.
Call my car cayenne hot
my alcohol Kyle hot.
It means I love you.这意味着我爱你。
Oh, I hope I oh, that's what it means.哦，我希望我哦，就是这个意思。
Can you say ****你能说（其他语言)
to seal
in there
to seal,
seal, seal, seal.
I think it's seal yeah.
To seal
I think that's ask out asking for a kiss我想那是要求一个吻
or you want to give me a kiss, please?或者你想给我一个吻，好吗？
You guys have,你们已经改变了，改变了我的整个拉面。
like, changed,rocked my whole ramen thing.
It doesn't seem that bad to me.这对我来说似乎并没有那么糟糕。
It really doesn't seem that bad.看起来真的没有那么糟糕。
Like who? What, what?像谁？ 什么什么？
It doesn't seem like a.好像不是一个。
Bad thing to be like,
hey, you want to go here? Romance.糟糕的是，嘿，你想去这里吗？ 浪漫。
The other vibe.另一种氛围。
I guess it's like the
the cultural implication from I know I'm我想这就像我知道我不是韩国人的文化含义，所以我的
not Korean, so my
you know,你知道，
I say just suki suki.我说只是,喜欢，喜欢你。
Hey. Suck嘿。
test succumb.
So I cannot.因此我不能。
Oh, my God, that's so hard to read.哦，我的上帝，这太难读了。
Is that Russian?是俄语吗？
That looks Russian to me.这在我看来是俄语的。
Don't succumb, suck OK?不要屈服。
Ah. Oh, no.啊。 不好了。
Oh, no.不好了。
Ah. Do I have any Russians in chat
that know how to, like, stop?啊。 我在聊天中是否有任何俄罗斯人知道如何停止？
Annunciate that because it is hard
to romanised that language宣布这一点，因为很难将这种语言罗马化
sometimes.有时。
None then solid
son Yoda and none non a.
Son that you
don't know what that means不知道是什么意思。
son, huh?
OK. You好的。 你
yeah.
Daniel（其他语言）
yeah.是的。
Daniel
Daniel I.
Mean, I said oh.意思是，我说哦。
Again.再次。
The Z number.
It done well, not on the Lord.
I don't do I don't do French accents.我不做我不做法国口音。
Well,好，
that's like it's a hard accent.这就像它是一个硬口音。
For me.为了我。
I, I should just play more chamber, right?我，我应该玩更多的房间，对吧？
And I can get used to it.我可以习惯它。
Yeah, I know.是的，我知道。
I know how to say I love you.我知道怎么说我爱你。
And in the Russians.在俄语中。
Yeah, like you said.是的，就像你说的。
Yeah, Libya dip. Yeah, yeah.（俄语：我爱你）
Libya dip. Yeah,
let me switch ears.让我换耳朵。
So it's not like deep inside.所以它不像内心深处。
Ah, one ear the entire time.啊，一直一只耳朵。
You want to play?你想不想玩？
Let's play.让我们玩。
Yeah.是的。
I got back into civilian again recently,
and that's all I can think about我最近又回到了平民，我能想到的就是当他说，你想玩，让我们玩我的意思是，我会说
is when he says, you want to play,let's play I mean, I would say
he's a kinky French dude, but I love his
I love his kit.他是个古怪的法国人，但我爱他的我爱他的装备。
His guns are awesome.他的枪真棒。
I love his using his all a lot so far. Is到目前为止，我喜欢他使用他的所有东西。
going to be one of my favourite,将成为我的最爱之一，
you know, my favourite all agents.你知道，我最喜欢的所有特务。
So can you please say ah,所以你能说啊，
yeah.是的。
That's a cute way of calling Elder Brother
in Chinese. OK,那是用中文称呼哥哥的可爱方式。 好的，
ok, geigei,好的，哥哥（救命不要读geigei啊）
older brother
in Chinese
I hope I'm pronouncing this thing.用中文我希望我正在发音这个东西。
Jack.
Jack, you. Are
mm hmm.嗯嗯。
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.好，好，好，好，好，好，好。
I, I don't know.我，我不知道。
I don't know. Out of pronounce it.我不知道。 发音不准。
It's novel.它很新颖。
Don't believe me, sir.不要相信我，先生。
Ha ha ha ha.哈哈哈哈。
Tom, I'm embarrassed now.汤姆，我现在很尴尬。
You guys embarrassing me
and I don't often answer Gaga.你们让我尴尬，我不经常读嘎嘎（哥哥）。
It's Gaga.是嘎嘎（哥哥）。
Oh, then why is the e?哦，那为什么是e？
Why is the E? There are only Josh为什么是E？
don't look at me. You别看着我。 你
got Gaga.得到了嘎嘎（哥哥）。
Gaga?嘎嘎？
Oh, no.不好了。
I got to get this right now.我现在必须得到这个。
I got to learn how to say this. Huh?我要学会如何说这句话。 嗯？
G is k ga ga ga.G是k ga ga ga。
G is k ga ga.G是k ga ga。
Ga ga ga ga ga ga嘎嘎嘎嘎嘎
ga ga ga嘎嘎嘎
a. Close close？接近了吗？
I'm gonna get kick, kick, go我要。。。
get them.读对他。
OK, ok.好的好的。
Look, I feel softer.看，我感觉更柔软了。
A sound.一个声音。
Pop. I don't know I need to listen to it.流行音乐。 我不知道我需要听它。
I need to.我需要。
Like,
listen to somebody say it because, like.喜欢，听别人说，
I do better.因为听别人读我学得更好。
When I hear it.当我听到它。
Like,
I can't just do it based off of letters.就像，我不能仅仅根据字母来做。
Right I need.对，我需要。
To actually hear it sometimes,有时真的能听到，
and then I can do it perfectly after
I hear at least, like, a couple of times.然后我至少听了几次之后就可以完美地做到这一点。
Yeah, ok.是的，好的。
Yeah. OK.是的。 好的。
OK. OK, ok.好的。 好的好的。
OK. Shh.好的。 嘘。
I don't know.我不知道。
I don't know. Man.我不知道。
Does Google translate it?谷歌会翻译吗？
Oh, my god. I'm我的天啊。 我是
I'm sweating.我在出汗。
I am.我是。
I am sweating right now because, man,
you guys really embarrassed me我现在正在出汗，因为，伙计，你们真的让我感到尴尬。
with that one.
I just decided no sobs.我只是决定不抽泣。
OK, ok, ok.好好好。
Yeah. Mm hmm.是的。 嗯嗯。
I'll I'll figure it out.我会想办法的。
I will. I'll figure it out.我会。 我会弄清楚。
I know. Time after this.我知道。 这之后的时间。
OK, so. The.好的，所以。 这。
All right.好的。
I'll.患病的。
I promise I'll I'll.我保证我会的。
I'll learn it for for next time. OK?下次我会学习它。 好的？
Mm hmm. Hmm.嗯嗯。 唔。
I'll I'll try.我会我会尝试的。
I will try better I'll try that ok?我会尝试练习的更好的。
All right.好的。
Now, I'll go back to like, two other现在，我会回到，另外两件事我可以说
other stuff I can say
is on me.在我身上。
Say, Ohio.说，俄亥俄州。
I oh, darling,我哦，亲爱的，
and I'll darling我会亲爱的
darling,宝贝，
darling.宝贝。
Darling.亲爱的。
Darling,亲爱的，
darling,宝贝，
darling.宝贝。
Darling,亲爱的，
darling, oh亲爱的
singing de la la la la la
la la for you does. Oh.
I'm going again right now.我现在再去。
And you say你说
well.好。
We'll see.我们拭目以待。
Why? I hope that's not bad.为什么？ 我希望这还不错。
I hope that's not.我希望不是这样。
I don't know what that says.我不知道那是什么意思。
I don't. Want to say anything that's. Bad.我不。 想说什么。 坏的。
I don't know.我不知道。
I don't know what it means.我不知道这是什么意思。
I ask me, darling.我问我，亲爱的。
I ask me oh yes, me我问我哦，是的，我
it means I like you.这意味着我喜欢你。
Oh, oh, it just means I like you, OK?哦，哦，这只是意味着我喜欢你，好吗？
Another.其他。
Oh, I can do this one.哦，我可以做到这一点。
Yeah, I've done before. OK.是的，我以前做过。 好的。
Cynthia, come up（其他语言）
a chimp.
Come up
yonder
yonder a softball
and the racial pull back.
I mean, dude我的意思是
good boy.好孩子。
Good boy.好孩子。
Good girl.好姑娘。
Muh亲亲。
Hmm.La Sue. Sue.
What is Sue?什么是sue？
I should sue.额。
I sure mean我的意思是
well, I mean, is.嗯，我的意思是，是。
Is that tough of Sue?sue有这么难吗？
All I need. Hmm.我所需要的。 唔。
Is that a name is on, then?那是个名字的吗？
I don't know.我不知道。
Soyung I said say on before（韩语）我之前说过soyung了。 我知道
now. I know
oh, polish.哦，波兰语。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
Column柱子
Cogent.有说服力。
Column C considerC列考虑
call to call and see I.打电话来看看我。
Oh, my God.我的天啊。
I don't know. Polish dialect.我不知道。 波兰方言。
So I'm very unfamiliar with that.所以我对此非常陌生。
Slow, but surely I'm getting more used
to a Swedish dialect, though, because of.慢，但我肯定越来越习惯瑞典方言，因为。
I like, there is like I know我喜欢，就像我知道有一个短语，他说就像，只是可爱的东西。
there's like a phrase that he saysthat's like, just lovely something.
Zavala It's something.萨瓦拉 这是什么东西。
It's just more Swedish cursing. Yeah.这只是更多的瑞典诅咒。 是的。
Don't tell him I said that.不要告诉他我说过。
Yeah, don't tell him I don't tell my said
anything bad.是啊，不告诉他我不告诉我说什么不好的。
He got mad. At me
when I said the word for pussy他生气了。 当我在瑞典语中说出屁屁这个词时
in the Swedish
understandably so,
because I think it's, it's like,可以理解，因为我认为它就像，
I think it's like,
you know, offence is like.我认为这就像，你知道的，就像一种冒犯的感觉。
Why would you say that?“你怎么会那么说？”
You know,你知道，
uh, salamat
malum sama
salamat malum.
I means goodnight.我的意思是晚安。
Right, goodnight对了，晚安
amu yeah.
I said on aniuram but m u我对你（韩语），但是这个不一样
m m you don't know what that means.mm 你不知道那是什么意思。
It means.它的意思是。
Darling. In Vietnamese.亲爱的。 用越南语。
Oh, darling, I'm Vietnamese.哦，亲爱的，越南语。
Gotcha.明白了。
I want to learn more.我想了解更多。
Like I want to learn more stuff
that's equivalent ah.好像我想多学点东西那是等价的啊。
The Netflix and chill shit that we said
before.我们之前说过的 Netflix 和其他东西。
Like, how do you how.喜欢，你怎么样。
Do you guys say like, hey,
one want to come over and do something?你们是不是说，嘿，想过来做点什么？
But in actuality, like, you're,
you're like, you know,但实际上，就像，你，你就像，你知道，这就像一个性暗示，对吧？
it's like a code phrase for sex, right?
Like, of the whole, like a common mockery就像，总体而言，就像一个普通的嘲弄
thing.事物。
To know if anyone has that.想知道有没有人有。
Oh, wait.等一下。
So on said Toradol detail.所以就说Tordol细节。
What Jollibee OJ what's什么 Jollibee OJ 什么是
really.真的。
Jelly.
Really真的？
OK, that doesn't sound right. OK.好吧，这听起来不对。 好的。
Lao low
ball.（老婆）
Yeah. What is what does that mean?是的。 这是什么意思？
I should look,
I should look these things up.我应该看看，我应该看看这些东西。
Lao Paul Alpo.老婆，老婆，老婆
Lao Bo Alpo.
It means old.是老女人的意思？
Lady.吗？（信不信我打你shoto）
It means wife.是妻子的意思。
Oh, it means wife.哦，是老婆的意思。
Ha, it has a lot of juicy meanings.哈，它有很多多可爱的含义。
This is what it says.这就是它所说的。
Why? Oh, why would it have.为什么？ 哦，为什么会有。
Juicy meanings, huh?可爱的意思，嗯？
Isn't it just mean wife. Most of all?
Why would it?它只是妻子的意思吗。 最重要的是？ 为什么会呢？
Why would I have juicy meanings?为什么我会有其他的意思？
What does that mean?这意味着什么？
Juicy. Huh?嗯？
OK. It's flirty.好的。 有点轻浮的感觉。
Oh, oh, it's flirty. OK,哦，哦，很调情。 好的，
that's really cool.这真的很酷。
That's the way to describe it, I guess.我想这就是描述它的方式。
Juicy. Yeah,是的，
ok. OK.行。 好的。
I see. Thank you.我懂了。 谢谢你。
I'm being educated
and being more and more educated我正在接受教育并且越来越受教育
by the day.到了一天。
If all they see is.如果他们看到的只是。
Oh, ok. OK.哦好的。 好的。
All right, Barbie.好吧，宝贝。
Got it.知道了。
I feel like, ok.我觉得，好吧。
I feel like I've embarrassed myself
enough.我觉得我已经够尴尬了。
Were far off
trying to say these and say all this.离试图说这些和说这一切还差得很远。
So I will simply所以我会简单地用一个漫长而草率的吻离开你们。
leave you guys off with a long, sloppykiss.
So, hey, prepare your ears
because it's about to get really,所以，嘿，准备好你的耳朵，因为它真的要开始了，
really personal.真的很个人。
Mm hmm.嗯嗯。
I think that was my mom in the background.我想那是我妈妈在后台。
She probably just sneezed. OK.她大概只是打了个喷嚏。 好的。
And did you hear that?你听到了吗？
Did you hear that?你听到了吗？
Mom, get out of here!妈妈，离开这里！
God! Get out!上帝！ 出去！
Mom, god damn.妈妈，天哪。
There it goes again.它又来了。
There she goes again.她又去了那里。
OK, ok, ok, ok, ok.好的，好的，好的，好的，好的。
It's just me and you.
Just me and you. All right?只有我和你。 只有我和你。 好的？
I just got.我刚得到。
To say bless you.说祝福你。
Yeah, I guess. Bless you.是的，我猜。 祝福你。
Got it.知道了。
Hold on.坚持，稍等。
Hold on a second.稍等一下。
OK, I think I think
I think I got the message clear.好的，我想我想我明白了信息。
Anyways, let.无论如何，让。
Me until我直到
I feel like I'm being ard right now, is
is that the right word to describe it?我觉得我现在很紧张，用这个词来形容它合适吗？
I'm being cuts.我正在被刀削一样。
I don't know.我不知道。
Cock blocked.cockblocked（指性挑逗时被干扰）。
Yeah.是的。
If there is a
there's any way to experience a cock block如果有任何方法可以体验cockblock并像这样好吗？
and be like this ok?
Yeah.是的。
Yeah, wow.是的，哇。
And hmm.嗯。
Mm. Mm亲亲
hmm. No.唔。 不。
Oh, mm mm哦，嗯嗯
mm mm mm mm mm亲亲轰炸
mm mm亲亲
mm mm mm mm亲亲
am I.我是吗
Good boy.好孩子。
My good boy.我的好孩子。
Oh, ok.哦好的。
OK. Oh,好的。 哦，
oh, all right. Oh.哦那好吧。 哦。
Sus kisses.瑟瑟的吻。
You heard a car? Yeah, it was a car.听说有车？ 是的，那是一辆车。
Ignore the car.无视车。
Listen to me.听我的声音啊。
OK? Don't I don't get tired
and get distracted by other things.好的？ 不要被其他事情分心。
Why you look,
why are you focussing on other stuff?为什么你看，你为什么专注于其他事情？
You should be focussing on me.你应该把注意力放在我身上。
Why aren't you focussing on me? Hmm?你为什么不把注意力放在我身上？ 唔？
Hmm. OK.唔。 好的。
I can't do that anymore.我不能再那样做了。
All right,好的，
but i think that is going to be it但我认为今天的梦想就是这样。
for for this dream today.
Yeah.是的。
I don't think I have anything else on the我不认为我还有其他东西
on the menu either.在今天的menu上。
Not uh oh.不是哦。
Hold on. Let me,坚持，稍等。 让我，让我快点
let me quickly
look through any other terminations
that I might have missed.查看我可能错过的任何其他终止。
Yunji. Thank you for that.云集。 谢谢你。
So nation. You're so cute.你太可爱了。
Your face is cute.你的脸很可爱。
Cindy,
thank you for the $6.90 of what I need.辛迪，谢谢你提供6.90 美元。
Well, in the end.嗯，最后。
The birds. Are finally coming out.那些鸟儿。 终于要出来了
A. Melania.答：梅拉尼娅。
Thank you for that. So now, um,谢谢你。 所以现在，嗯，
you know about this Chinese thing?你知道这个中国的东西吗？
Oh, I don't know.
Do I have a Chinese name?哦我不知道。 我有中文名字吗？
I don't know.我不知道。
You know, like, how.你知道，比如，如何。
In other languages are people give like,在其他语言中，人们给予喜欢，
people other
I don't know were just like nicknames.其他我不认识的人就像昵称一样。
And stuff like that. Do I have a nickname?诸如此类的东西。 我有昵称吗？
I don't think I do. It's a shuttle, right?我不认为我这样做。 是摆渡车吧？
And a shuttle.还有班车。
I'm not sure if you know, people call me
anything else我不确定你是否知道，人们叫我别的什么
or, like, some kind of, like, pet name.或者，像，某种，像，宠物的名字。
Yeah.是的。
Not shotom.不是shotom
No, not shotom.不，不要shotom。
Keno. Thank you for that.基诺。 谢谢你。
I'll no into guru. Guru.我不会成为大师。 大师。
Thank you for.谢谢你。
That's on our那是在我们的
teacher Shin申老师
ask sister for a kiss.向姐姐要一个吻。
I hope that what我希望什么
an only thank you for只感谢您的捐赠，并感谢您的捐赠。
the donation as welland thank you for that.
Till now congrats on 300 k.到目前为止，恭喜 300 k。
I've been listening to your stream经过漫长的一天后，我一直在火车上听你的直播，这真的很放松和瑟瑟。
on the train after a long dayand it's been really relaxing and sussy.
And sussy.和色情？
and it was a great way to end the day.这是结束一天的好方法。
Thank you for sharing. No problem. Set up.感谢你的分享。 没问题。 设置。
You enjoyed the time
and have a wonderful time going back home.你很享受这段时光，回家过得很愉快。
OK, stay safe.好的，注意安全。
You're going there.你要去那里。
That's where you make a
thank you for this.这就是你为此表示感谢的地方。
I know I am我知道我是
in depth on you深入了解您的一些植物群。 谢谢你。
some flora. Thank you for that.
Now. Panel, Myanmar.现在。（其他语言）
Myanmar
fearless. Poppy, thank you for the donor.无所畏惧。 罂粟，谢谢你的捐赠。
I recently felt particularly happy
because I met you, although the previous最近因为遇见了你而感到特别开心，虽然之前的
also lived a very happy life.也过着非常幸福的生活。
After knowing you feel more happy.知道之后你会更开心。
I think I understand
what you were trying to say there. And我想我明白你在那里想说什么。
I think you mean我想你的意思是
was it是吗
happy that you got to know me
better through the previous streams?很高兴你通过以前的直播更好地了解了我？
And, hey, I'll be enjoying
more to come there.而且，嘿，来到那里我会享受更多。
Thank you for coming by today.谢谢你今天光临。
I hope it wasn't too.我希望不是太。
Too awkward. For you.对你来说太尴尬了。
The whole lot is similar experience.全部都是类似的经历。
I won't be doing this next week, though.不过，我下周不会这样做。
Because it was just like one more time
to try and feel a little bit因为这就像再一次尝试并对此感到更有信心。
more confident about it.
And I feel like I succeeded in that我觉得我成功了
actually.实际上。
Thank you for that, John. On Zero.谢谢你，约翰。 在零。
I for the till now you play say coffee,
tea or me.我直到现在你玩说咖啡，茶或我。
With a goodnight kiss.带着晚安吻。
You want me to be like.你想让我成为这样的人。
Oh, hey, hey honey, do you want coffee?哦，嘿，嘿，亲爱的，你想喝咖啡吗？
Or maybe you want saw you want some tea或者也许你想看到你想要一些茶
would you like me instead或者你会喜欢我吗？
do think that it's OK?认为它可以吗？
No, just thank you for that dona not to
you know thank you for that dona though不，谢谢你的dona
and the thank you for the five to ones谢谢你的捐赠
OK I can好的，我可以赶上所有这些
catch up on all of them
oh everything anything extreme.哦，一切都是极端的。
You guys you and your friends
have been under a lot of pressure recently各位小伙伴们，最近因为一些工作失误，压力很大。
because of some work mistakes.
How do you relieve the work pressure?你如何缓解工作压力？
How do I relieve work pressure?如何缓解工作压力？
Masturbate自慰
just kidding.只是在开玩笑。
I usually like to play some video games
and I like to sing a lot.我通常喜欢玩一些电子游戏，我喜欢唱歌。
So most of the time, whenever I'm
feeling anxious or stressed out,所以大多数时候，每当我感到焦虑或压力过大时，
I try to我试着
what's it.它是什么。
I try to sing a song or
like sing a few songs that I really enjoy我试着唱一首歌，或者喜欢唱几首我当时真正喜欢的歌曲。
at the time.
And singing really helps take the,
you know, anxiety away唱歌真的有助于消除焦虑
and I get to just vibe out with a,我得到了一个氛围，
you know, with a song
that I've been I'm comfortable with.你知道，用一首我一直很喜欢的歌。
It lets out
a lot of tension from your like,它释放了你喜欢的很多紧张感，
I'll know from your brain我会从你的大脑中知道，当你就像在歌词中，在旋律中失去你的想法一样，
when you're just like lose your thoughtsin the lyrics, in the melody,
singing or video games.唱歌或电子游戏。
So I like playing golf
and fantasy league and you know,所以我喜欢打高尔夫和梦幻联赛，你知道，
Bellerin in Minecraft玩我的世界。
maybe也许你可以学会用中文介绍自己。
you can learn to introduce yourself inChinese.
Are Ni
ni hao or C shot ball.你好还是 sho宝。
Oh, thank you for
thank you for the lesson for today.哦，谢谢你，谢谢你今天的课。
I hope I get more lessons in the upcoming
shootings.我希望我能在即将到来的事件中得到更多的教训。
Teach me more.教我更多。
OK, thank you.好的谢谢。
I would love to that.我很乐意这样做。
That sounds. Cute.听起来。 可爱的。
I would like to learn more phrases
sorry I could use on a daily basis我想学习更多对不起我可以每天使用的短语
like survive if I ever want to如果我想活下去
if I ever needed to use Chinese.如果我需要使用中文。
Really ok.真的可以。
Yeah,是的，
we're going to end it off here guys.我们将在这里结束它。
So be sure to have a good night and所以一定要度过一个美好的夜晚
I don't think we're going to be reading
anybody.我不认为我们会读到任何人。
We're just going to end it off here
and we're going to relax, chill.我们将在这里结束它，我们将放松，放松。
And you sure have a good night.你肯定有一个美好的夜晚。
Have a good rest of your day好好休息一天
off. Here you go.离开。 干得好。
I want to see one more thing,
if that's OK.我想再看一件事，如果可以的话。
If you guys.如果你们。
All right,好的，
Hold on等下
for some of you.对于你们中的一些人。
It's really late, so you can pretend that真的很晚了，所以你可以假装
this is like you're laying down on me or这就像你躺在我身上或
you can fall asleep如果你愿意，你可以在我的胸前睡着，
on my chest if you'd like,
right?对？
Yeah.是的。
Just one more time.就再一次。
Cuddles hmm.听我的心跳。
Goodnight.晚安。
So, Paul.所以
OK, OK.好的好的。
Take care.小心。
And I'll see you next week.然后我下周会见你们。
Uh uh亲亲
uh uh.亲亲
uh ok.好吧。
Um, before we head off,嗯，在我们结束之前，嗯，一定要确保加入不和谐。
um, just be sure to join the discord.
Yeah. If you are. Or.是的。 如果你是。 或者。
If you want to join discord, it's discord.如果你想加入discord，那就是discord。
Social pull.
And be sure to follow on Twitter on the
suffering tea and subscribe on YouTube.
一定要在 Twitter上关注，并在 YouTube 上订阅。
I posted a new YouTube video today
that I think you guys would like.我今天发布了一个新的 YouTube 视频，我想你们会喜欢的。
So check it out, ok. Showed some love. And所以检查一下，好的。 表现出一些爱。
also thank you for 300.也谢谢你的300k。
Again, thank you for a thank.再次感谢您的感谢。
On the on switch.在开启开关上。
We hit this milestone so fast
and it just keeps getting我们以如此之快的速度达到了这个里程碑，而且它越来越大，所以我觉得我无法赶上，但是
bigger and bigger so and I feel like I'mnot able to catch up, but
I hope that I'll be able to handle我希望我能够处理所有新的粉丝
all the new guildies that come on by
and hopefully you guys
can set a good example to希望你们能树立一个好榜样
Night guildies.
All right. Have a good day. OK.好的。 祝你有美好的一天。 好的。
Take care and I'll see you next time.保重，我们下次再见。
Bye bye.再见。
Well, there's another hype train.好吧，还有另一列庆祝活动。
You guys start hype train before I leave.你们在我离开之前开始庆祝。
What's why would you start a hiring before
I had a job offer today?为什么你会在我今天得到工作机会之前开始招聘？
Bruh bruh.
OK, but have a good night.好的，但祝你有个美好的夜晚。
All right. Take care. And I love you.好的。 小心。 我爱你。
OK? Oh,好的？ 哦，
yeah.是的。
I'm big.我变得很大。
There you go. Bye.好了。 再见。