Maybe
I just.
Take my headphones off.
On. Give me a second
Hey, guys.
Good morning.
I actually woke up
and woke up pretty early today for once.
That's kind of surprising.
I didn't think I would wake up so.
Early today for a stream,
but I don't know.
I think I just had
I had a lot on my mind also.
Oh, yeah.
Does the
does the microphone sound OK?
I think some good.
So I sound fine.
So I sound OK.
I don't know, because I just hooked it up,
so I'm not sure if it's like
it's all good, like last time.
Sounds great. OK.
Nice.
Oh, sorry.
I was. What's it called?
We can get a lot of time necessary
to talk after the stream, but I was so
so tired after the collab.
I just wanted to hop off and go,
like, relax and eat some food.
So yeah, it was a lot of chaos and
very hectic and all over the place,
but I had so much fun.
So thank you guys for coming
by and supporting both of us.
Did I sleep well?
Yeah, I did sleep well.
I think I slept pretty early tonight too,
but I only got like 7 hours, but yeah.
Yeah,
it wasn't that. Much sleep, but I.
Still like.
I feel super refreshed, like more
so than usual.
So that's kind of crazy.
Hi, guys. Good morning.
Welcome, everybody.
Ah, good.
Good evening.
Yeah, good evening to some of you guys
because it's like,
I know it's Night-Time
for quite a few of you right now, right?
Yeah.
Also, I.
Did want to say.
We did.
Hit 300 K on the on switch.
Like not too long ago. I think we hit it.
Within one before stream started.
Or maybe yesterday. I don't know.
I just took a look.
Right now
because people are talking about it
and I was like,
Wow, we're already at 300 here.
So that's crazy.
And bronzer 400 on Twitter too.
So guys, that's fucking insane.
I mean, it's rigging.
That's like almost half a million.
And that's like really those are really
big numbers and they don't
it's it's scary.
It's, it's awesome.
But, you know, it's also scary.
But I know you guys understand, right?
Because it's like, it's a lot
it's a lot of people, but
I'm always excited to meet new people. So
I'll tell them, you guildies, I welcome
you with my open arms
and hope you're having a wonderful time
seeing here
congratulations. Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you so much.
That being said, I think.
I will have a. Karaoke.
Celebration next week to say
thank you to everybody for, you know,
just for all the support recently
and the fact that I haven't had
a, you know, karaoke in a while.
I wanted to sing a song.
No, not just a song.
I'll just sing many songs
next time we had a karaoke session.
So I think.
You can expect one probably be
next week and around like.
Friday.
Let's say maybe Friday or Saturday.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
So excited.
Me too. Dude, I'm so excited.
It's been a while
since we've gone to sing anything.
I really wanted to, you know,
I've even I've had, like, the what's it
the motivation to sing again recently.
So that's I've been just, like,
trying out different songs and stuff, but,
yeah, I want to
I want to do karaoke since we haven't done
one, you know, a bit.
And everybody's been doing.
Karaoke lately, so it's been kind of
inspiring me to also do some karaoke too.
Right.
Oh, yeah, right.
Did you guys want to.
Did you guys want to guess?
Hold on.
If you're so weird.
Going back for, like,
was it kissing the ear on the microphone?
I'm still trying to get used to it, but.
Uh. I'll get there eventually.
Like, one of these days,
it'll feel a natural, and, you know,
you'll feel good.
Yeah, you'll feel really good.
Like, it's right if you're not good, but
you'll feel right and I'm doing it
correctly.
That's why. That's when I'm nervous.
Because Not feel.
Good. Yeah.
That's the wrong word.
That's the wrong word to use.
Okay, hold on.
Let me give another kiss.
To OK,
But hopefully everyone's
been having a great weekend so far.
I have a lot.
To do today and tomorrow.
So your boys can be quite busy.
Um. Could you write?
Let me read
through some. Of the donations.
Thank you for the little 500, by the way.
Oh, my God.
I'll see you guys in a lot of
you might have
had some new, new sub
because there was a lot of give some.
Yes, very. Again, big.
Thank you to consider and give notice
for all the gift subs.
From yesterday.
It means a lot, guys. Really
Eve, thank you for the deal. No,
Akari, thank you for the bids.
Thank you, Kate. Congrats. Thank you.
Thank you for the congratulations
to see Sadie.
Thank you for the five months, five months
since one feels like just yesterday
when I found you wondering
because of mortuary assistant.
I'm glad to know that you've been.
Around for that long zero
it and you've been enjoying my consent
since, you know, five months ago.
That's almost half a year.
Have you been having fun?
It's been fun, right?
Also, just thank you for the 10,000
bits as well.
Just thank you for the 10,000. Oh, my God.
Hope you're having a great day too.
Good morning.
And Kimura, thank you for the Jono
Pavi thing for the eight months.
Dear Linh, thank you for the dono
and the 10th year and give subs
around thing for the donation as well.
Shuttle. Woof, woof,
woof, woof.
Thank you for the donation.
Best part of every day is hearing
your voice.
My exact anxiety would break down
disappear in the short period of time
or two.
Or really.
That's so sweet.
I'm glad.
I don't know. It's just like.
I guess I understand
because there are like some things I do
to, you know, relax and just take away
the anxiety from a long, hard day.
But I could never imagine, like,
my voice or, like, just me talking
or just me being here and talking to you
guys would be enough to help that much.
It's like
it's really cool to know, like,
I don't know, just my presence
or me doing
this has a healing effect on you guys,
and it just makes me feel so much better
about myself.
And makes me feel so much better about,
you know, doing what I'm doing right now.
So thank you. Really?
I don't.
I don't get to hear that enough from,
like, anybody.
So thank you.
So I feel like the.
Hold on.
Give me a.
Second.
Like, this might be too high.
I'll bring it down lower.
It might be better.
Yeah.
That's good enough.
OK. OK.
Oh, wait.
Is the music still on?
I just realised. Oh, my God.
I just realised the music was still on.
Holy shit.
I guess I took off my headphones.
I forgot my Spotify was open.
So I just let my Spotify keep going.
On and all.
Until somebody in chat told me like,
Oh, it's still on.
OK, thank you for telling me.
Oh my God. OK,
I appreciated Hopefully we don't get our
I don't get TMZ from that. Hmm.
OK, all right.
So is everything good now?
And he's fine.
You guys can hear me.
It's just me and you.
There's no music now. Right.
I think this is better OK.
Oh. Sorry.
Excuse me.
That's like, hold back a sneeze.
As hold it back because, like,
I don't know, like, sneeze into your ears
or whatever.
That sounds really gross and loud
appearing
under you
for the two to one gift subs. And
anything for the five to one.
I guess I'm still interviewing
for the Don on Anthony.
Thank you for that tone. Yeah.
Could you close your eyes
so I can kiss you on your face?
I mean, if you want to.
OK, come dark.
Come here then.
I. I guess
Did you do it yet?
Did you.
Hello? Did you.
Did you do it
I'm sorry.
I guess you. Did it
Also, Gracie, you are not.
Allowed to dono our dude.
My mods are like the last people I feel
like should be donating to me right now.
But I got it.
Congrats on three, bro.
Today marks one year
since I first followed you.
Thank you for your smiles,
loss, and good times.
I appreciate you beyond words.
I'm so glad to have found this community.
One treat yourself. I will.
Oh, God.
Guys, mods.
You can't do this. Roll
You can just
do so much.
You don't need to give anything.
If anything, I feel like I should be
giving to you guys because you guys keep.
You know,
you help out so much in the back,
during the streams,
and, like, for the server.
I guess you shouldn't be doing that.
For real.
But thank you so much for the downloads.
It means a lot. Just please.
You. It make me feel better if you use.
This money to, like, treat yourself
rather than me to myself, if anything.
So please. Just No more.
No more of that. All right?
And that goes for each
and every one of my months.
Like, I'm watching you guys.
Ash, thank you for the donation.
Congrats on the work you've been doing.
So long,
given so much support to the guilties,
you absolutely deserve so much love.
Hope you have a good time in a weekend.
I will have a great weekend.
Thank you, guys.
And I also have a great stream.
Oh. All right, well, um,
I did a.
I did have some prompts written up.
Not a lot.
I might repeat one of the problems
from last time, too, because I felt like,
you know, it was such a good prompt
and it was, like, super comforting.
So I thought,
why not? I'll take a, like, a,
I'll do a redo of it
or like, you know, just try it again.
With more effort
this time since I'm, like,
a little bit more confident now.
I don't know. Right.
I have one prompts here.
That's like,
Oh, I just got home from work
and you're worried about me
and we're about to cuddle
or something like that.
And then there's another one that's.
I, I don't think.
I want to do this one because, like,
I was writing it last night
before I went to bed,
and I was kind of sleepy
The thing about this prompt
is that it has.
It's like sub dog boy.
Um, and I call you master
and I don't think I want to do that.
Just for.
How about this? How this
if if somebody
Oh, my God.
I know if somebody. Gives 50 subs.
I'll. I'll do that.
The the dog.
Boy one bite
a little later.
Yeah, I'll do a little later.
It's just.
Really, I don't know.
It's like when I write these late
at night, it's,
I don't realise it's like when you draw
or when you do work at Night-Time, right.
And you wake up the next day
and then you look at it or like
one more time you look at it one more time
and you're like wait this is a mistake.
I shouldn't have done this or like,
oh, this looks so bad.
Or like, you know,
you kind of like pull back
and want to like fix it, but
Yeah, but I feel about this one right now.
I have another one
that's kind of like Gouda inspired
because, like,
she did this on her steam one time.
It was like some kind of Cinderella thing.
So I thought, should not be fun.
Yeah.
Never a mistake.
What do you mean,
it's just super, and.
It's really, really embarrassing, dude.
Like,
it's.
There's so much here that I feel like.
Oh, it's.
It's so embarrassing.
I only ever get even stomach
doing this one.
Even even if I did reach that goal.
Okay, I'm going to.
I'm going to. I'm
yeah.
We'll all look back. On that later,
though.
We'll look back on that later.
Maybe I'll feel okay about it.
Oh, Mitzi, thank you for the five.
Thank you for the 50.
Congrats on the educate.
You deserve every single number
and more. The shrooms.
Also the perfect time for me.
Shelia, since it's almost 11 p.m..
Here, I'm glad I get.
To do these kinds of things for everybody
when they're, you know, about
to sleep in the other side of the world.
Since I do feel like, you know, for the
past year plus, I've only been ever been
streaming
for, like, one time zone.
So getting to, you know, to a little bit
more for other time zones is nice.
Alright, thank you for the donations
and thank you for your content.
Thank you for existing
also.
Thank you for the donations Hill. OK,
are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
Guys, guys,
well,
guys,
oh, my God.
Both of you.
Both of you like.
OK, I guess
Oh, see, I didn't think of it.
Of course it's course hidden.
Or is it do it tell. And look here.
Thank you both for.
50 from each of you.
OK, fine. I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I'll just
call and let me just put it back
in the document real quick
because I got rid of it
because I was so
sure I wasn't going to do that one. But.
All right.
No, you guys prove me wrong
every time you guys prove me
wrong on anything.
You for the five artsy ones as well. OK,
Well down, guys.
God damn
I don't know what it is
about the dog boy
that gets everyone riled up,
but ok, I'll try my best
when we get there.
All right.
Just do it now.
You guys just want me to do it now
so I could get out of the way.
It's like ripping off a bandage, right?
It's like when you rip off a bandage.
It's my as well,
so I don't have to, like, do it later.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
OK. Through the ears.
Jesus.
Puppy.
Yeah, puppy. It's puppy.
OK, I got a dog into the puppy mindset
right now.
Yes, I can
I am dog.
I am talking and talking and talking
like Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
But I agree to this.
What compelled me to do this,
I don't know.
See, this is.
I don't. Trust.
I don't trust. One.
A thought shop or two to do like a proper
job at, you know, thinking properly.
OK, let's just get into it.
Hey. Hey, master.
Hey. Master.
Well, plus, hmm.
Hey, master.
Hey, son, wake up.
Come on, get up.
Master. Hmm?
Oh. My sir.
Can we go walkies?
Come on.
I know you're awake.
Get up.
Don't ignore me.
I see you smiling, too.
Hmm. Fine.
Yeah. Oh.
I master
to that.
Get you up
Come on.
Hurry and get out of bed.
Oh, come on.
Get up, please.
Get up.
wolf, wolf
Did you sleep well, master?
Are you going to make me breakfast?
Are we going for a walky?
Today too?
please
Can I maybe get a head pat, too?
Please.
Just.
Just one.
Head part
OK. Maybe a hug too.
Mm hmm.
OK. OK.
OK. Maybe.
Can I get some kisses too?
And some
cuddles? Hmm.
Hmm. Please.
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm.
Hmm. Hmm.
You will
Uh. Uh.
Uh hmm.
Mm hmm.
Hmm hmm. Hmm hmm. Hmm.
Thank you.
I love you so, so much.
Mm You make me so happy.
So soft and warm.
I love how you smile till.
Right.
You feel so good till.
Thank you for taking care of me.
And thank you for loving me. Till
I'm your puppy.
I'm your good boy.
You'll call me good boy, right?
Mm hmm.
Do you like it when I kiss you like that?
Tell me one more
Can you.
Can you call me a good boy till.
I do it?
Mm hmm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
Hmm. Hmm, hmm.
Hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm Oh.
Oh. And my
am I doing good?
Master
love, love.
OK, I did what you asked.
Now, can we go on walkies?
Please, please, please.
Please.
Walkies, please.
Hmm. Hmm.
Thank you.
Thank you, master.
Let's go.
I'll even put a collar on this time.
If if you want
huh? No, it's
not like I wanted you to put it on me.
Shut up.
Let's just go. OK,
Oh, my God.
I'm done. I'm done.
I'm done. I'm done. OK.
OK, it's done.
I finished it.
God fucking damn.
Like my heart with all my heart.
I was like I was digging.
My fingers into my leg
this entire time I was doing that.
Jesus. Oh.
Oh, my God, bro.
Oh, I, I.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. Or you're welcome.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what to say to that.
What the fuck did I do? Huh?
What the fuck was that?
What?
What did I do, guys?
What did I just do?
I don't know what I did.
I'm so sorry.
Aw, you're welcome.
I don't know. I don't know.
Here is your Selby.
Selby dog boy, puppy boy content, whatever
it's called. Man.
Oh, you did great.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
Appreciate the
I appreciate the the pep talk
even though was really embarrassing.
I r I don't think I'll ever
I don't think I'll ever do that again.
I don't think I'll ever do that
ever again.
OK, I'm taking the talking yourself. OK,
that's enough.
They're gone.
I don't know who that was.
I know who I was.
That wasn't me.
That was not though.
That was a something else.
Uh, Maggie, thank you for this honour.
I'd say back what I had said. Dog boy.
It's scary.
I'm foster children.
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I so honoured.
Thank you for that. Done as well.
When I rub your ears and by U.S.
pancakes, I want sushi so bad.
Yes, thank you.
And make a
thank you for the gift sobs and pound on.
Thank you for the donation, HP.
Thank you for the five to ones as well.
The man
uh. Guys, guys.
Guys.
Uh, that didn't happen.
OK, that's.
But that's between. Me and you.
That was Dylan's between me
and you guys are.
Don't that don't so don't tell anyone else
about what we just did today, ok?
What what happens in the stream
stays in this stream.
What you guys heard
and what you guys know.
It's like it's like forbidden knowledge.
You keep it here, ok?
We don't we don't tell anybody
else. We don't talk about it.
You know
that song like we don't talk about Bruno.
Yeah, it's exactly like that.
Just don't talk about it, OK?
Just don't talk about it.
I'll bite your hand off
oh, god damn, bro.
Stupid soul.
So stupid. OK.
Well, I'm.
I'm flustered now.
I'm I'm really flustered
from whatever just happened.
So my my brain is kind of like
broken.
I'm like, I'm like,
mind break tagged it at the moment.
You guys, the guilties.
I've have mine break tagged me
and it's only been l how long is it.
It's only been 30 minutes.
Unlucky, dude, unlucky
do not kill the part of you
that is cringe kill the part that cringes.
Thank you for the donation
and wise message Noa
I'll take that to heart
Asla thank
you for the fight the ones in the cage
thank you for the 50
and just thank you for the 30
am I practise blowing.
Yeah I can blow
like blow.
Into blow into your ear not you know you
you know I can try again
but I don't think it's
I don't think it's going to go too
well I'll try Lleyton Murray.
No, maybe.
I don't know
it it's so obvious.
Why be embarrassed.
I really admire your bravery
and confidence.
Thank you.
It takes confidence to be somebody's
dog. Boy
or puppy boy, whatever you call it.
OK. Oh.
Well, that's done.
I let me see.
Let me check something.
I do want to try something
as well.
Like, I'm
going to go through like a string of words
or like a string of phrases
and try to, you know, bring some comfort
to people that might feel
a little doubtful of themselves.
Or maybe there are some days where
you just feel like you can't I don't know.
You feel like you have a
lot of answer on not
you have a lot of expectations.
And, you know, sometimes you just don't
want to
it's sometimes it's too much, right?
There's a lot of expectations on everybody
and it can be so heavy.
And I understand that so
I guess this is like my little thing
for people
that have so much on their shoulders
and they are
they don't know what to do,
I guess.
So hold on.
Can you hear that?
Yeah, OK.
All right.
Yeah, it's cuddle time.
You want to call it that?
It's cuddle time.
Sure.
Yeah, my heart is beating fast.
I'm embarrassed, dude.
You're doing great.
I believe in you.
You're doing your best.
And I'm.
I'm really proud of you.
That's it.
And you guys can hear me swallow, too.
I hope that's not embarrassing.
I don't know.
Can you hear me? Swallow, huh?
I never thought about that.
It's OK.
Everything will be OK.
I'm so, so proud of you.
You're going to do amazing.
I'll be here with you all the way
murder's OK.
You can do it.
And don't worry, I'll stay by your side
till the very end.
I couldn't help myself.
I had to say it.
It's like that one.
Mean, you know,
guys, I'm like, this is.
I'm like a whole package, OK?
Just remember that.
You can't.
You get, like, the mirror and you get the,
you know, the soft side,
so you got a yardstick.
Take it for what it is. Boys and girls.
OK, you
can do it.
Keep moving for it.
All right.
I got your back
you'll succeed.
I know you will.
Trust me.
You're beautiful.
And you shine brighter than the stars
and the moons in the sky.
I believe in you.
OK, I'm
proud of. You.
Oh, yeah, OK.
Yeah, I know. My heart break.
My heart rate is high.
I'm just nervous.
I'm just really nervous, that's all.
All right.
That's enough.
Get off my chest now.
I hope that was good.
I ah.
I just want to try something
akin to, like, you know,
a nice hug, a nice cuddle
and having somebody there
to tell you you're doing great.
And you're doing OK.
All right, all right.
So we drink more tea.
Tim, thank you for the.
Oh, thank you for the doll. No,
and Nancy, thank you for the towel.
No. Is well,
straight out crying right now.
No, you can go. Please don't cry.
Nauseated. Don't worry.
All of you are doing great. Trust me.
I don't know what kind of battles each
and every one of you have and
that's why I want to talk about, like,
a lot of time, I try to go into a mindset
that you don't know anybody.
I don't know you.
You don't know me.
And, like, we have a lot going on
behind what we show everybody else, right?
And so you guys are better at lying
than other people and, like, hiding,
you know, what you're going through.
So for those of you that are, like,
hiding that
I don't know what you got going on, but
it's like a little
message for me to say,
hey, you got this, OK?
I don't know what you're going through.
But I feel like you'll be able to do it
because you're my guild members.
I believe in you.
You're here at the Avengers
Guild for a reason, right?
I don't know.
I don't think my guilds or whatever,
you know,
gets get overtaken by a small challenge.
So I have more faith in
you guys than they might think.
Some other people might think
of you.
Thank you for the donation as well.
Do you remember the song Before
I Close My Eyes?
All right.
I still can't believe you remember that.
Hold on.
Do I remember?
you want me to humm it?
I think I remember how it goes.
Hmm. Hmm, hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm.
It's an odd song.
It's like it repeats the same melody over
and over again.
Name it down to sleep.
I pray Lord my soul to keep.
I hope it's not too late for me.
Yeah, I think it goes like that.
Mm hmm.
Changing in the heart.
Then come
hmm. Yeah.
It's been awhile.
Isn't it an old one?
I can't believe you remember that.
Yeah.
It's been so long since ever since I sang
anything related to that, but, hey,
that's really. It's really nice, dude.
Thanks for reminding me.
I used to like it a lot more back
then than I do now, I guess.
But you know,
you grow out of certain songs.
You really do. And
I know now I'm listening to a bunch of
a bunch of ki pop and rock,
and I'd say an R&B
my music tastes
change a lot over the years.
It happens, right?
Yeah.
Happens
you'll miss hum Isabel's lullaby.
Oh, is it.
Is that the one that's from a
that's the one from Promised Neverland.
Right.
Hold on.
How did he go again?
Fuck.
It's been so long
since I've watched The Enemy.
You kind of went like.
Hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
It was like that, and I don't remember the
rest for some reason.
Yeah,
it's been
a long time since I've watched it.
It's a it was a great anime.
I love the the first arc of that series.
It's really beautiful.
Yeah, that lullaby is.
I'm. I can't continue.
I don't know how to. Continue, though.
I don't know how to continue.
That's been.
I don't know.
And, uh, you brought you.
Bring back a lot of memories
about the show, though, so
I'm not karaoke stream, by the way, guys,
so I don't the
I can sing anything,
but I can, you know, just do a little bit
Hold on.
I think,
I think some people want more,
more attention
so give me a sec.
How Oh, yeah,
yeah.
Yeah.
Oh, uh,
uh, mm mm mm
mm well.
Wow. Mm
mm mm
mm well.
OK. Oh, oh.
OK, oh.
It's.
Just not there because my lips,
my lips are going to, you know, to what
your young will, to what
I really hope
the Iraqis sound good to you guys.
Like,
I've been trying my best
to find the right spots,
and hopefully I'm hitting the right spots
for that.
You know what they say.
Practise makes perfect. Yeah.
Or practise
more.
Thank you for the donation.
Today's or one month
anniversary of liking you
are welcome back from one month tour
and the donation is well and mincey.
Thank you for the demo.
Glad you found my strings.
You thank you for being so amazingly kind.
And so the voices. So call me as well.
I'm glad
that you find comfort in these times
when we do get like a moment like this
and it's not like all the time chaotic
and yelling when we play like overcooked
or a whale or like it takes two or.
I don't know. Something
where I am like
balls to the walls, you know,
I'm glad I get to have moments like this
so you guys can just chill back.
And I can also chill back since I'm
I don't want to.
Oh, no.
I want to be,
you know, yelling all the time,
like, loud all the time.
I enjoy my quiet
I feel like everyone enjoys their quiet.
So it's nice to take some time
like this and
embrace some solace once in a while.
And that's what we're doing right now.
Just enjoying some moments of solace
also I'm running out of tea.
T Oh, my God, bro, I'm running out of tea.
Ahh.
I think
I just drank too much earlier on
because I was nervous
from the Dog Boy stuff.
I think
there is another prompt.
Yeah.
Here we go.
There's another prompter
I did want to try out.
It's not very on
ASMR leaning, but
it's like Cinderel.
It's kind of cinderell
because I saw a video
of someone doing something like this
and I was like, oh,
I'm going to try this
so I guess I'll give it a try.
Oh, God, yeah.
Oh, God.
OK, give me a second.
OK, I'll put on the face
I mean, there's a way to find the face.
Check it on.
Cut off. OK,
how do I approach this
without embarrassing myself? OK.
Oh, a simply, I didn't know.
You walk this way.
Oh, I'm very in front of your house, huh?
Oh, no, I.
I wasn't looking at it
or looking for you or anything.
I just.
I happened to be walking by
and and I noticed
Mark, I was, like, walking by,
but. OK, OK, fine.
The truth is.
I wanted to give you something.
Listen, don't get. Me wrong,
but I was just up till two. A.m.
making lunch for school today.
And I know.
Hamburgers steak just happens
to be your favourite, and I was making.
Some, and I want to know if you would like
some, and I had extra.
Be grateful.
Like, OK.
How do I know it was your favourite?
I, i,
i ok.
That's it.
Ah. Oh.
I don don't look at me.
You did.
And my.
Ears are so red.
My ears are so fucking red from that.
You guys have no idea.
My face is so hot.
I am. I'm flustered beyond imagine.
How did that get
me more. Flustered than. The.
Jesus are. The.
The screaming.
Yeah you know, it's it's it's called
you got to put in some.
An embarrassment factor so I like a
got to be flustered.
Shut up.
Don't look at me shut up.
Don't, don't look at me.
I'm just kidding
you can look at me if you want
but since some people asked
yeah you can listen but
I don't know if, like, people ever
to just, like, a stream of thought.
Like,
they put the microphone up to their heart.
It's like, oh, poor me,
you've had a bad day.
And I'm coddling you in brackets.
You're laying on my chest and can hear my.
Heart rate or heartbeat.
Yeah,
you know, I mean, bro,
you know what I mean? Did.
Yeah.
Gail Foster.
Yeah, I did.
Stop sobs.
You don't have. To say it like that.
If you want to say it like that.
Just going to call me out OK?
Oh, that's really stuff on YouTube.
Wow. Really?
That's really cute.
Did I know about that?
OK, this next prompt that I wanted to try
leaned along the lines of
what's it
as opposed to last time.
It's more like
this time I'm going to.
It's it's.
Something similar.
It's something similar, right? So
just more wholesome shit.
Something more wholesome.
Again, nothing lewd,
just only wholesome vibes.
Derrick song
but no, I don't believe in that.
Say so. It's not real to me.
I firmly believe Say So is a cult.
It doesn't exist
everybody.
Everybody is lewd to a degree.
Even the most special person
you might have, you might have seen right
especially me.
What OK,
so let me see.
What are we doing now?
Give me a second.
I'm looking for it.
OK, here it is.
OK, oh, boy.
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
Only time, only time.
Only time.
On their time. On their time.
On their time, on their time.
I mean, sister on me is our brother right?
When my friends are, I was like, chilling.
Chilling off each one of them.
And I kind of brought it up
and they were telling me to say it
in like in different ways.
And one of their favourites was like
when I did it in like a questioning
tone, like I think those.
All on that song,
on that song,
on that song.
Oh, I need some.
Like in it yeah.
Like asking them something
or like asking something from them.
It's like a,
I don't know.
I don't know what the appeal of it was.
OK, oh, OK.
I think I'm good to try this one out.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Oh, boy.
Oh. Hey, baby.
Sorry I got back home a little late
where can we stay?
A little longer than I wanted to, but
I brought back some ice cream
as an apology gift.
Oh. Is everything OK?
I didn't make you sad or anything, did I?
Did I worry you again?
Oh, sorry, honey.
You know how busy I am.
It's not easy, but
I promise I'm not overdoing it.
I just.
I really
want to impress my co-workers, and
I want to make you happy till.
I mean it.
Yeah, I mean it.
Don't sell yourself so much silly.
I want nothing more than to come home
as soon as possible to my darling
oh, come here and cuddle me, OK?
That's it.
Yeah.
How'd you sleep today?
I wish I got a little more chill,
but it doesn't help.
I had a nightmare
you know, I've been having
the weirdest dreams lately.
No, I'm not going to.
Just tell you.
It's embarrassing.
You'll make fun of me.
Oh, you'll have to pretend
like you don't know either.
Besides the nightmare.
It's not like I really dream
about anyone else.
Besides, you
don't have to tease me so much.
You know that
you're bully
fine.
I just want to follow you.
Then how about that?
Oh. You want it that badly?
Oh, I'm sorry.
OK. OK, sorry.
Sorry.
I don't tease you like that again.
Fine.
Come here.
I'll hold
your can you.
Know, I worry.
About how you treat yourself till since
I'm not the only hard worker here.
Take it easy.
Once in a while. OK,
maybe we should go on a date
to the Spring Festival together.
The flowers are all blooming
right now and.
To. Be great.
Take pictures together, right?
Yeah.
I want to see the flowers.
So feel
you're really beautiful, too.
More beautiful than any of them.
Was that you? Cheesy.
Sorry.
But, you know, I mean that, right?
You make me so happy
and you smell good.
And you look so stunning in the sunlight.
OK, ok.
I think that's enough cuddling, though.
I think it's about time
we make dinner soon.
Right
now, it's ok.
You can rest a little while longer.
I can take care of dinner tonight.
No, I don't need any help.
Please just rest if you need it.
OK, babe,
you can help out a little later
with dessert
if you want
now, close your eyes.
That's it.
Good.
Good boy.
Good girl.
You've always liked forehead
kisses, right?
Yeah, I know you do.
And I'll wake you up soon.
Sleep well, baby.
I love you.
Goodnight.
OK, that was.
Yeah, that was one.
My friend
wrote for me.
Because I had no idea what to do.
And she was like, you know,
I think something a little.
A little cheesy romantic would fit.
And then I was like, sure, why not?
So, hey, I tried.
I didn't
I just like my first, like, you know, time
reading through the entire thing
since he gave it to me.
He's really cute.
That's really cute, though.
My two are
not too weird.
Sorry.
That's a stretch.
Really.
Second
I think you should those right.
It felt so cheesy.
It felt so cheesy, dude.
Like, Oh my God, there's so much
mozzarella and and chowder everywhere.
When I was reading through it
I thought
it was cute though.
Know as long as you guys liked it
then that's all that matters.
Sorry.
Cheesy is.
Good, Ivan.
Yeah,
everyone likes some cheese, but, man,
it's like
there's.
You can have
you can have too much cheese, right?
You can have a little
too much cheese sometimes. So
it's on.
So take a shot every time. She says,
don't look at me tonight.
Oh, my God.
You're going to get very inebriated on
very, very inebriated.
Indeed.
Thank you for the $13 chateau.
You're Sookie.
I want to give you a big hug. Then do it.
How are you?
Come here and give me a hug. Then
Oh, yeah.
I remember last.
Time there a song tell me to do a dipen.
And then it came out really weak. Like
it sounded really.
Ah, baby,
and people made fun of me for it
because it was so weak.
But it's. I can't.
If I do it too loud, then.
It's going to hurt your ears. Right?
So I'm not going to do that.
That's. I didn't want to do that.
Yeah, it was like it was last time
it's going to break anybody's
ears too early.
Right?
Something for the kids.
Oh, no.
Good morning to you
and good night to myself.
Good night.
Did I hear any good one
other? Thank you for the zone.
I, too, was so comfy.
I'm almost falling asleep.
How many of you guys are on your phone
right now?
I want to know again
how many people are listening
to me on their phone or on the PC?
Yeah,
oh, that's a lot of people
listening on the phone.
Oh, my goodness. Wow.
Yeah, a lot of phone users.
I mean, it makes sense.
Some people are still in bed, right?
A lot of people. Just
rolled into bed
and they might pass out. So
Sunset iPad. Wow.
I haven't used an iPad in such a long
time.
It's been like years.
I think since I've gone to touch one
but I hope you guys enjoyed that
little prompt
if you have any.
What's it
if you have any small requests,
you can let me know either through
chat or through donations or whatever.
I can try and do them
if you want for the rest of the stream,
like something that's doable.
Nothing like too much, of course,
but I'll read through it
and if I can do it, I'll try and do it.
Like say a phrase like I'm our last time.
So and try to give me a say
that skirmish line or whatever.
And I was just
I free balled.
It ends is pretty, you know,
I'd say it was close, right?
Kind of miaow is it?
Everyone wants him yell.
I like miaow like miaowing.
I guess when I hear cats for
yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I yeah.
Well,
you well.
I don't know how to miaow dude.
I don't think I know. I don't know.
It's it's not
it doesn't come as easy as like,
like, like dog does.
It's hard to do both.
It's not like I'm pick and choose
voice actor.
She can do a lot uh.
A wolf
d wolves.
Well, well,
well, well.
Oh, hold on.
Give me a second.
I think I
yeah, give me a quick second.
Guilties hold on.
Sorry.
I thought I heard somebody at my door.
I don't think anyone was there.
On your on your on your
buddy.
Guys like.
The O'Neals so much.
You know who I blame?
I blame.
I blame the boys
for for influencing that
yeah.
All of are.
All them are.
Quite an influence in
you know, that's ok.
It's totally fine.
It's adorable.
Oh. Katherine,
your friend is going to have a birthday
and a wedding very soon.
Can you give them a happy birthday
and happy wedding blessing?
I can say. I can just say, hey,
happy birthday.
And to help
you enjoy your wedding to your friend.
Have a wonderful day.
Did I'm not.
Thank you for the Tano
attending marks here.
Three months as being a guilty, holding
you and smiling you my imagination.
No, thank you, darling.
Thank you for being around for so long.
I know
some of you people of
your voice and words
and your heartbeat helps me a lot
can you call me your little puppy, please?
I thought I was the puppy here
which 1 a.m.
I, owner or puppy?
You have an exam in two weeks
and in a week?
In two days.
Can you bully you into studying?
You want me to bully you into studying?
How do I do that?
I don't look like.
I listen to myself trying to be, like,
you know, assertive.
And I could not take it seriously.
Like, last time,
it made me so embarrassed guys.
Like,
I heard it, and I was like,
no, that does not feel right.
I can't.
I can't be like, oh, go.
Go study right now
or go do your go to your work.
Be word, you know,
or or
go a fucking
be responsible.
You a whore.
I don't like that
that Zaza doesn't come after that song.
And doesn't come out.
It's on to all
employees.
I don't know.
I feel like maybe it's not meant for me.
I try and.
I try and I try. Trust me, I do.
I really do.
But it always like, you know, comes back
up and just makes me feel like.
Well,
it doesn't feel it doesn't feel right.
Doesn't feel natural.
It's not even about tough.
It's like involving a top or it's on.
It's just like, you know. That being mean.
Or like degrading.
I feel like being mean
and degrading is not my forte.
And even though
I tried it before, it's like
doing it on the spot, it's kind of like.
Well, I don't want to be mean to you when.
You just, you know,
I mean, you did give me permission
to be means you.
So I guess that's different
well,
so are you going to hear me
stretching a lot?
Because again,
I woke up not too long ago, so.
I need to.
Crack my bones and my back
yeah.
Cracks a little bit.
I I feel like when you stretch, you should
hear your bones crack like a little.
It's because you're, like, getting rid
of all that pent up gas or whatever.
It's in between your bones.
OK, oh, we were one K away from
from 400 on.
So they're really.
Really
hold on.
I didn't know a lot.
Oh, my God.
We are
oh, my goodness.
Oh, my goodness.
Did you write a really close
thank you, guys.
That's really.
Two and one day
dots.
You milestones and ones a.
Pug. Pug
oh, thank you for another dimension.
Can you whisper in my ear
like last time? Hmm.
I think I can when I get
the last, like, I might read
through the script that we did last time.
Again,
for Fonzie's
because that one was really good.
I'm proud of that.
I think it'd be really nice
to go through that again.
Yeah,
so it's a very it's
a very sweet little one.
Little message
for for anybody,
whether it's your first time here
or like you're hearing again,
I feel like it's
it gets a
comforting
idea or like a comforting message thrill.
And that's all I want to do.
So on.
Yeah, give me a second. I'll do that.
I'll probably do that.
I just need to clear my throat real fast.
All right, hold on.
OK, I don't know if you guys can hear
that.
I think my
there's like, something going on outside.
I was.
I'd ok
am I eating
and my eating?
No, I'm not eating.
I mean.
I ate before this, you know,
if that's what you mean.
I'm not eating right now.
You know?
Hold on, hold on. Give me a second.
I, I could, I could
I could do this
yeah.
Some people like.
The crunch right
yeah.
It's more pretzels.
People like.
That's a
when I crunch on the
hard pretzels from my bag.
I swore aloud.
What do you mean?
I swallow loud? Well,
you can hear that to.
Oh, my God, you can hear me swallow like.
Oh, God, dude.
Holy shit.
I didn't know that OK?
Nah. It's water.
I was just drinking some water. OK?
But I think I'm good to a read there.
Another part, another prompt.
So give me a second
a swallowing is somewhere. No.
All right.
We did this one last time,
but I wanted to do it again.
OK, so
oh, you're still in bed, darling.
It's been 2 hours,
and you've been scrolling
through twitter and ticktock all morning.
Are you enjoying yourself?
You had a hard day.
Yessiree, babe.
Oh, I know you work so hard all the time,
but if you keep working yourself
like this, you're going to burn out
you've had a lot on your plate lately,
and we haven't gone to go out
much to get either.
This everything OK?
I know
work is important,
but you should remember that
you're the most important
don't try and overdo it, please.
I know you can be a little too nice
sometimes and take on too much
oh, I just.
I want you to value yourself more, babe.
OK, you know, you.
Mean the world to me.
Have you been eating enough lately to
sorry?
I just worry about you a lot.
You know,
well,
it's nice to spend the morning
like this to ourselves.
Yes, come here.
Let me take care of you today, OK?
I'll make you breakfast after this
till now.
What does my love once eat today, huh?
Omelettes, bacon,
hash browns.
Hash browns
actually sound really good right now.
Maybe I can make an egg souffle.
I can make some pancakes
and try a new recipe.
Sorry.
I'm just this hungry too. I guess
maybe if you're feeling better,
we can make it together.
If you want to make it together,
you're not feeling it.
Oh, honey,
you have to take care of yourself
tomorrow, OK?
You know,
you can lean on me more too, right?
You love me, right?
I love you, too.
It's OK to ask for help.
It's OK to feel a little vulnerable
to shh.
That's it.
Let it out.
Good bye.
Good girl.
You're amazing.
You're amazing
and special.
In one of a kind.
Nights.
I'll never want to see you hurt
you too.
A lot every day.
And it's okay to take some time
for yourself once in a while.
It's OK to be a little greedy
and need some more affection.
All right.
Just ask me and I'll be there for you.
I'll always be there for you.
You've been doing so well.
You don't need to try so hard
all the time.
You're really inspiring.
Not only to me,
but to so many other people.
You might not even realise
I'm not lying either.
I promise.
So what would you like me to do for you
today, darling?
I can clean up while you sleep. Why?
I can make all the meals for today.
Maybe I can do all your chores till
you just want my company
you know you have all the time, right?
Oh, on
sorry.
I thought I heard something outside me
that's on my room.
You just saw my company.
You know,
you'll always have it all the time, right?
Silly.
As if I'm going to go anywhere
OK? I can do that for you.
Anything for you.
My hard.
Little worker. Hmm.
Deep breaths, ok?
Breathe slowly.
That's
good.
That's my boy.
That's my girl.
Focus on my voice now.
I'm proud of you, baby.
I'm so proud of you.
Even if things feel like
they don't seem like they're going,
they're a right way.
You'll get better.
You'll get what you want.
You know I'll be there.
I'll be there beside you for it.
Just.
It's been stressful, right?
And you've been doing your best
right shh.
Shh. It's ok.
Everything will be OK, babe.
Everything will be OK.
Just first, your
head down a little while longer.
And listen to my voice
forget about everything else
and listen to me. OK?
Good, good.
That's right.
Good girl.
Good boy.
I'm here now
and I'll always be here
just call my name
I love you. Rest
that pretty face a little bit longer.
Darling,
darling, darling, OK.
I love that word.
It's really.
It's really a cute little.
I don't know.
You call it like
term of endearment.
Yeah,
I'm glad you guys enjoyed that.
Oh, hello.
Thank you for all the scripture reading.
Can I also ask you to hum coffee?
You'll meet hum coffee for you.
Yeah, I can do that.
Sure.
I I can hum coffee.
Just give me a second.
All right?
All right.
It's a drink.
A little bit more water.
Because I'm running out of water.
Yeah, running long water.
Got no more wah hmm.
It feels weird to not even sing it
so. Stay away for too long.
Tom, go to bed.
I'll make a cup of coffee.
For you, and.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Hold on.
Tom. Stay awake for too long.
Tom called up and said,
I'll make a cup of coffee for you,
and I'll get you up.
And go and out of bed and I.
Promise that. One day.
I'll feel fine.
And I promise that one day
I'll feel all right.
And I'll make a cup.
Of coffee with the right amount of sugar.
I like
and I'll make a cup of coffee over there.
I don't know no sugar.
How you like can
how you like.
So know how.
Long I'll stay for?
It's OK.
Knock on your door.
Well, to come down.
And get me.
Oh, I.
Like it when you hold me tight
You make me feel nice
The green in your eyes.
Makes me feel where I'm in sign
And I'll make a cup of coffee
with the right amount of sugar
How you like get
and I'll make.
A cup of coffee with the right
I'm gonna shake your hand
till I get
how you like
my. Baby.
Yeah,
it felt more proper to sing it rather.
Than hum it.
Things on all so requested close to all.
I can probably do that
and it's a popular one.
You guys like a lot to someone
I like a lot. Tell
why two.
Birds suddenly appear
every time you ride in
I love you a lot.
Yeah.
Let me find it real quick.
Close to you
lyrics
Studio Ghibli songs.
I think the only
Studio Ghibli song I know is
the one from Spirit Away Way.
That's like how to go again
a month.
Mm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm mm hmm.
hmm hmm hmm.
It was like,
yeah, I forgot what the name was.
Mm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm.
Mm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm.
What was the name?
One summer day.
Oh, it's one summer day.
Oh, all right.
Thank you.
Oh. Oh.
Well.
Hold on, Anita.
And you get another drink really fast.
All right.
Here.
Oh. I felt really good.
It's apple juice.
Yeah,
I just opened the thing of apple juice,
that's all.
Okay,
now I need to consider before I forget,
and then we can do other stuff.
Mm hmm.
Hmm, hmm, hmm.
And hmm, hmm, hmm,
hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm hmm.
Hmm hmm hmm.
Hmm. Mm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm
Hmm hmm hmm hmm
hmm hmm hmm hmm hmm
Okay.
Okeydokey.
Uh, shut the by to all means
all of you in Chinese.
And also, it's the week after
which I have a few chances.
What a shame.
I study hard because of you,
especially learning English.
You always bring me warmth,
and I love you forever.
To the good luck of school, ok?
And I believe in you. You got this.
Don't work too hard, though.
Are we doing song requests?
No, no, no, no, no.
We're not doing song requests.
I was just doing a couple for fun,
that's all.
This is not like a
it's not a karaoke stream.
Don't worry.
That can wait until next week, OK?
Oh, congrats on the educated.
You make a P.O.V.
like urging you to go to sleep.
They'll help you a lot.
I think I already did something like that
tonight.
Did I not just do that?
I feel like I just did that
with the.
Other, you know, the other script
I just read
at least I think I did.
I don't know.
Puff, thank you for that.
So now,
because he'll buy your arse a Martian.
Thank you for this sweet night.
Can you give us more pep our some ear
massage.
Or pat that.
On the ear like this
like I'm.
Pat, pat, pat, pat, pat.
Oh, yeah. Yes.
So I was talking about
you're blowing stuff again.
I'm overwhelmed.
I don't know
somebody said not too hard,
but you can't do it too, like, low, too,
because he can't hear
right.
Because
I don't know what enough.
I tried.
I didn't get a chance to practise.
I did not get you instructors going.
I didn't anticipate doing
another one of these so soon.
I don't know.
Is that is that right?
Softer, softer.
I don't. Are
so-and-so's it sound like a typhoon?
No, never. No.
No more.
No more. No,
you're mean typhoon
or you mean not the.
I tried it.
Maybe it's
just that maybe I'm just not cut out.
For it, you know,
maybe I'm just not cut out for the ear
blowing stuff.
It's not my.
It feels odd to when I try and do it
uh, would you mind
see some daily pick up lines with
the fuck.
Boy what you want me
to lot of what you want me to say.
Pick up lines in a fuck boy voice no,
no, I can't do that. Like
I unironically
or whatever cos though
I don't think I could do that.
Without like and yet somehow.
I could do that all boy stuff.
Crazy, right? Yeah. That's crazy.
Yeah.
Basically asking to me to be like,
oh, hey, girl, ha ha ha.
Fuck. Like, that kind of stuff.
And no,
or like, I could are like,
you want me to ask for your what?
You want me to ask for your number?
They only say, like, oh,
what kind of music do you listen to?
I like I like catchy.
Oh, what kind of
what kind of car do I ride?
I ride a Lexus.
I Well, what rank am I in? Legal legends.
I'm Diamond.
Oh, I like I like Supreme.
I, I go to raves, right?
I love Boba.
I love Boba so much like that.
That's pretty much what you're asking.
Me to do right. Now.
I don't know the that's.
That's very much in. Yeah.
At least that's my experience
of a lot of them.
Yeah, that's the ah, I don't know.
From what
I've seen the Asian football experience.
Well like, I don't know.
Like most of them and most of them,
they always.
Right. A Lexus and have a perm. Yeah.
And have a perm.
No, they have a perm. Right.
And then they say it's all is,
is, is a perm.
No, it's all natural.
It's all natural curls.
Like a liar.
OK, I'm done.
I'm done.
I don't want a clown.
I'm not clowning on people anymore.
Kevin, you went, huh?
Yeah, pretty much a Kevin Nealon.
You guys know OK?
So, um, I'm not too sure
what else I could do right now.
Do you guys have any suggestions?
Any suggestions at all?
You only say, Hey, girlie, who says that?
Who says that?
Who or what? Who the fuck says.
Oh, hey, girlie, stay still for me.
Like it does.
Not come out really well, child. Ha
I had to put on my cologne.
That's put on my headphones for this
because I'm.
I want to know till
is this is this the right video?
What are your
I'm not going to listen to that.
That's all I need to hear.
I'm not listening to that.
Sorry, guys.
As much as you would want me to.
I don't think I don't think I could last
another 2 seconds into that video.
That's not the. Video.
OK, well, I don't care. That's not the.
That's not the video.
What did
I what did you guys make me watch?
Oh, no.
Mm can I have a kiss
oh, sure.
Thank you for the tone.
Oh, give me a second.
Let me do more.
Believable sounds. Believable.
Believable sounds.
What are believable?
Sounds like
pop, pop, pop, pop.
Like that.
Was mine.
It sounds like a it sounds like a, um.
What's it a fish?
It sounds like I'm a fish.
There's our kiss, though.
I almost forgot.
It sounds like a pop.
Yeah, pops.
Those are.
Pop noises.
I don't know if that's what you wanted,
but I.
I did that.
I hope that's.
I hope that's correct.
Yes, it was. OK, cool. Cool.
Thank you.
You want me to pretend that I'm drunk,
but I need to explain to my
partner that I'm not drunk.
I don't know how to pretend to be drunk
because. It's
I've never.
Had to, like, pretend to be drunk before
in my life because, like,
why would you need to pretend to be drunk,
right?
You just,
you know, when you're drunk, you're drunk.
You're just like. A little.
Tipsy and kind of, you know, out of it.
And just don't you have, like,
no inhibitions and all that?
Yeah.
You know, I found out I found out that
what kind of. Drunk was I? I'm not.
I'm not like a sleepy I'm
not sleepy drunk, but I am a
I'm a
I'm like a happy, like, very happy.
Vibes drunk.
And also just chill and happy.
Yeah, I'd say I'm chill.
I'm happy and ah,
you would think I'd be horny.
You would think I'm a horny drunk.
But no, I'm not.
All I really am is just
I just feel I just feel like I'm here
to have a good time.
And I want a hug.
I get affectionate.
Oh, yeah.
I get really affectionate. When I'm drunk.
I'm like, I want to hug.
I want to hug people
when I get drunk, like,
and not even, like, get, you know, like,
that type of vibe.
Just I want to just hold somebody
or, like, be held by somebody.
Either way, you know, body contact
it's the help of the top of the comfort
even more, I think, just enhance it
a lot of people
asking for goodnight kisses right now.
Sure, I can do that.
You worked hard today, darling.
Goodnight.
Sleep well.
Good luck tomorrow.
Come come that they're gone, buddy.
Come up the hotel
I don't know which one it was.
Well, I need.
Well, I need what I need.
Oh, I in there.
I say.
Well, OK. Good night, guys.
For those of you
that want to sleep, rest well, OK.
Don't stay up too long.
Yeah.
Please don't stay up too long.
I'll be sad
these ones are the.
I was the.
I'm not doing that again.
The old Katie, go sit in some.
Or. Go. Honey, sit your foot in these two.
Sorry.
Don't know what she that bullshit.
I. I can't some
I don't know if it can if like.
Rips a part of me a rips a part of my soul
on. I want to try and see that it's.
Not I'm.
Sorry you guys only get the
one time in the one time ever
you just did.
Know there's a difference.
Between reading it
and like you know during the whole.
A guy Katie Kyrie ill.
Voice and.
And to.
Be all flirty,
you know, is there's a difference there
yeah.
And that
oh, what happen?
Hold on.
Are all. I.
Issued thank you for. The are do.
Thank you for those 52
and give some stupid holy shit
thank you so much
help you enjoying the stream so far
and hope
you're having a good night
you know I can say I can do more
I can see some stuff
in different languages
if you guys want me to
that is
that is not you know to does not bad it's
you natural me
yeah it's not do not show me
with anything that's like. I don't know.
Not like
who tongue you know whatever that
the Tagalog thing was
nothing like that
here we go. Uh,
oh, yes.
Here's a pug par pugi pugi I young
pugi I pugi I don
t daughter boring.
You bet.
I think that's it.
T daughter.
Putting. Your bed.
I don't know if I said that right.
I don't know what the fuck that means.
Again, I just know that it was it's very
it's very lewd, isn't it?
I know it's.
Isn't that lewd?
I think that's pretty lewd.
It sounds a little
foggy.
I am.
Yeah, I think so.
And are
my, my friend Allie
ever since she told me about that,
I've had it there.
I forgot what it means.
I have to ask
somebody. Can someone translate that?
Yes. It's
it just means let's sleep together.
That that's wholesome.
It's like,
hey, let's go to bed and sleep, right?
It just means that sleep together
that's all that's it's adorable.
My alligator
and my.
Keeper
oh, I need to
oh. Was that
can you say that bucket?
What does that mean again?
Oh, no, oh.
Oh, paging means.
Good morning, baby.
Oh, I see.
It's just a very it's just more
more cute Terms of Endearment.
I don't know.
OK, on,
on on you, him
and and
yeah.
And then there is, like,
something. Else to call off that I think.
I don't know.
If I. I don't, I'd see I don't know yet
you all.
But don't people say like Depp
or isn't that is that, like, kind of like,
you know, belittling?
I don't know.
It's like saying, oh,
you look very handsome.
You look very beautiful.
Are you something? I don't know.
Got it.
I don't know.
I'm like that.
People would probably know that
yeah.
It doesn't mean beautiful. OK,
LA on lemon mocha.
Got it.
Llama on local.
Got it was.
Let me try that again
llama on mocha got it
llama on local. Girl
that's Korean.
What did I just say?
No, they see something bad.
I hope I didn't say anything bad
all it's not.
Oh, it just. Means
you want to eat ramen together. That's it.
OK, that's not that's
what's bad about that.
Well, you guys are making it seem like
it's such a bad thing.
Let's eat ramen.
Oh, OK.
Play is it's the whole on.
Hello.
It's the Korean version of Netflix
and chill
it is.
Has a bad vinny. What do you mean
as of that?
Meaning, guys, it doesn't
that doesn't seem to that.
OK, maybe all zen are.
Now I know.
What is your guys's languages
versions of like Netflix and chill.
OK, well,
I guess I know it for it. I'm on.
No go. Got it.
OK, for Korean
it's sexually suggestive. Oh.
I mean that I mean.
Netflix they you want to Netflix and chill
that's OK.
We can we can get Cosby on the couch
and then they can be like,
oh, are you still there?
Right where no no.
You want to say, well, I can do that
one more time.
Yeah.
Oh, I need to
Russian are lovely
Russian
masala.
Call my car cayenne hot
my alcohol Kyle hot.
It means I love you all.
Oh, I hope I oh, that's what it means.
Can you say in there
to seal
in there
to seal,
seal, seal, seal.
I think it's seal yeah.
To seal
I think that's ask out asking for a kiss
or you want to give me a kiss, please?
You guys have,
like, changed,
rocked my whole ramen thing.
It doesn't seem that bad to me.
It really doesn't seem that bad.
Like who? What, what?
It doesn't seem like a.
Bad thing to be like,
hey, you want to go here? Romance.
The other vibe.
I guess it's like the
the cultural implication from I know I'm
not Korean, so my
you know,
I say just ski ski.
Hey. Suck
test succumb.
So I cannot.
Oh, my God, that's so hard to read.
Is that Russian?
That looks Russian to me.
Don't succumb, suck OK?
Ah. Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Ah. Do I have any Russians in chat
that know how to, like, stop?
Annunciate that because it is hard
to romanised that language
sometimes.
None then solid
son Yoda and none non a.
Son that you
don't know what that means
son, huh?
OK. You
yeah.
Daniel
Daniel I.
Mean, I said oh.
Again.
The Z number.
It done well, not on the Lord.
I don't do I don't do French accents.
Well,
that's like it's a hard accent.
For me.
I, I should just play more chamber, right?
And I can get used to it.
Yeah, I know.
I know how to say I love you.
And in the Russians.
Yeah, like you said.
Yeah, Libya dip. Yeah, yeah.
Libya dip. Yeah,
let me switch ears.
So it's not like deep inside.
Ah, one ear the entire time.
You want to play?
Let's play.
Yeah.
I got back into civilian again recently,
and that's all I can think about
is when he says, you want to play,
let's play I mean, I would say
he's a kinky French dude, but I love his
I love his kit.
His guns are awesome.
I love his using his all a lot so far. Is
going to be one of my favourite,
you know, my favourite all agents.
So can you please say ah,
yeah.
That's a cute way of calling Elder Brother
in Chinese. OK,
ok, kiki,
older brother
in Chinese
I hope I'm pronouncing this thing.
Jack.
Jack, you. Are
mm hmm.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
I, I don't know.
I don't know. Out of pronounce it.
It's novel.
Don't believe me, sir.
Ha ha ha ha.
Tom, I'm embarrassed now.
You guys embarrassing me
and I don't often answer Gaga.
It's Gaga.
Oh, then why is the e?
Why is the E? There are only Josh
don't look at me. You
got Gaga.
Gaga?
Oh, no.
I got to get this right now.
I got to learn how to say this. Huh?
G is k ga ga ga.
G is k ga ga.
Ga ga ga ga ga ga
ga ga ga
a. Close close.
I'm gonna get kick, kick, go
get them.
OK, ok.
Look, I feel softer.
A sound.
Pop. I don't know I need to listen to it.
I need to.
Like,
listen to somebody say it because, like.
I do better.
When I hear it.
Like,
I can't just do it based off of letters.
Right I need.
To actually hear it sometimes,
and then I can do it perfectly after
I hear at least, like, a couple of times.
Yeah, ok.
Yeah. OK.
OK. OK, ok.
OK. Shh.
I don't know.
I don't know. Man.
Does Google translate it?
Oh, my god. I'm
I'm sweating.
I am.
I am sweating right now because, man,
you guys really embarrassed me
with that one.
I just decided no sobs.
OK, ok, ok.
Yeah. Mm hmm.
I'll I'll figure it out.
I will. I'll figure it out.
I know. Time after this.
OK, so. The.
All right.
I'll.
I promise I'll I'll.
I'll learn it for for next time. OK?
Mm hmm. Hmm.
I'll I'll try.
I better I'll check that ok?
All right.
Now, I'll go back to like, two other
other stuff I can say
is on me.
Say, Ohio.
I oh, darling,
and I'll darling
darling,
darling.
Darling.
Darling,
darling,
darling.
Darling,
darling, on
singing de la la la la la
la la for you does. Oh.
I'm going again right now.
And you say
well.
We'll see.
Why? I hope that's not bad.
I hope that's not.
I don't know what that says.
I don't. Want to say anything that's. Bad.
I don't know.
I don't know what it means.
I ask me, darling.
I ask me oh yes, me
it means I like you.
Oh, oh, it just means I like you, OK?
Another.
Oh, I can do this one.
Yeah, I've done before. OK.
Cynthia, come up
a chimp.
Come up
yonder
yonder a softball
and the racial pull back.
I mean, did
good boy.
Good boy.
Good girl.
Mm. La la la.
Hmm. Sue. Sue.
What is Sue?
I should sue.
I sure mean
well, I mean, is.
Is that tough of Sue?
All I need. Hmm.
Is that a name is on, then?
I don't know.
Sound or I said say on before
now. I know
oh, polish.
Hold on.
Column
Cogent.
Column C consider
call to call and see I.
Oh, my God.
I don't know. Polish dialect.
So I'm very unfamiliar with that.
Slow, but surely I'm getting more used
to a Swedish dialect, though, because of.
I like, there is like I know
there's like a phrase that he says
that's like, just lovely something.
Zavala It's something.
It's just more Swedish cursing. Yeah.
Don't tell him I said that.
Yeah, don't tell him I don't tell my said
anything bad.
He got mad. At me
when I said the word for pussy
in the Swedish
understandably so,
because I think it's, it's like,
I think it's like,
you know, offence is like.
Why would you say that?
You know,
uh, salamat
malum sama
salamat malum.
I means goodnight.
Right, goodnight
amu yeah.
I said on you him but m u
m m you don't know what that means.
It means.
Darling. In Vietnamese.
Oh, darling, I'm Vietnamese.
Gotcha.
I want to learn more.
Like I want to learn more stuff
that's equivalent ah.
The Netflix and chill shit that we said
before.
Like, how do you how.
Do you guys say like, hey,
one want to come over and do something?
But in actuality, like, you're,
you're like, you know,
it's like a code phrase for sex, right?
Like, of the whole, like a common mockery
thing.
To know if anyone has that.
Oh, wait.
So on said Toradol detail.
What Jollibee OJ what's
really.
Jelly.
Really
OK, that doesn't sound right. OK.
Lao low
ball.
Yeah. What is what does that mean?
I should look,
I should look these things up.
Lao Paul Alpo.
Lao Bo Alpo.
It means old.
Lady.
It means wife.
Oh, it means wife.
Ha, it has a lot of juicy meanings.
This is what it says.
Why? Oh, why would it have.
Juicy meanings, huh?
Isn't it just mean wife. Most of all?
Why would it?
Why would I have juicy meanings?
What does that mean?
Juicy. Huh?
OK. It's flirty.
Oh, oh, it's flirty. OK,
that's really cool.
That's the way to describe it, I guess.
Juicy. Yeah,
ok. OK.
I see. Thank you.
I'm being educated
and being more and more educated
by the day.
If all they see is.
Oh, ok. OK.
All right, Barbie.
Got it.
I feel like, ok.
I feel like I've embarrassed myself
enough.
Were far off
trying to say these and say all this.
So I will simply
leave you guys off with a long, sloppy
kiss.
So, hey, prepare your ears
because it's about to get really,
really personal.
Mm hmm.
I think that was my mom in the background.
She probably just sneezed. OK.
And did you hear that?
Did you hear that?
Mom, get out of here!
God! Get out!
Mom, cut down.
There it goes again.
There she goes again.
OK, ok, ok, ok, ok.
It's just me and you.
Just me and you. All right?
I just got.
To say bless you.
Yeah, I guess. Bless you.
Got it.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
OK, I think I think
I think I got the message clear.
Anyways, let.
Me until
I feel like I'm being ard right now, is
is that the right word to describe it?
I'm being cuts.
I don't know.
Cock blocked.
Yeah.
If there is a
there's any way to experience a cock block
and be like this ok?
Yeah.
Yeah, wow.
And hmm.
Mm. Mm
hmm. No.
Oh, mm mm
mm mm mm mm mm
mm mm
mm mm mm mm
am I.
Good boy.
My good boy.
Oh, ok.
OK. Oh,
oh, all right. Oh.
South kisses.
You heard a car? Yeah, it was a car.
Ignore the car.
Listen to me.
OK? Don't I don't get tired
and get distracted by other things.
Why you look,
why are you focussing on other stuff?
You should be focussing on me.
Why aren't you focussing on me? Hmm?
Hmm. OK.
I can't do that anymore.
All right,
but i think that is going to be it
for for this dream today.
Yeah.
I don't think I have anything else on the
on the menu either.
Not uh oh.
Hold on. Let me,
let me quickly
look through any other terminations
that I might have missed.
Yunji. Thank you for that.
So nation. You're so cute.
Your face is cute.
Cindy,
thank you for the $6.90 of what I need.
Well, in the end.
The birds. Are finally coming out.
A. Melania.
Thank you for that. So now, um,
you know about this Chinese thing?
Oh, I don't know.
Do I have a Chinese name?
I don't know.
You know, like, how.
In other languages are people give like,
people other
I don't know were just like nicknames.
And stuff like that. Do I have a nickname?
I don't think I do. It's a shuttle, right?
And a shuttle.
I'm not sure if you know, people call me
anything else
or, like, some kind of, like, pet name.
Yeah.
Not shotgun.
No, not shotgun.
Keno. Thank you for that.
I'll no into guru. Guru.
Thank you for.
That's on our
teacher Shin
ask sister for a kiss.
I hope that what
an only thank you for
the donation as well
and thank you for that.
Till now congrats on 300 k.
I've been listening to your stream
on the train after a long day
and it's been really relaxing and sussy.
And sussy.
and it was a great way to end the day.
Thank you for sharing. No problem. Set up.
You enjoyed the time
and have a wonderful time going back home.
OK, stay safe.
You're going there.
That's where you make a
thank you for this.
I know I am
in depth on you
some flora. Thank you for that.
Now. Panel, Myanmar.
Myanmar
fearless. Poppy, thank you for the donor.
I recently felt particularly happy
because I met you, although the previous
also lived a very happy life.
After knowing you feel more happy.
I think I understand
what you were trying to say there. And
I think you mean
was it
happy that you got to know me
better through the previous dreams?
And, hey, I'll be enjoying
more to come there.
Thank you for coming by today.
I hope it wasn't too.
Too awkward. For you.
The whole lot is similar experience.
I won't be doing this next week, though.
Because it was just like one more time
to try and feel a little bit
more confident about it.
And I feel like I succeeded in that
actually.
Thank you for that, John. On Zero.
I for the till now you play say coffee,
tea or me.
With a goodnight kiss.
You want me to be like.
Oh, hey, hey honey, do you want coffee?
Or maybe you want saw you want some tea
would you like me instead
do think that it's OK?
No, just thank you for that done not to
you know thank you for that on though
and the thank you for the five to ones
OK I can
catch up on all of them
oh everything anything extreme.
You guys you and your friends
have been under a lot of pressure recently
because of some work mistakes.
How do you relieve the work pressure?
How do I relieve work pressure?
Masturbate
just kidding.
I usually like to play some video games
and I like to sing a lot.
So most of the time, whenever I'm
feeling anxious or stressed out,
I try to
what's it.
I try to sing a song or
like sing a few songs that I really enjoy
at the time.
And singing really helps take the,
you know, anxiety away
and I get to just vibe out with a,
you know, with a song
that I've been I'm comfortable with.
It lets out
a lot of tension from your like,
I'll know from your brain
when you're just like lose your thoughts
in the lyrics, in the melody,
singing or video games.
So I like playing golf
and fantasy league and you know,
Bellerin in Minecraft
maybe
you can learn to introduce yourself in
Chinese.
Are Ni
ni hao or C shot ball.
Oh, thank you for
thank you for the lesson for today.
I hope I get more lessons in the upcoming
shootings.
Teach me more.
OK, thank you.
I would love to that.
That sounds. Cute.
I would like to learn more phrases
sorry I could use on a daily basis
like survive if I ever want to
if I ever needed to use Chinese.
Really ok.
Yeah,
we're going to end it off here guys.
So be sure to have a good night and
I don't think we're going to be reading
anybody.
We're just going to end it off here
and we're going to relax, chill.
And you sure have a good night.
Have a good rest of your day
off. Here you go.
I want to see one more thing,
if that's OK.
If you guys.
All right,
I'll phone
for some of you.
It's really late, so you can pretend that
this is like you're laying down on me or
you can fall asleep
on my chest if you'd like,
right?
Yeah.
Just one more time.
Cuddles hmm.
Goodnight.
So, Paul.
OK, OK.
Take care.
And I'll see you next week.
Uh uh
uh uh.
uh ok.
Um, before we head off,
um, just be sure to join the discord.
Yeah. If you are. Or.
If you want to join discord, it's discord.
Social pull.
And be sure to follow on Twitter on the
suffering tea and subscribe on YouTube.
I posted a new YouTube video today
that I think you guys would like.
So check it out, ok. Showed some love. And
also thank you for 300.
Again, thank you for a thank.
On the on switch.
We hit this milestone so fast
and it just keeps getting
bigger and bigger so and I feel like I'm
not able to catch up, but
I hope that I'll be able to handle
all the new guilties that come on by
and hopefully you guys
can set a good example to
Night guilties.
All right. Have a good day. OK.
Take care and I'll see you next time.
Bye bye.
Well, there's another hype train.
You guys start hype train before I leave.
What's why would you start a hiring before
I had a job offer today?
Bruh bruh.
OK, but have a good night.
All right. Take care. And I love you.
OK? Oh,
yeah.
I'm big.
There you go. No.